So I'm Nora Herold. I know
a lot of you are familiar with my work. For those
of you who are meeting me for the first time,
I've been channeling consciously
for about 20 years.
Um, but for all of my life, I was hearing things
and feeling things and seeing things and
knowing things and I didn't
have a context for it.
I didn't understand it.
Oftentimes it felt distracting and overwhelming.
I didn't really understand that it could be
an experience that would support or contribute to
my reality.
And then in 1996 I found myself in
a ball on the floor.
At the age of 29 years old, going through my Saturn return,
my first Saturn return.
And I was depressed and had gone
through a very dramatic breakup and felt
brokenhearted.
And you know the beautiful thing about heartbreak
is it opens us all up.
And in that very open space I was
hanging out with a dear friend one night who read
tarot cards as I also read tarot cards.
I'd read tarot cards for years. I'd played with crystals. You know,
I'd started to tune in consciously at
about the age of 20.
She mentions that she had met a woman recently who
channeled her spirit guides.
And that woman was Wendy Kennedy. So this is back
in Chicago back in 1996. And I said oh
I think that's what I'm looking for. And why don't
we try? And she said great, I've been trying and she'd
had some luck,
feeling something. But when the two of us sat down together that night
with the intention to connect it happened almost immediately.
I felt the presence of a being
that was so loving,
so calming,
and so nurturing to me. It was unlike anything
I had ever experienced as Nora
before.
And it was very quick moment. I felt his
love. I felt his energy as male and
I knew his name started with an M.
And then the tube on Amy's television blew
out.
As Amy was also having her own connection experience. And then very
shortly afterwards, she and I got together with Wendy, and that was my first
meeting with Wendy Kennedy. And Wendy, Amy,
and I channeled together
for play, for fun, for quite some time. That was how
we spent our evenings was hanging out channeling for
each other, channeling for our friends, you know,
we didn't go to bars and get drunk. We stayed in my apartment, my little
basement apartment in Chicago and ate cookies
and channeled.
And then at some point it became clear that
this was the service work that
I was here to do.
So it is now what I do. It's what I've done for a very long
time and my work has evolved over the years. I channel many
different beings. The Pleiadian Collective
is primary right now in my channeling work
and then Yeshua and Calliandra are close behind,
and then behind them the Lyrans and the
archangels and all the other beings. And
so many beings participate when we channel, you
know, it's funny, you know listening to Shelley bring through Gabriel
and I could feel all the other energies braiding in
and working through her as well.
It's true for everyone I listened to yesterday,
so the same will happen today. What I
recommend for all of you
is that you really...
allow yourselves to recognize
your own experience of channeling while I'm
channeling today.
Because to be able to receive channeled information in any
format means that your channeling.
Doesn't matter that's coming out of my mouth.
You're acting as the receivers for the information as well. Okay, I'm
going to sit down now.
I'm gonna straighten myself out here. How's my hair? Okay. Now
now Nora will quiet down. I'll
tell you that when I channel. I'm very present.
So you may hear from me again during the channeling portion. Okay?
(Oming sounds)
Ahhhhh.....
Fantastic!
Greetings, this is the Pleiadian Collective and as always
it is so wonderful to connect with all of you
beautiful universal beings of
light and love, look at you all.
Look at your beauty!
Look at your light!
Look at the beauty in the projection of
your light bodies into your
physical reality, see yourselves right
now as the beautiful beings you are.
Both beings of light,
beings holding physical density. Feel your
bodies, put your hands on your body.
Yeah.
Put your hands somewhere that particularly you don't like.
Alright, find a find a place on your body that you
perhaps might not think is so beautiful. Alright, and just
breathe.
And connect.
This is your light!
What you're touching right now
is you,
your light.
You are love
incarnate.
You are nothing else.
All around you
is love incarnate, nothing else.
Doesn't matter what it looks like, feels like,
the costume it's wearing.
Love incarnate, the table,
the chair,
the ceiling, the walls, the air, the atmosphere,
the Republican, the Democrat, the Illuminati.
Yeshua, us, you, love incarnate.
Love playing a game. That's all this is.
And that's all there is
to the idea of awakening from within.
And as we look at all of you,
what we see: all of you here in this room, all
of you listening in, all of you tuning in at
a later date,
is you're already awake.
Right?  Who in the room feels awake?
Yes.
And yet you continue to awaken.
Because this is the game.
You wake up, you remember right? You all remember
that? Yes, remember when you woke up? Everyone here had some
sort of an awakening moment. It may have
been very small. It may have been gigantic. It really
doesn't matter, every single one of you at some point
came in awake,
went back to sleep, because that's what happened, for all
of you. Most of the children coming in now, they don't have
to go through this, you know.
They're not going back to sleep as you all did.
Sometimes they take little naps, alright?
They forget for a bit of time who they are
and then it's very easy for them to wake themselves up and remember. But
you all,
you came into an incredibly dense environment awake
and then went back to sleep because that
was the game plan. That's the program. You weren't
supposed to remember
throughout the totality of this incarnation
that you are love incarnate.
You were supposed to come in, forget that,
throw on a costume,
create a whole bunch of drama for yourselves,
work through a myriad of issues,
traumas,
most of which have nothing to do with this incarnation.
Alright so think about that piece right now. Anytime you've given
yourself something to work on in this lifetime, what
you've also been doing and the main reason
you gave yourselves those things to
work on, is you've been clearing up with yourselves all
of these unhealed traumas from all of
these other lifetimes, that didn't happen in the past,
that are happening right now,
because all is now, right?
Every version of you that you see is a past life version of you, is
truly existing right now in a
moment in time, currently experiencing whatever pain,
whatever loss, whatever grief, whatever anger, whatever
hurt, whatever anguish, etc. And throughout this
incarnation you have picked up again
and again and again and again these pieces
of your oversoul that
are sitting in distress. You have interacted with
them,
sent them transmissions of unconditional love as you
have worked on your own stuff.
And suddenly you find yourself then to be a much more powerful, clear,
and sovereign being.
Ever wonder if there's intelligent
life elsewhere in the universe?
Well, I have....I've been wondering since I was a kid.
My name is Reuben Langdon.
And on March 29th, 2007, in the middle of the day,
I saw a number of strange objects in the sky.
Coincidentally, I was working on
the film Avatar at the time, playing an alien.
And ever since then I've been on a quest...
A quest to find out if aliens really do exist and if so...
...are they here with us?
If beings of higher intelligence are here...
...what is their purpose?
Why don't they make themselves more known?
Why the secrecy?
I've asked these questions to many experts,
yet, each seems to have a different theory.
So I thought to myself,
why not ask the aliens directly?
So that's what I set out to do!
Well, sort of...
Nora.
Reuben.
Here we are, thank you for doing this
second time, sort of.  We've been filming you on and off here.
Um.
Can you describe to me
the process of what do you do and
what kind of energies do you tap into
and then hopefully we can tap into them today?
Sure. So I do what's called direct voice channeling.
I also translate, so there are two different
versions of channeling work.
Translation is, I listen and receive and then tell
you in my own voice the information
I'm getting and what I hear and often do
that when I work privately in one-on-one sessions
I'll do some translation work
and I'll use my own voice and they've
expressed the importance of us, all of us,
accessing information in a variety of ways.
So that's one of the ways I access
information, but then I also direct voice channel.
So direct voice channel means I
raise my personal vibration to a point
where I can connect up with beings who
exist in a higher dimension, another
vibration, another frequency. They
interact with me telepathically, move
through me energetically, I allow them to
alter my vocal cords, speak directly through me.
The beings I work with are
the Pleiadian Collective. So they're a twelfth
dimensional collective of beings that, if
we were going to assign them a location
in our third dimensional version of reality --
Twelfth dimension - how do you even
have that? I mean that's even so far out
of Earthly terms, but...
It's different experience, different flavors along with
that comes different abilities, different awareness.
So when I say twelfth dimensional Pleiadian Collective -
they are a gigantic being
of love and light, that knows themselves
to be one, and yet understands that they
are comprised of many ones, but they do
not each individuate themselves like we
do here on Earth.
Hence the term 'collective'. So it's not a
specific being in particular.
That's correct, but there are specific beings
I work with as well. So the Pleiadians are
one of many groups and beings I work
with. A specific being would be
Calliandra, she's a fifth dimensional
fairy, so we'll call her a fairy,
that's how she presented
herself to me. I also work with Yeshua.
I see Yeshua to be a collective being,
but we know that being to be an
individual entity that we call Jesus
on this planet. But I know that
energy to be a collective energy.
Or the Archangel Michael at times will come
through me, the Lyrans, beings from
Lemuria, the Zeta's have made contact
with me. It's a very in-the-moment
process for me, but the majority of the
information I'm accessing at this time
is coming from the Pleiadians, Yeshua,
and Calliandra, those are kind of the big three for me.
And are you, you're
present in your awareness when
this happens, it's not like you conk out
and then and then you wake up and I go,
what happened? I've seen that,
I've seen people who have channeled and
that's taking place.
Yes, so what you're talking about there is
trance channeling. Trance channeling? Yes. What I do is
called conscious channeling and/or
semi-conscious channeling. And you
can even see a difference in me when I'm
fully conscious and then when I'm semi-conscious.
So has that happened to you in the past?
Yes. So the fully conscious channeling is more that,
okay, I'm accessing the information, I'm gonna
give it to you right now: Reuben,
they're telling me: blah blah blah blah blah blah.
So that's almost like, when you work with clients --
Yes.
Hearing it and kind of translating it --
And then I will go into a semi-conscious state
with clients as well where then I allow the
Pleiadians, Yeshua, whomever in the moment
to directly work through my body.
Is there...you must resonate with all the
different frequencies otherwise they wouldn't
be coming through. Do you have a favorite?
Or can you not say?
Do I have a favorite? Depends on the day?
Yeah, it's really, it's the
Pleiadians, Calliandra, and Yeshua. I could
not pick one of those out of the three.
However, I'm aware that I have a very
specific contract with the Pleiadians.
And I believe that's why they're
predominantly coming through right now
and I've really noticed that over the
last year especially when I go into the
semi-conscious direct voice channeling
state, it's mostly the Pleiadians
transmitting and then occasionally
Yeshua, Calliandra, the others, the Lyrans,
Lemurians. In the past there used to
be more of a variety in my work, so I'm
very aware that for now, maybe we'll
say the Pleiadians are my favorite.
Sorry, Calliandra. Sure she understands. Oh she understands,
but she's like this right now.
Well, maybe we can give her some time to voice as well.
Well, in addition to being a channeler,
or maybe this goes hand in
hand, because you're also clairvoyant or
a clairaudient or is that kind of one and the same?
So language is very interesting because we use it to
help us understand and label and then we can
often then limit and categorize.
Channels will use their clairvoyant,
their clairaudient, they're clairsentient
abilities to help them access
information. Yes, I am also as Nora
however, very intuitive, psychic,
clairvoyant, clairaudient, clairsentient.
That's a little bit different from channeling.
Yes, that's me using my own operating system.
So and you have those abilities as well. Awesome.
Because I've talked with other, I guess,
intuitive people, in quotes, where to me
and after hearing the process, it sounds
like they were just tapping into like
more channel type you know.
Well, it wasn't me, it was I heard a voice and
this is this is what I'm getting, and you
know, most the time it's accurate so.. But
I just wondered how your operating system works?
Yes, and really when it
comes down to it, it's all information
coming from source energy. Whether you
access it directly in your own body or
you access it from a vibration or a
frequency outside of you. We are all
source, we are all that love energy
incarnate. It's just fun to get to do it
different ways. That's one of the gifts
of being here on planet Earth, we get the
variety and the selection.
And you know and yeah getting to that and maybe
this is a question later for the
Pleiadians, but by giving it these
labels, is that just more because I've
noticed some people who are new to the
intuitive side of things they're
feeling energies, they're hearing it, but they
don't, maybe they don't know how to
categorize them right or is it
even appropriate to categorize it?
How does that, you know how does that all--
when ultimately we're trying to get
to a place where we're not labeling
anything at all. How does that help us
and does that serve us?
I think it helps initially to label, categorize, to help
the mental body catch up and understand
what it is you're already doing in your
emotional and energetic and physical
bodies and then once you achieve that
level of understanding, it's very
important to release the labels and the
attachments and just be in the moment.
Because then your mind has relaxed. So
the mental body was really set up to
filter out the third dimensional mental
body. Was set up to filter out all of
this input, all of this information.
Zoe, you're now part of the movie, officially.
So this is Zoe. Zoe is an elf and a
unicorn. We like to call Zoe the Alphacorn
because she brings through the
elfin and the unicorn energies strongly
in our space.
We have a couple of cats, one is bringing through
the fairy vibration and the other
Pleiadian frequency and vibration. Animals,
they are definitely helping us here on
so many levels. We've had Zoe now for
just a little over a year and she has
brought with her such an amazing
transmission of unconditional love and
fun and play, our entire reality has
shifted with her presence.
I've noticed that with animals, if humans
could operate on an animal level in so many
ways that you know where we... it's
like they do something and we're mad at
them but then they're in the doghouse so
to say, but two minutes later they're: oh
I didn't do anything, or
I forgive you or whatever. You know they
can't, even if you are physically angry
with them or something, they'll you know:
it's okay, the ultimate show of how to forgive.
Yes. And also how to be present.
They're extremely in the moment, they don't
tie their moments together
in the way that we do and
they also don't filter out the
information that our mental bodies
filter out. Coming back to, back around to
that -- thank you, Zoe -- so I'm aware that
Zoey and Izzy and Ursula the Smurf, our
cats, are always interacting with the
beings that are present in our space.
I see them watching the beings and seeing
things that I can't access in the moment.
Excellent. Well thanks guys, let us know
if something pops in here, maybe we'll catch it on film.
Well, I guess the last question before we move in
is: when you were trying to find labels I
guess, or if you weren't even
trying but did
they present themselves and say I am
such and such, I am Pleiadian Collective,
I am Calliandra. Is that how it happened or
were you able to... how did that come
to you, for each? So initially it wasn't
that easy. Okay yeah, that's what I figured,
I knew there'd be a story to this. With the Pleiadians it
was easy. Immediately I recognized that
the transmission from the Pleiadians as
a Pleiadian transmission.
I recognized it in my body, in a visceral
way. It was very clear to me that's who I
was in contact with, and I'd been aware
of the Pleiadian energy so my
mental body had already accepted the
truth of the Pleiadian Collective and
their work with us here on Earth. So when
they made direct contact with me,
my mental body didn't freak out and try to
screen out that piece of information, it
was clear to me. Now many of the other
beings that I've worked with, it's taken
me some time to kind of work my way into
discerning who it was I was connecting
with. Now when I say time, I mean perhaps
a matter of minutes or hours, yes. It's
never been longer than that and that's
just I guess part of my operating system.
Calliandra, for instance, when she first
made herself known to me, I felt a new
being link up with me -- I was preparing
for radio interview that night -- I could
feel this really wonderful playful
presence, and immediately I knew it to be
fairy. So again Nora had accepted fairies,
that was easy, ah I know this vibration to
be fairy. So I asked for a name and
I got the name initially Calliana. So I was
playing with Calliana, I was like okay, and
I thought no, that's not quite right, and
then I got Calliandra -- got it.
As soon as I heard, felt, that's really
predominantly how I access information
when I'm not in the semi-conscious
direct voice channeling state, ok? So when
Nora is conscious and awake,
and when I choose to seek out
information
as Nora, meaning information I can't just
read from a book or you know, I feel it
and I hear it. I hear the words. I see it.
I see it sometimes like words on the
paper. I see the story. Very occasionally
I access more of my clairvoyant
abilities, meaning I will see an image,
I'll see some light, I'll see a story
playing out in my mind's eye. So I felt,
heard, the name Calliandra and thought okay
her name is Calliandra. And then I had to
go outside and ground myself because I
was working with a new vibration, a new
frequency and I found it actually really
powerful and intense to work with a
fifth dimensional being. So I was used to
working with these very, very high
vibrations and high frequencies which
were in some ways easier to work with
because it's so... well, any of you
listening right now, if you just take a
breath, you can tune into that
light high, high vibration. Imagine it's
like interacting with a cloud, yes, gentle
easy, right. Calliandra was like
interacting with a sledgehammer, her
energy was so powerful because she has
more density to her vibration as a fifth
dimensional being. So I had to go outside
and stand on the ground. And then I came
in and sat in front of my computer and I
thought I'm gonna look up the word
Calliandra and see what I find, because I
like to also, if I can, back up my other
dimensional information with third
dimensional information and I googled
the word Calliandra, and it's a plant
called Fairy Duster and I'd not ever heard
that word before and
it was such a moment of validation for
me, which was great. I was gonna go on the
radio that night and introduce a new
being, so how wonderful that I got that.
So the information you got was
Calliandra the fairy and then the
validation was caught under the name...
So that took me a couple of hours to
answer that question and discerning
frequencies and vibrations. Sometimes
when I'm working with a client and someone who's
passed, connects up with me, you know
sometimes I'll feel immediately like oh
this is their mother whose passed. And
that's work that I don't do a lot of
but I do do it occasionally when it's
necessary. They will present themselves
to me and then typically I'll just ask
them questions of the client you know
where's your mother is usually how I'll
start, as opposed to I've made contact
with your mother, because that can be
startling for somebody who's lost...
But how about so-called dark
energies or even manipulating tricksters
or these kinds of, you know, what we see
typically in the movies...
Actually this whole experience, you know,
channeling, has kind of been made quite
negative in our media and with you
know, like "The Exorcist" and these kinds
of things. So I've interacted especially
when I first started channeling,
had a couple of interactions with
energies that felt, that seemed to be
wanting to guide, and seemed to be wanting
to give information and so initially it
was interesting and then, what I found
happening was I started feeling afraid.
Not of the being itself but of the
information they were giving me, it was
causing me to feel afraid. Afraid that I
wasn't going to have what I wanted in my
life, afraid that I wasn't really
powerful. So that's.. then I become aware,
oh I'm accessing another vibrational
energy that I don't want to be playing
with. And then I would just.. And that's
how you could kind of discern
which energy is there, just if it's
doing some..., if it's putting you in a
fear-based state. If you're accessing
an energy and you start to feel bad in
your body, it's not really an energy you
want to be playing with. So the thing to
do then is to just send a big
transmission of unconditional love to
that being, and raise your own
vibration. That clears the being out of
your space, it raises your energy. Then
you're able to reconnect with those
higher vibrational beings, and then you
can always - as well, if you're already channeling,
so if you're familiar with the process, you
can call on a being that you know to be
of a higher vibrational nature that
you're familiar with, to kind of
reconnect, solidify those connections.
I've heard of cases where
energies start out good, it's almost like
almost like the church, you know start
out good, with good love and light
messages and get people in and then
somewhere down the path the
message can kind of turn and then start
putting people in a fear-based situation
and then usually after they get a bunch
of people kind of already in, and you know
very much like a church type scenario.
Well the other issue that you're
touching on here is, you know as a
channel, you still have an ego. So
often what will happen is, in those
situations, the energy itself stays in
that high vibrational state - it's the
filter that alters, meaning the channel.
So I'm constantly checking my
filter. I'm constantly having to
disengage from any personal intention
or attachment to anything personally for
Nora, while channeling, or the person I'm
channeling for. So if I were channeling
for you, Reuben, in a private session and
I had a particular desire for you, for
your success let's say? If I was attached
to that, that would cloud my ability to
clearly discern the information that's
coming through and I'd put my own spin on it.
So what you're talking about
I think are those cults that have come up
around channels and things like that,
it's, you know, there's an imperative
underneath that the channel was running
for a prosperity issue or relationship
issue or sexual issue or whatever it is.
And suddenly 'the being' is recommending
everyone hand over their money,
when really, it's the channel speaking and
the being has no control over that.
So that's the other wonderful thing
about this co-creative work in channeling.
I can only bring through what I
allow myself to bring through. They can't
force me to do anything. So I can
alter the message, really, any time I want.
You really have to keep yourself in check though?
Yeah - and I have a lot of
lessons that I've experienced in this
lifetime to remind me to keep myself in check.
I'm sure they're guiding and helping you do that.
Yes, yes.
As long as you're paying attention.
And I guess when those others, that
we talked about, probably aren't paying
attention or you know they're not,
I'm sure those higher beings are
probably screaming at them and
then the ego kicks in and tunes them out.
I think those things happen for
karmic reasons or because they've got
trauma they haven't resolved, and that
trauma begins to spin this tale.
But the other thing you've got to look at here
is anybody who gets pulled in by
something like that, they are a
co-creator in that experience as well.
They are willingly handing over
their free will to that entity or that
higher being and that's their lesson as
well. So then the channel who's bringing
through the information in that way with
their own, perhaps, distorted filter
is suddenly serving to offer this lesson to
anybody who wants to hand over their
free will and forget they're sovereign.
Man, so many people hand over that free will so easily.
Well, we're also programmed
to be enslaved, so we really...
Is that a DNA programming, you think, or is that..?
It's in our genetic code and it's
something that we're in the process of
rewriting as we integrate our higher
selves because our higher selves don't
have that imperative to run the
enslavement games.
They don't have genetics, do they?
Well, they don't but, as we're integrating our
higher selves into our third dimensional
chakra system, our higher selves are
interacting with our physical genetic
structure.  Now I'm a bit
going into the channeling state, so I'm
not fully direct voice channeling, but if
you're paying attention to me you're
going to see I look a little different
right now because my eyes are starting
to get a, have a different focus, so the
Pleiadians are just reminding us right
now that as we integrate our higher
selves we are altering ourselves from
the inside out physically, genetically as
well and we're breaking down... Greetings!
This is the Pleiadians Collective as
always, it's wonderful to have the
opportunity to link up with you in this
way, and we'll give you back Nora if you need
her again? No this is a good transition.