What motivates relating?
What motivates that ability
to relate to another person?
that is sort of this desire to 'see'
and to be seen.
open up and have a sense of that openness
so that others can see you.
And you are open to
seeing them. It's like this intimacy.
I use the word 'see' because
when we are seeking to relate
we're really going back down
to basics of our five senses.
What am I seeing?
What am I perceiving
with my eyes?
Intuitively we might feel
something.
We might feel something different
than what our eyes are seeing.
But because our intuitive
body is picking up something.
That doesn't necessarily mean
it's true for the other person.
In this relatability we're
focussing on what we're
physically observing.
So there is an inner knowing
that needs to be paid
attention to,
an acknowledgment of
what is in feeling,
and our society often will
talk about these boundaries
and I think those are important,
but I think those boundaries
can also be readdressed
with how we intuitively
feel in the moment.
Sometimes intuitively you will be
like this is a bad situation
I'm outta here,
I'm getting completely latched
onto and drained,
and I've had that before,
it's definitely a different feeling
to have to be emotionally
in tune with yourself.
Ever wonder if there's intelligent
life elsewhere in the universe?
Well, I have....I've been wondering since I was a kid.
My name is Reuben Langdon.
And on March 29th 2007, in the middle of the day,
I saw a number of strange objects in the sky.
Coincidentally, I was working on
the film Avatar at the time, playing an alien.
And ever since then I've been on a quest...
A quest to find out if aliens really do exist and if so...
...are they here with us?
If beings of higher intelligence are here...
...what is their purpose?
Why don't they make themselves more known?
Why the secrecy?
I've asked these questions to many experts,
yet each seems to have a different theory.
So I thought to myself,
why not ask the aliens directly?
So that's what I set out to do!
Well, sort of...
>> All right.
Deete.
Thank you for having me here.
I wanted to find out a
little bit about yourself
and your process, and
your journey, and--
>> All that jazz.
>> --all that jazz.
Where do you want to start, or where
would you like to start?
>> All right.
So I grew up Mormon
since day one.
Born in Salt Lake City.
We did move to Phoenix,
so I didn't grow up
in Salt Lake City.
But growing up with
that religious mindset,
that was a big program that
I had to break free from.
And I think part of the
reason that my journey started
was two things that
was the catalyst, which
was my grandma passing
away and, prior to that,
I was sort of feeling like I
had had enough of this life
and was ready to kill myself.
>> Oh, wow.
>> Yeah, I didn't know how
to break out of the religion
and the mindsets.
And I felt like the only escape
would have been to kill myself.
And then shortly after,
my grandma passed.
And I started getting
like visitations from her.
And in the Mormon community,
and I think as well
as other religious
communities, if you
have a visitation from a
grandma, it's not so weird.
My grandma passed, and I
felt like she was around me.
It wasn't like an odd thing.
>> OK.
>> And so that really helped me
learn to communicate with her.
And then I started having
other beings come to me.
And then it was ET beings.
And that's when things, I think,
got kind of weird for people.
Like, oh, we're having
other-dimensional
communication.
>> So at the time were
you still hardcore Mormon?
>> I was transitioning
out by that point, yeah.
>> And members of your community
accepted the grandmother
visitations?
>> Yeah.
Yeah.
>> But then going beyond that,
is that when things got weird?
>> That's when I wasn't sure
how much I should give out
to people.
Like, when their passed
grandmothers were coming to me,
or even if their
mother had passed
and they were
giving me messages,
I felt like it was too
much for me to say,
hey, I can hear your
grandma as well.
This is what she's saying.
But if I get the message
from my own grandma,
it wasn't so weird.
>> I see.
So people-- because I guess
some may feel a little intrusive
then if they were
given those messages?
>> Yeah.
And maybe they feel like,
well that's my grandma.
She should be
communicating with me only.
>> Oh, I see.
>> And then that's the funny
thing that I learned with being
a channeler and a medium,
is when you open yourself up
to, any spirit can communicate
with you and give messages
of healing, if they feel
like you're going to listen.
And other people close
themselves off to it sometimes.
>> Well, don't you have
to get permission from--
or you get permission
from their family members,
from the other side?
How does that work?
>> The other side really
doesn't care too much.
>> They're just like, hey,
someone here can understand me.
Let me communicate
to you, for example,
to convey that message.
>> Yeah.
>> And I guess
when other people--
I was going to ask, is when
some of the information coming
through is spot on or
accurate, does that sort of
freak them out a little bit?
>> Yeah, that's when they're
they come up with the logical
excuses.
Well, you probably know
that because of this,
or things like that.
I think it does make them a
little like, how would she
know that?
That's nerve wracking.
So my logical mind will step
in and try to make sense of it.
>> Right, right.
Yeah, I've done that
a long time ago.
That was-- part of
the series was getting
to see-- proving for myself
whether all of this other side
stuff is real or not, or
if it's just, you know,
are all these people just
going on the internet
and finding things out about
me, and then conveying it?
But then I'm like, no.
That's not what's happening.
>> You're like, I don't know.
Yeah, I think that's why
spirit just doesn't care,
is because they
connect to the heart.
And they know that even if
the logical mind steps in,
that heart space can eventually
come through and be like,
you know what?
I feel like this is real.
>> So you start
channeling ETs,
or thought communication, I guess.
What was your
first communication
from the ET realm, or that?
>> So I would set a daily
practice of meditation aside.
And that's when I started
channeling other beings
and things like that.
Or I guess spirit beings
that I knew as people.
And then that's when
I started getting
visuals of other beings.
I had a Reptilian that
came that I didn't even
know anything about Reptilians
or anything at that point.
And it kind of was
like, that was weird.
Did my imagination create
a giant lizard guy?
I don't know, it
was just a weird--
and then I just saw
things that I didn't think
that I could create in my mind.
Like the Lyran beings--
cats and things.
And I decided to look
it up on the internet,
and there were other people that
had had similar experiences,
or had visions of the
same type of being.
So I'm like, maybe
this is a real contact.
And that's when I opened myself
up more, and I got more of it.
>> So the first being
was a Reptilian.
What did he say?
>> Well, he had-- it was
interesting because he had this
cape on.
And it looked like he could
have put a hood kind of thing.
And so I was meditating,
and he came through.
And I was kind of like, whoa.
And then he faded away,
and then a Gray came in.
So I don't know if he
shapeshifted to make it
more something that I felt--
>> Like, "I'm an
alien" kind of thing?
>> Yeah, I'm just an alien.
Yeah.
But he's told me that he's
my guide and protector.
And so he's kind of
always been there.
But initially it was
a weird thing for me.
And then I got--
>> Does he have a name?
>> Does have a name?
>> Yeah.
>> As far as I can
hear, he calls himself--
he says "Balthazar,"
is how he says it.
>> Do you know what
realm of Reptilians?
Because there's so many.
>> Well, he says he's
with the Alpha Draconis.
But he often works
with the Council
of Beings, which can be Pleiade
or from all over, basically,
to help humanity.
>> OK.
So for those who
are watching, there
are Alpha Draconians
that are actually helping,
as opposed to being all--
because a common
misconception, I
guess, would be that all
the Reptilians are bad.
A lot of people who
subscribe to this information
are like, oh,
Reptilian, stay back.
>> Yeah.
And with that, I'll Alpha
Draconis is mainly just a star
system.
So it's like
Pleiades star system.
And you're going to
have benevolent beings,
and you're going to have
those that are in favor
of humanity's evolution.
And that's the same
with the Draconis.
They have a lot
of evolved beings
that are in service
of humanity now,
even though maybe at one
point they hadn't been.
And there are still those
break-offs in that star system
that are heavily domineering.
And then there's
also the species
that stay within Earth that
are lower realms of Reptilian
that I would say are
more of the dangerous
because they're not evolved.
And they wish to stay
in Fourth Density.
>> So all this information
that you just described,
this is all just coming through
these different interactions
with these different beings?
>> Yeah, or just through
channelings that I've done
for individuals and,
I guess, more public.
>> Yeah.
Well, when I first
discovered your work,
I was blown away
on how correlating
it was with all the other
stuff I've been doing,
interviewing others.
And you haven't been doing
this that long, right?
It's only been this
past year or two?
>> Maybe a year and a half.
>> A year and a half.
>> Maybe, yeah.
>> Wow.
And I was blown away by
the in-depthness of some
of the channelings and
the information coming
through that, again,
just correlates
with everything I've been
studying for the past 10 years.
>> Good, I'm glad
I'm not way off.
>> No, no.
You're right on track,
which is why I'm here,
and we're doing this.
So after the
Reptilian encounter,
shapeshifting into a Gray,
what other sort of beings
came through?
>> There was a Gray and a Mantis
that came through after I was
resisting a while on
my path and things.
And I don't know if the Gray
was the Reptilian in disguise.
I don't know.
There was a lot of language that
sounded like ancient Egyptian,
and spoke of like
choosing me to be
the channeler for information,
and things like that.
And so that's when
I basically started
taking things more seriously.
And there was another very vivid
contact where I was actually
on the couch here.
I had fallen asleep one night.
And a Draconis being came.
And he looked like a giant bat.
It was so intense.
He had the wings.
It was dark.
And I had-- it felt like
a lower dimensional being
standing to the side of me.
I couldn't get a glimpse
of what it looked like.
But it was cursing me out.
And the Draconis
was like, basically,
surrender to your path.
Let go of the old ideas,
because at the time
I was having a hard
time transitioning.
But he did it in such a--
I don't want to say
dark way, because it
benefited me to understand
that I need to get serious.
But it was dark energy.
It was just a very intense--
I mean, he was basically like--
the way he stood, his
presence, everything
was just very interesting.
>> This was the bat being?
The bat?
>> Yeah.
>> But you said there was
another lower being at the same
time that was yelling at you?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> And he was yelling
at you as well?
>> No.
The bat being--
I actually woke up
and was like, why
is there a bat man in my room?
Because it felt so-- or not
in my room, but next to me,
because it felt so
much like a bat man.
>> Right.
>> But then the lower
dimensional being was the one
that's cursing me out.
The other one--
>> So the other
one was just there.
>> He was there, and he
basically communicated
in a very dignified way.
But it was a very powerful way.
Like, to the point where
you'd want to listen.
But everything just
felt very intense.
>> Have you made
sense of that since?
Why the two beings--
two different beings,
and at the same time.
One is doing the-- you know.
>> Basically, from
what I understand--
I don't know if this is 100%.
But because my vibration had
to rise so much to communicate
to this other Draconis being--
because I could almost see him.
There was no third
dimension, where I was at.
I had to slip through
the fourth dimension.
And so I was able to interact
with fourth-dimensional beings
that were trying to, I guess,
take me down or communicate
negative emotions to me,
things like that.
>> So when you open
yourself up as a channel,
then it can be
negative, positive?
Everybody's trying to
get to you in a way.
>> Yeah.
>> To communicate
through, or to--
what do you think
the purposes are?
>> I don't think they like when
there's light being brought
into the soul.
I feel like there's
a lot of emotions
that they can gain when
things stay in low dimensions.
Low density.
And during the time when
I was starting channeling,
I didn't know how to block
myself, or how to set the tone,
I guess.
My intention.
And I got a lot of low
dimensions coming in.
And I just don't
think they like it.
I don't think they like
you shedding light and love
to people and letting
them know their power.
>> And I guess if you are
going to, and they can see you
as being a conduit, then, well,
maybe they can use that energy.
Or use you as the conduit
for their energy instead.
>> Yeah.
>> So having both
channelings of--
I try to guide more to the
positive, and empowering
messages.
But I guess in
the same sense you
can have people
channeling the bad stuff.
Negative energy and
disempowering information.
>> Well, and it's kind of like
where our world is at today.
There's a lot of powerful people
that know ancient knowledge.
They know about those things.
And instead of using it for
good, they've used it for evil.
So it's like if I
can tap into that,
can they get me to use
it for evil purposes
or whatever the case is, like
they've always been able to do?
Or can we transmute
that and use it
for collective of
humanity's evolution?
>> Right, right.
When did you go public
with all of this?
When did you decide
to share this gift?
>> Share the gift!
So I woke up one morning, and
I had this burning sensation--
yearning or whatever-- to
channel Princess Diana publicly
and post it on YouTube.
And it was just something
that I just knew I had to do.
>> Was she already
coming through?
>> She had been coming through.
Not quite like I
did on the video.
That was pretty
long and intense.
So.
>> I don't think I saw that one.
Can you just give
us a little sneak?
>> It was very emotional.
It was the first time
I ever really did
a long period of channeling.
And she basically got
into some deep issues.
And yeah, that's basically
how I started on the YouTube
and decided whoever
comes, I will
channel you and make it public.
And that's kind of how it went.
>> And what was the reaction
when you put that up?
How did people respond?
>> Actually, fairly well.
People really enjoyed it.
>> And then that propelled
you to keep doing this?
>> Yeah.
And then I started
getting more and more
people's deceased loved
ones coming to me.
And that's when I decided to do
private channelings on my own.
And so it just kind of
took off from there.
>> OK.
Being in Salt Lake and
in this energy, what's--
because you mentioned
earlier people
were OK with the
grandmother stuff.
But beyond your
personal grandmother,
when you started going to other
grandmothers or other spirits,
have you gotten much of a
blowback from the community?
>> So I am not very verbal
with all of that now.
I just feel like if
people are ready,
Spirit will help them find
me through the internet
or whatever that way.
I've just had too many
just put up walls,
and they just don't know
how to deal with it.
I do find that women that
have their children out
of the house, and they're
trying to rediscover themselves,
they are starting
to dabble with this,
even if they are in
the Mormon church.
So a lot of my clients that
I have had from Salt Lake
are older women.
>> When you say children
out of the house, like,
grown up and out?
>> Yeah.
>> Is that what you mean?
And they kind of are just like,
I've gone to church for years.
Had the same lessons
over and over.
What else is there?
The kids are out of the house.
So they'll start to
explore these things,
and they're more open to it.
And it's the ones that are
having their little kids,
their kids that they're trying
to get into church zone.
And there's still
a little bit unsure
what to bring into their family
life, and even themselves.
>> Right, right.
And probably being conditioned
since birth, right?
So they're probably
still a little
scared to go outside
of what they know.
>> Yeah.
>> So, well, hopefully
that'll be changing.
It seems like it is.
>> Yes, I'm really hoping.
>> I've done a little research
on the Mormon religion.
But for those who
aren't too familiar,
I'm guessing it's a pretty
rigid set of rules in it's belief
system?
>> Yeah.
I mean, it's not
just a religion.
It's like you change your
whole life and culture,
almost like Islamic.
You change everything about
how you live, your interactions
with people--
>> In what ways
could you go into?
>> Well, so you don't drink.
There are a lot of
regulations with--
I guess just how
you live your life.
>> Well, not drinking, that
could be a positive thing.
>> It is a positive thing,
yeah, because it can--
it's fun.
It's really fun to drink
every once in a while.
But it can bring your
vibration to a low state.
And you can't
think very clearly.
So there's something to that.
>> I was recently in
Kuwait, and it's illegal--
alcohol is illegal there.
>> Oh, really?
>> Yeah, they don't
have it at all.
So I thought, oh, that's
actually good to know.
There's nothing wrong with that.
>> Yeah.
The thing is, though, I
think with kids being told,
like, we don't do that.
It's a rule.
Then they get more
intrigued, and then they
take it to a whole other level.
>> Yeah.
Overcompensation
because of the--
>> Yeah.
>> --suppression.
>> I think sexual--
one thing when you
said suppression,
I think the sexual side of
how we are in our culture
is also another lifestyle
that is unhealthy.
And just the way that we live.
>> And is that--
because I know the multiple
wives thing, that's sort of--
how does that work?
>> So that is a break-off
from the Mormon church.
So we were--
I say we because I've been
a part of it for so long.
But I don't go to
the church anymore.
But the Mormon church
was polygamist.
The government was
getting at them.
And so they said, OK, we're not.
But another side said,
well, we still want to be.
So they broke off,
and they still do.
And they call the FLDS,
or a fundamentalist.
>> OK, so there's different
divisions within the Mormon--
>> Yeah.
>> See, I didn't even know that.
OK.
>> Yeah.
>> And so overall, basically,
the polygamy is not so much?
>> No, not in the main
Mormon church, no.
>> Because I've seen
some TV shows of--
>> Oh, like--
>> Where they go
into the lives of--
>> "Sister Wives" and-- yeah.
>> Yeah, and just glimpses.
And I'm like, oh,
that's interesting.
>> Well, they believe pretty
much a lot of the same stuff.
It's just the polygamy
that's been altered
that we have taken out
because we were getting
so much from the government.
>> I see.
>> So getting back
to the ET stuff,
you mentioned channeling a
Zeta and-- was it channeling,
or connecting with
a Zeta and a Mantis?
>> Well, I guess it would
be more of like a contact
experience.
They came to me and
just talked to me.
And my vibration had to be
raised so much that I didn't
feel like I could even move.
I was basically thrown down--
not thrown down by them.
But my energy felt
so transitioned
that I laid down on the couch.
And then they came over me.
And it just took a while for
me to even gain my energy back.
>> Because I've been exploring
my own personal connections
with both Zeta and Mantis,
could I ask what it felt like?
What did you--
>> I felt like I was
in a dizzy tunnel.
>> Were they coming
at the same time?
>> They came at the
same time, together.
They came together, and kind of
came toward me and spoke to me.
I felt like the Mantis was
doing something with my energy
to raise it enough where
I would understand, almost
like they were speaking
directly to me, like we are.
But obviously there
were no words.
>> The Gray was?
>> Yeah.
The Gray was speaking, and I
could understand it, almost
like you and I were talking.
>> So the Mantis was
more of a facilitator.
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> Just sort of being there.
>> It felt like it was doing
something with my energy
to raise it to a certain degree
where I could understand that.
>> And what did they say?
>> It was--
>> Or what did the Zeta say?
>> OK, so it said, basically,
you need to do your path.
You've been chosen for this.
And then they said all
this stuff in, like,
Egyptian that I--
I think they thought that maybe
it would click or something.
But I just didn't--
>> Well, what did it feel like?
>> It felt like ancient
information that you need
to reintroduce back into
the human consciousness.
>> Do you have an
idea of what that is?
>> Yeah.
So since then, I've done
meditations and clarified it,
and it always goes back
to the Egyptian times.
>> Which is-- what are
those messages, generally?
>> So there's a lot.
[CHUCKLES]
>> Just the short version.
>> I think the biggest thing for
that time period was there were
beings on the planet.
>> Already interacting
with humanity.
>> Yeah.
And when I go back
into my meditations,
they show me that there
are extraterrestrials
all over the place that are in
control of different paradigms
of the social structures.
And somewhere along the lines,
most particularly probably
the Roman times when
the Romans took over,
they transitioned it to be more
of a three-dimensional world.
And they sort of faded
in the background--
with control still, but we
are not able to see them.
And because of that, we
have become unconscious.
And so that's where all the
transitions have happened.
And so they just basically
want to reintroduce the idea
that they've always been here.
But the fact that--
they kind of say that
the cycles of the planet
have taken us into
a lower dimension,
and other beings took
advantage of that.
And so we stayed in three
dimension for a while.
>> Right.
Are you familiar with
the density terms?
Density levels
correlating with chakras?
>> Yeah.
So isn't it the
lower is your third,
and then it goes up higher
to the higher dimension?
>> Or density dimensions-- this
is sort of creating a thesaurus
of words to describe
these experiences.
And I like to use
the dimensional--
when I use the
term "dimensions,"
I correlate it with
actual scientific--
how the scientific community
says we're actually
in the fourth dimension with
X,Y, Z, or up, down, left,
right, and spacetime being the
fourth dimension for measuring
dimensional space and time.
And then fifth dimensional
concepts and ideas
would be getting out
of the linear concept.
So from A to B, no longer
going in that linear sense,
but jumping around
the spacetime.
And that gives a
fifth-dimensional perspective
on our reality.
Where I've noticed with some
of the other interviews,
and Lyssa Royal and others
used the term
"densities" to describe
the actual consciousness.
And we're sort of--
they say we're moving from
third to fourth density.
And I notice these terms kind
of get confusing sometimes,
as people say 3D, 4D.
So would you say more
of the third density,
the heaviness of the energy?
>> Yeah.
>> And then we're moving
into fourth density?
>> Yeah.
So what I understand
with that is we
were a fourth density or a fifth
dimensional-type being before.
And then I guess it was the way
that the cycles of the Earth
rotated, or however
it worked, beings
knew this, and came down,
and used these paradigms
to take and control
our fear and structure.
And we went down into density.
And some of us have
stayed here for a while.
And now that the earth has
done its cycle rotation,
we're able to come out of it.
>> Right.
>> Does that seem like it--
>> Matches right
with everything, yes.
Totally.
So the planet itself is it's
own higher dimensional density
being.
And we as densities-- beings--
on it have to evolve with her.
>> Yeah, yeah.
That's the perfect way,
because people get upset.
Like, how could the
beings come and do that
to our consciousness?
But it's like, we're
all doing this together.
And in a sense, in almost every
single one of my channelings,
it was basically
humanity's choice.
We let the fear overcome us.
We let that maintain
our consciousness.
And we just didn't
break out of it in time,
I guess, for
everything to evolve.
And we stayed with
it for a while.
>> Yeah, I was hoping later
today, in the channeling,
we can get into some of the
history a little bit more.
Fall of Atlantis, and these
cycles, and stuff like that.
And the human evolution.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> I think that was going
to be the main focus.
>> That's good.
>> Sounds like you've gotten
a lot of information on other
beings.
>> I think that's the
biggest scope of my path
as a channeler, because it can--
each channeler has their
things that they focus on.
And I feel like right now that's
what they want me to focus on,
because this is what
was needed, I guess,
for this evolution process.
>> Yeah.
And we can always
learn from our past.
Even though we're recreating
it in the moment now.
>> I know, I know.
>> Awesome.
So you've connected with
all these different beings.
Do you have one being that
you normally connect with?
Or is it just always random?
>> A lot of times it is
like the Council of Light,
if it's to do with healing.
If there's something
to do with healing.
It's just depending on the
question and things like that.
If it's something with origins.
>> And they call themselves--
is it a collective,
the Council of Light?
>> Yeah.
But they'll visually
show me who's
stepping forward, usually.
>> OK.
So within the council,
one person of the council
will step forward and say,
OK, on behalf of the council?
>> Yeah.
>> OK, cool.
>> Especially if that individual,
if they know that individual has
a specific question about
healing, with whatever reason,
they know how to answer that
question.
Maybe more than somebody
else or whatever.
>> Interesting.
>> But I do feel like, as far
as the origins in humanity,
it is more like ET and the
Draconis that I connect with.
Reptilian type stuff.
>> OK.
When you say the ET, so the
Draconis part of the ET stuff?
>> Yeah, but also just other ET
beings that maybe are not fully
part of the council with healing.
They just know about humanity,
and how things have fit in.
Such as Lyran beings
or things like that.
They have a lot of wisdom that
came with this time period,
and so they'll help
with that kind of thing,
if you're gaining knowledge.
>> Very cool.
Do you have a favorite?
>> Well, I like doing
the Reptilians and--
>> Yeah?
>> Yeah, their energy
is just so direct.
And I like that.
I don't like the
fluff of everything.
Let's just get to the reason
why we're here, and let's do it.
And that's how they are.
>> Nice, nice.
Very cool.
Do you think maybe later we
can talk to some Reptilians?
Let's see if they come through.
>> Yeah.
>> That'd be cool.
Yeah, my process over
this, doing this series,
has been learning and
categorizing, and learning
about these different energies.
And the Reptilians-- we had
one super happy-go-lucky TReb
come through Rob
Gauthier, a Reptilian.
But other than that,
I really haven't
tapped into too many other--
personally, I've sort of seeked
out and seen and connected
with.
But I think that would
be nice, to introduce--
>> So have you seen any?
Like, in your meditations?
>> Reptilians?
>> Mm-hmm.
>> No, actually.
Well, I-- kind of.
But not in a
communicative sense,
where they're creating
a rapport of question
answers kind of thing.
Just images and feelings.
>> They just kind of flew
by your line of vision.
>> Yeah, sort of Reptilians.
And I sort of got one one
time during a meditation.
I saw this really nasty, dark--
claws and teeth and snouts
and all that stuff coming in.
And then for a second,
for a split second,
I was really afraid.
But then immediately I was like,
well, no, that's super cool.
Look at how cool that
is, looking at it
from the little
boy's perspective.
Like a "Jurassic Park"
or something like--
kids love dinosaurs, and
playing with that stuff.
It's a cool factor.
And as soon as I did
that, it shifted,
and it turned into a cartoon.
>> Oh, really?
>> And it was kind
of like Shrek.
>> Oh.
>> You know how he tries to
be the mean giant in front
of everybody, but he's
just a cuddly Shrek guy.
>> That's funny.
>> That was the analogy.
I was like, it's just
about your perspective
and how you look
at these things.
Which creates them, right?
So in reality, it was just a
lovable cartoon puffy dragon
thing.
>> That is what
I've heard that
you can transmute
what you're seeing into
something more lovable
or in the light kind of thing.
>> Yeah.
So that was-- and I think
that was the lesson,
that it was coming
through and saying, hey,
we're not all scary, nasty--
we can be cool.
It's just you guys are
so used to perception.
You're so trained, oh,
this is bad, this is good.
So if you let go of
all that, there's
actually something
really cool to be seen.
And even lovable and happy and
good with the Reptilian stuff.
But conditioning-- even
in the New Age community,
the conditioning of Reptilians
has not been the greatest.
They've sort of had,
you know, stay away
from the Reptilians, or the
evil Reptilian government,
the Illuminati, and all that.
Of course, that
faction and those--
they do exist.
But for us to--
I think it's time for us to
embrace all of that side of us.
Because we all have
Reptilian in us.
>> Yeah.
Well, as far as I know, there
are the ancient Reptilians.
And then, like I
said, there's more
the lower dimensional that just
want to be in fourth density.
And they don't want
to evolve right now.
And those are the ones
that are kind of like, OK.
But the other ones,
they're very wise,
and they have a lot
of intelligence.
>> That dragon's been
around a long time.
>> Yes, he has.
>> And there's a reason.
It's funny.
I actually had-- and I was
in an ayahuasca journey.
And this was right--
literally days after
the election of Trump.
And I saw Trump as this wise
dragon, flying around the room.
And it was something-- because
there's so much fear around
that.
And there was other people
in the ceremony that
thought we were all going to
be put in concentration camps
and taken away.
I saw the energy of
what Trump is here.
I'm not-- whoever's
watching this,
I'm not a big Trump supporter.
I'm not saying that's--
>> It was just maybe
what you needed to see.
>> It's just what I
need to see to say, hey,
let's not be afraid of this.
Don't be afraid of the energy.
Instead, maybe there is
some wisdom behind it.
Not saying that he's conscious
of any kind of wisdom.
But there should be--
whatever energy is coming
through there for the planet
and for the lessons that we
need to learn at this time,
it could be this ancient
Reptilian wise energy
to help move us
through our evolution.
It's all here to serve.
Otherwise it wouldn't
be happening.
>> Yeah.
I like that.
>> Well, actually,
I wanted to ask you.
So your process, I've noticed,
online, from the videos
I've seen.
It's sort of a
little bit different
than your traditional channeler.
It's almost like you're
translating in real time.
And sometimes I've seen you
go full talking as the being.
>> Yeah.
>> I think most people who are
familiar with this show are
used to people sort of embracing
the energy of that being.
And I'm sort of having a
conversation with that being.
How does it work for you?
>> So initially I did let
myself completely go into more
of a deeper trance, and I took
on the energy of the being.
I have trained myself to
hold back a little bit
to be a little bit more present
and use my own personality
in communicating.
>> OK.
>> Just because I feel like
there are some information
in advance--
not advance, but there's
a lot of information
that people are
just still trying
to get a grip on that I feel
like I need to explain it
in my own terms, versus using
the personality of the being.
But it just depends
on what is needed.
And the deep trance--
I definitely initially got
into a deeper trance.
>> So when you go
into deeper trance,
are you still able to
hear the information?
>> Yeah, I'm just not able
to communicate with you
as clearly.
I'm just totally replaced.
>> But the information that's
coming through is clear
information?
>> Yeah.
So that would be good for--
like right now, you and I--
or even maybe doing something
over interview on YouTube.
But as far as personal
channeling, it's easier for me
to stay more present.
And that's why I've trained
myself to kind of like....
>> So you can be present
to ask the questions.
>> Yeah.
>> OK.
Otherwise you don't know
what's coming through.
>> Yeah.
>> So when you're by
yourself, it's more of that--
I'm having a conversation
with this being.
>> Yeah.
>> But in this case, would
you just go full trance then?
>> I think full trance
would probably--
maybe even a little bit
more toward my personality.
But more into trance than a
private channeling session.
>> I see.
>> Because sometimes the
client will stop you and ask
questions.
And then you have to
come back out of it,
and then you have
to go back in it.
So it's better just to
keep a middle ground.
>> I see.
Interesting.
I noticed one channeling
where you were bringing in--
I think it was a
Reptilian energy.
Or no, it was--
was it a Reptilian?
One of these ancient
bearded guys.
>> Ancient bearded guys?
>> And he was one of these
bigger tall beings that lived
on Earth.
>> Oh, the red-haired giant.
>> The red-haired giants.
>> Yeah, that was a weird--
>> Yeah.
You were saying just physically
how it felt. And you're like,
this is just weird.
>> It was weird.
>> So was it just weird because
it wasn't like anything else
that you've against?
>> Yeah.
That's exactly-- it wasn't
like anything I had felt.
It was like I was
talking to somebody
that looked like a human,
but it felt like an animal.
>> Oh, OK.
Right, right.
>> Yeah.
>> Animalistic energy.
>> Yes.
>> Yeah, and I remember watching
that and sort of feeling that
as well.
Any other strange,
weird energies
that you want to mention?
>> I will mention channeling
Brigham Young is quite
interesting.
>> And he was the one
who found the skeletons?
No.
>> He was the one that
took the Mormons--
>> Oh.
>> --from the region in
Illinois over to establish what
the church is today.
So built up pretty much
all of Salt Lake City.
>> Wow.
So you channeled that--
you channeled him?
>> He actually came to me.
And it was very intense.
And it's interesting
because Utah
is named after a raptor,
which is a Reptilian.
And he's got a lot of
Reptilian-type energy.
And he has just a lot--
I don't know.
It was just a very
weird energy, I
felt like, when he came to me.
>> In that interview?
That energy on your website?
>> So when I was
like, all right,
let's make a YouTube
of the channeling,
he actually switched and made it
a little bit more light-hearted
and loving.
Because I felt like--
maybe he did that
because the collective
wasn't ready to hear what
he was actually telling me.
>> Oh, OK.
>> Because there is a lot
of reasons why religion was
brought here in the first place.
And some of them aren't
so good, because it
can capture our consciousness.
And he was part of that.
>> He was part of the--
bringing it here, right?
>> He was part of making
it into what it is today.
Sort of capturing
that consciousness
to keep it into a childlike
state, versus expanding.
>> Can you go into depth
a little about that?
>> So basically, what I
understand is Joseph Smith was
here to bring in
information from the past,
and to help others
understand where we were.
Then created a
religion because of it.
Brigham Young actually,
after Joseph had passed over,
took all of the saints
over to this region
and established the church.
And I guess used that
information against the people.
So it was good initially,
but it was transformed--
>> As all religions.
>> Yeah.
And he really does--
Brigham Young really does
have a very dark energy.
I feel like there
was a lot going
on at that time that really--
yeah.
>> Well, how long ago was
this, when he came through?
>> I don't know,
maybe a year ago?
Maybe?
Yeah.
>> Because I could see that
definitely would be some
blowback.
You could definitely get a
blowback from the community.
>> Yeah.
They were kind of
like, that's not safe
for you to do that right now.
>> To put that out.
>> But individually, if they
come to you and ask questions
in a private channel,
we can do that.
>> Again--
collectively, though--
we all choose to
have this experience.
So he's just a facilitator
for that collective desire--
>> Yeah.
>> --to experience this
religious constraints,
or disempowerment,
or whatever it is.
So again, another perspective.
Not to look at him
as this bad guy, or--
>> That's really good.
I love that.
Especially because,
at the time, Joseph
channeled a lot of information
that was beneficial.
And then people-- he
built this church,
and people were coming to him.
Oh, should I plant this
type of seed in my yard?
Should I do this?
And then all of a sudden
you're giving your power away
to somebody else, when you're
able to tap into that yourself.
And obviously, like we
said, you could use that
for good or evil.
And the leadership
was taken to use--
come to me for all
of your problems,
and I'll make it right.
>> Right.
>> And they allowed it.
The people allowed it.
>> Yeah.
So you get what you ask for.
>> [LAUGHS] Yeah.
>> Interesting.
Well, cool.
Well, I do look
forward to seeing
what other energies come through
later today and the future
of your work.
So, definitely.
>> Thanks.
Thank you.
>> Thank you.