[MEDITATIVE MUSIC]
>> There are many paths to
figuring out the true nature
of our reality.
The path of my
journey has taken me
to Sedona, Arizona
several times.
And every time I leave, I find
myself making plans to return.
It was one of the
first discoveries
I made during my research
into the ET subject matter.
Sure, it was a hard
one to swallow.
I remember going to
an ET meetup group
at the Flying Saucer
Cafe in Santa Monica.
Some of the experts
there said that they
had spoken to several
abductees who claimed to have
seen these children on ships.
They said they
were teaching them
how to do mundane daily tasks,
like go grocery shopping
and wash dishes.
Well, at the time, I
thought it was ridiculous.
But several years
into my research,
now I know it to be
more true than not.
In fact, all of the
extra dimensional beings
I've interviewed so
far have all confirmed
the programs and the
existence of hybrid children.
Today, I'm meeting with Bridget
Nielsen, a beautiful young lady
who says she can
communicate directly
with these hybrid children.
She claims that she
can even show me
how to connect to my children.
Though I have no
conscious memory
of being on board any
ships and having my essence
or sperm taken, I'm going
to follow along and see
where this all takes me.
[MEDITATIVE MUSIC]
Ever wonder if there's intelligent
life elsewhere in the universe?
Well, I have....I've been wondering since I was a kid.
My name is Reuben Langdon.
And on March 29th, 2007, in the middle of the day,
I saw a number of strange objects in the sky.
Coincidentally, I was working on
the film Avatar at the time, playing an alien.
And ever since then I've been on a quest...
A quest to find out if aliens truly do exist and if so...
...are they here with us?
If beings of higher intelligence are here...
...what is their purpose?
Why don't they make themselves more known?
Why the secrecy?
I've asked these questions to many experts,
yet, each seems to have a different theory.
So I thought to myself,
why not ask the aliens directly?
So that's what I set out to do!
Well, sort of...
Today's main topic,
the alien hybrids.
>> Woo.
[LAUGHS]
>> Wild and crazy stuff...
So tell us your story.
Tell us how you got involved
in the alien hybridization
program.
>> Yeah, it's the least expected
career path I would have ever
thought, I guess.
>> Career path?
>> Well, it kind of
is a career path.
It's like, well, it's my
passion path, I guess more so.
So it's not what I
would have expected.
And it started
with doing a bunch
of healing, different
trainings that I was doing--
like I told you earlier--
doing different past
life stuff, Earthbound
spirits, mediumship, of
those kind of things--
angels, guides.
And a part of that
was abduction.
And I thought, I was cool with
all the other inter-dimensional
stuff, but not abduction.
>> And this is helping other
people with their past lives.
>> Yeah.
So I would channel that through.
So I would, like, connect
with their other lives
and bring that through, or
connect with their guides
and communicate from them--
those kinds of things.
>> Before we jump ahead,
can you just tell me,
how did you stumble upon
that work in itself?
Because that realm, it's
not common for people to--
it's becoming more
common, I guess.
But what led you into that path?
>> One, being in Los Angeles.
So that opens up that door.
Two-- you know, it was right
after I got out of college.
And then I went immediately
into, like, advertising,
big time corporate advertising.
And just like really dove
into the corporate world.
And then after that experience,
as well as, like, boyfriends
and my own stuff, I just went so deep
into something energetically
that I wasn't, that
I just catapulted
to another extreme of I'm
going, I need to, like,
look at what I really
am passionate about,
and look at what my gifts are.
And, like, fix my
own personal stuff.
Like, why am I experiencing
certain things?
>> And when you say
deep in something you
weren't, that's the
corporate world?
>> The corporate world
and stuff like that.
>> So you were doing
the 9:00 to 5:00--
>> Yeah, 24 hour iPhone as
the pillow kind of thing.
>> And then that felt not right,
so then that's the catapult
you're talking about.
So you went the other direction,
the opposite of 9:00 to 5:00--
the opposite of corporate.
OK, gotcha.
>> And even as a kid, I just
was very attuned to, like
I loved fairies.
I loved nature.
I can sense certain things.
I could definitely feel a
lot more going on with people
than they knew themselves.
And I had those
extra sensitivities.
And then over the years and
years and years of schooling,
they started to dwindle,
and dwindle, go away.
And then once I hit the
extreme of then going corporate
after all the schooling,
it was just so far,
that I knew exactly where to go.
I was like, let's
go back to nature.
Let's go back to
my natural self.
And at that time,
too, my dad was
heavy into the metaphysical
community in LA.
So he was going to
Bashar channelings.
And he was doing
channeling-like stuff himself.
And then he was connected
with a shaman in Los Angeles,
and we were doing
family constellation
work, which heals family
traumas that are passed down.
And so he was in that.
And I was dabbling
and I knew about it.
But once I had gone
to such an extreme,
I went, OK, well I need to
look more at like who I am,
and where is this originating
from like, in my lineage?
Why am I creating
certain challenge like
in relationships?
What is the source of
my motivations in life?
And so I started
working with a shaman.
And I worked with
another clairvoyant too.
And I just started learning
all that they were doing.
And then I could see that I
had these sensitivities too.
Once I could see them
doing all of that stuff,
I went, oh I can do that too.
But it was so natural, that
I didn't know I was doing it.
>> Got you.
>> So then I went hmm,
well, let's dive into that.
And so then I did
different healing trainings.
And at that time, I
didn't believe fully--
I didn't have the visceral
experience of other lives,
like other simultaneous
incarnations.
I didn't really believe
in Earthbound spirits.
It wasn't, like
intellectually,
it wasn't matched
with my experience.
So that was one of
the primary reasons
that I went to do
the training, was
to see if it
actually hit to have
an experience with
these different segments
that people just flippantly,
like, throw around.
Like, 'Oh, my past life.'
And I'm going, no,
how does that relate
to this here and now?
And how do you know?
Like, where's the
knowingness behind that?
So I wanted to know
that for myself
before I just went
around just saying stuff.
>> Right.
>> And so then at that training,
I experienced crazy things that
were--
I mean, even backed
up by like Google--
certain things I was channeling
of different, like, spirits and
crazy things that were just--
>> When you say
backed up by Google,
what do you mean by that?
You would Google it later after
you've had the experience?
>> Yeah, after I had the
experience, it was like,
what I had brought through was
actually backed up by like,
historically in Google, like
different things that had happened.
>> Can you describe how?
You got us going
here, for example?
>> For example, we were staying
in a retreat center in
San Diego.
And it, itself, had kind
of interesting energies.
And that day, out of
the two week thing,
we had worked with
Earthbound spirits
and worked with people
that had passed.
And so that night,
my roommate and I
were both going back and forth.
And she was from England,
so she was telling me
about all the ghosts in
all the castles in England
that she would work
with and stuff.
And so we're just dialoguing.
And the door was open.
And the energy was open.
We were kind of like calling
it in, I guess you could say.
And then I could perceive, I could
feel beings walk into the room.
And it was three little
girls that I perceived.
And at the same time
I felt that, she
looked in the same direction.
And so I knew that
something was going on.
And we both are going oh,
like, something just happened.
>> Right, right.
>> And so then, at that moment,
we were like OK, this is it!
Like, something's going on.
And so I got out my pendulum.
And she's channeling too.
So both of us together
were going back and forth.
And what came
through, through me--
that I could hear from them--
is that there were
three little girls
that had been murdered
on this property
by this religious
group, by this, like--
I guess he was some kind
of bishop or something
that ran a center.
And he murdered them.
And they just were
stuck in this dimension,
because if it's an abrupt ending
or if it's unfinished, then
of course, you
kind of stay bound
to this until it's complete.
Or if you have a drug overdose,
or you get in a car accident,
those kinds of
things lead to where
those beings need
extra assistance
to move into the light.
And so we worked with
these little girls.
>> Your other friend from
England, she was there too?
Simultaneously getting
the same downloads?
>> Yes, same downloads.
>> So you were able to confirm
with her later the same
information?
>> Yes.
>>OK.
>>And then at the same time too,
so we sent them into the light.
We assisted them.
And then, I got on
my phone on Google,
and they gave me the year,
they gave that it was some kind
of religious guy that did it.
We knew the location,
three little girls.
And I Googled it, and
it was like on Google.
Like, three little
girls murdered
by this guy at this location.
And I'm like, oh!
So that was like
my first experience
of getting the
information and then
having it instantly
validated to reinforce.
>> Instantly.
Google.
We can do that now on the phone.
You didn't even wait
till you got home.
You went right on the phone.
>> Right on the phone.
I was like, OK.
Am I crazy?
So it was instantly validated.
>> Nice.
>> Yeah.
>> So that led you
into dabbling into healing others.
You said assisting others
with alien abductions?
>> Yeah.
So that was one baby
sliver of the two weeks.
And I thought it was crazy.
But at the same time, I was
open, because I had to be open.
That was my mission, was
to be open, to understand.
>> Open, meaning transparent,
telling friends and family
and the world?
>> Open in the way of like,
I was open to believing it.
I was open to acknowledging
that that was their experience.
>> OK.
Yeah, after you've had that
experience, how could you not?
>> Yeah.
Yeah.
So I mean, it was a
different segment,
but it all fits
into the same thing.
And a lot of people in
the spiritual community
don't translate over to
extraterrestrials, sometimes.
>> A lot of extraterrestrial
people don't translate
into other realms and things.
Which is, for me, I found
very hard to understand
those people.
Because it's like, if it's one--
I mean, if you're going to
let your brain leak out,
you might as well just let it--
>> Go all the way.
>> --just go full.
Full disclosure, full peanut
butter, go all the way in.
Might as well.
>> I'm with you on
all of that, yeah.
>> Because when you throw
out all scientific logic,
for one thing, why not throw
it out for the other stuff?
>> You've got to be open
to throwing everything out.
And it just spins and spirals.
But the abduction thing
was the last thing
I was going to throw
out. Which you'd think
for a lot of people, it is.
>> So that's meaning the
hardest thing for you to--
>> Acknowledge.
>> --acknowledge that
that's the truth.
>> Yes.
>> So ghost, you've got that.
>> Ghost, past lives, good.
Angels, great.
Fairies, awesome.
Aliens, no.
>> Mermaids?
>> Yes!
>> Yes on mermaids
before alien abductions.
>> Yeah.
>> Wow.
OK, never mind.
That's good.
>> I really like mermaids.
>> I figured you would,
that's why I brought it up.
So then, aliens.
>> So, aliens.
>> Aliens, in essence,
aliens or alien abductions?
Was it the abduction phenomenon?
>> Abduction.
I was fine.
See, yet again, it's
like star family is OK.
Alien abductions isn't.
And it's nice having had my
own belief dot disconnect,
because now I can see where
it is for other people, which
is just programming.
So in another part
of the training,
we had talked about star beings.
It's like, oh, you have other
lives from Sirius and Pleiades.
And I was good with that.
I'm like, that
sounds really cool.
I'm into that.
And then it's like,
alien abduction?
No.
So I definitely
had a disconnect.
But then as I started
doing this and working
with these different clients,
I would have almost all
of them were abductees.
And then I contacted
the different people
that I was trained with--
>> Male and female?
Or was it--
>> Male and female.
Yeah.
And I contacted the other
women I was trained with.
And I said, are you
getting abductees?
And they were like, no.
Like, uh, why am I getting
all the abductees, you know?
I didn't want to.
There was nothing in my, like,
ego or anything that wanted to.
But it was resonance
for some reason.
So you were working with these people.
What did you call
yourself, I guess?
A spiritual healer?
Or did you have a business card?
>> I had a business card.
I was a healer, I guess.
So I was a healer.
I did different shamanic
work, trauma release,
different stuff.
And then, more of the
metaphysical things too.
So it was just like
the full spectrum
of whatever was needed.
>> OK, gotcha.
>> So I was healer.
>> And then you had other, I
guess, coworkers, co-healers,
that were also using the
same modalities to help other
people.
And that was colleagues
that you could consult with.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Got it.
>> Yeah, and none of
them had had this--
>> And none of them
had had an abduction.
>> None of them were
getting abducted.
>> But had they heard of the
abduction phenomenon prior?
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> OK.
And you had heard of
it, too, from movies?
>> Well, that, and it was
part of the healing training.
>> Oh, it was?
>> Yeah, just like
a small segment.
So it was acknowledged.
And there was a checking.
It was kind of like
a checklist of what
could be out of
alignment, or what
could be the origin of
discomfort or trauma.
And right there is, like,
implants, like alien abduction.
And so I'd have to go through it
every time, and every time that
came up.
So I thought, hmm,
it's coming up.
I need to look at this.
And so I did.
>> Yeah.
In what way?
>> In the way that, well,
my dad was simultaneously
in the conspiracy avenue.
And he was like,
there are aliens.
There's evidence.
There's science.
And I'm on this metaphysical,
like, healing side, being like,
there's people saying
they're abducted.
>> The government's
covering it up.
It's a big thing.
Yeah, I've been down that path.
>> Exactly.
But it was good, because
there was the science evidence
aspect, and then
there was me, like,
having the
experiential situations
going on with these clients.
So we were like comparing and
contrasting notes, you know?
He would be like, well I
watched this abduction video
where they were
taking eggs and semen.
And then the person
would be like, yeah,
I saw myself on the table.
And so I had no context.
And it was just what these
people were telling me.
And so it was two worlds
kind of converging
to support this new idea.
>> About how long ago was
this, I guess, in day and age?
>> I guess, this was
about four years ago,
four or five years ago.
>> I see.
>> Yeah.
>> So enough information
is out there,
or had been out
there at that time,
to kind of put the
puzzle pieces together.
And you had different aspects
of the puzzle pieces, I see.
So what happened after that?
How did you help
these people who
claim to have abductions
and implants too?
Did they claim to have implants?
>> Yeah.
>> So how would you
go about helping them?
>> Well, we were told the
greater story of the Zetas.
>> From..?
>> From the woman that was
putting this on, she had that
perspective via Lisa Royal and
different people that she had
studied.
So there was the Zeta--
>> The woman who trained you
in the healing modalities?
>> Yeah.
>> OK.
So you actually got
kind of a certification
from her and stuff?
>> Uh-huh.
>> OK, I see.
>> And so she had this
perspective of going, OK
the Grays were this.
And they didn't have
emotion, so there was this.
And then it caused
trauma in people.
So we kind of had the
objective perspective.
I went at it more from
a trauma perspective,
rather than trying to cope
with the idea of aliens.
It was like, OK
this was a trauma.
And it kind of feels like
maybe a sexual trauma.
So like, how can
we look at that?
And part of it, in any
kind of healing modality,
is just acknowledgment,
just for it to be spoken.
And then that energy
is like released.
And so that was probably
like the biggest first step.
And I wouldn't go into
it too much at that time.
I went into more of the
other avenues that were up,
but just acknowledging it and
going through it in the session
was what I did.
>> And by just bringing that
up and acknowledging it,
did you see a transformation in
the people that you're working
with?
>> Yeah.
>> Would they have memories
that they would recall?
>> Yeah.
>> OK.
What was that like?
>> I mean, it was interesting,
because as you know with
the abductees, it's like, it's
someone's personal experience.
And that is powerful.
>> And a lot of times, our
sexual organs and our body
parts are very personal to us.
So when those areas get
violated, it hits home.
>> Yes.
>> Yeah, absolutely.
>> And so for me, it was just,
like, compassion and going,
whoa.
It just solidified
that reality for them--
because it wasn't my reality--
was real.
And so it just brought that
to a deeper place in me.
>> Yeah.
>> And you worked with enough
people to verify that they
weren't making it up.
>> Yeah.
And that's the thing.
No one wants to make up
that they were abducted.
I don't think that this
is like said enough.
There's no catalyst
of popularity
that is gonna come
from saying that.
>> I agree.
I've spoken to--
I think I mentioned
earlier, I've
spoken to probably
over 100 contactees.
Mix match, some
abductees, experiencers,
contactees, there's
whole subcategories
of that whole batch.
It's very hard.
Even government people
who have high level positions
and have everything
in the world to lose
by saying something like that.
And they're very brave,
I think, the ones
that do come forward
and speak of it.
And they're very reluctant.
A lot of them that
have kept secrets
for 20, 30, 40, 50 years old.
>> So you said until that time,
you hadn't associated it with
a personal experience.
Then what happened?
>> Then, I had to
honor the fear.
Because I was like
OK well, I might not
have personal experience.
But am I fearful
of this idea, of ETs
coming and taking
me out of my bed?
Yeah, sure.
It was a hypothetical
situation, still.
And then I watched
"The Fourth Kind".
And "The Fourth
Kind" changed it all.
>> In a positive, negative way?
>> Surprisingly, a positive way.
Because the show
completely freaked me out.
So you would think that it would
have repelled me even farther
from looking at it.
But I'm strange.
And so then after
watching it, I
knew about the idea
of hybrid children.
And so then I went to my
room and I just asked, like
with my full openness,
like full heart--
I will go down whatever
road this leads me.
Do I have hybrid children?
And well actually before
that, it was through the healing
stuff, it showed that
you could be abducted
in another life that was, like,
kind of simultaneous to now,
as well as this life.
And so I asked first, do I have
hybrid kids from another life?
Still kind of like
pushing it away.
>> Without asking the
question directly.
>> And then I was
just like..
>>Who would you ask?
Is this like a prayer to God?
>> That's a good question.
>> --or the universe?
Because a lot of
people have different
labels for their belief system.
So I'm just curious in how
would you present that.
>> Right.
So by that time for me, I
had a pretty clear attunement
to many streams of
different beings.
So I mean, I'm like, I had a
very clear awareness of what
an angel felt like, or
what a guide felt like,
or what an ancestor felt like,
these different frequencies
of asking.
And within the healing
work that I did,
it was all about creating
a real visceral experience
of your inter-dimensional
support team that you have.
So like everyone
has guardian angels.
Everyone has guides.
>> When you say
inter-dimensional,
that could also be
extra-dimensional?
>> Yes.
>> So just these
otherworldly beings?
>> Otherworldy beings, yeah.
And so I cultivated that really
strong communication conduit
to my own guidance system,
as well as my higher self.
So it would be my guidance
system and my higher self
that I'd be asking.
And probably for
this question, I
was probably asking Source itself.
Like, all right, let's have it.
>> All of you guides,
and the big cheese.
>> Yeah.
Is this the case?
>> And what was your answer?
>> The biggest yes I
have ever received.
Like, it just hit me so hard.
And I just started bawling.
And it opened this
emotional conduit in me
that I don't think I had had
this emotional an experience.
>> And up until this, you hadn't
had any conscious sightings
or lost time or
abduction-type things?
>> Not that I remembered.
The only thing that was sticky
that I could kind of look back
to was when I was,
I kept on having
this really strong feeling
that I was pregnant, a lot.
And I was a virgin.
And so that stuck
with me my whole life,
because I would always
say it to my mom.
And she would say
that I was strange.
And really, like no,
you're not pregnant!
So that stuck.
That was, like, there.
>> So that was always
there, even before you asked
the question?
It was a little kind
of, that was strange.
>> That was strange.
And looking back
on it now, I mean,
a lot of different
memories have come back up.
But another thing that is
strange that I haven't even
put together really, until this
past year, is from about age 8
to age 12, I would create
these really large families
of paper dolls--
like children and parents of
all different shapes and sizes.
And my cousin and I would create
little videos of these families
in these different scenarios.
And just the way that we did
it was not just like playing.
Like, there was some kind
of an intimate relationship.
And there were way too
many kids and certain style
that both of us
were coming from.
It was very odd and interesting.
So I feel like that
was remembrance
and a bringing through of things
I had seen on the ship that
was coming through.
>> So you asked the question.
You got a big knock
on the head, yes.
Immediately, did
memories and visions
start pulling through
of experiences?
Or how did you start to
come to that realization?
What was the
validation, I guess?
If you got a yes,
I'm sure there had
to be some sort of validation.
>> Right.
The validation-- I guess
this is almost an answer
to your question-- but
was I could hear them.
>> Could hear the kids?
>> So the yes was from the kids.
And I could hear them.
And it was a portal.
And it was an energy
stream from certain beings
that I had never
heard from before.
And so the full building of
the spectrum of all the beings
that I was connected
to, validated like
my communication
and my confidence
with these certain beings.
So by the time these kids
started talking, I'm going,
that's a new branch.
Like, this is a new energy.
This is a new thing.
And so that was validating based
on all the other things that
had built up my confidence
in this healing extrasensory
arena.
>> So what happened next?
I mean, after that, you
got the hit in the head.
>> After that?
>> Then you started
hearing these voices.
Did you communicate
back with them?
Did you have conversations?
>> For the next
probably five months,
I had to sleep on it for
five months, pretty much.
I knew that it was true.
But I was not ready to
go forward or do anything
with that.
Like it was just sitting, kind
of like dormant, waiting
to like burst to another level.
So I just kind of
sat with it and let
it digest for that long.
>> I see.
Did you sit on
it with more downloads, or no?
>> No.
No, I just sat with it.
>> Didn't ask any
more questions?
>> I didn't ask.
That was the only
question that needed
to be asked at that moment.
>> Yeah, gotcha.
>> You found out you
have hybrid children.
You're part of this program.
What is the program, if you can...
what's going on?
>> The program.
It's a program designed
to help wake up humanity.
>> OK, the program designed
>> And connect Earth with
its greater other aspects,
its galactic family.
So it's to merge galactic
family with the Earth family,
as well as wake up humanity.
And all those are waking
up humanity, that process.
>> So it's a
multi-level type program.
>> Yes.
There's many reasons to it, yes.
>> And one of them, which--
like I said, is the
first time I even
heard it put it that way,
to help wake up humanity.
And I can totally
see that happening.
But usually, it's perceived
in a negative context.
>> Yes.
It starts with like
the understanding
of maybe a negative context
through the abduction program,
which most people
know about, which
is a connection of
the Zeta Reticuli,
which is a parallel
reality human,
and also is part of our
original DNA strand in us,
which is kind of freaky.
So it's like they're
taking themselves,
because it's themselves
in another dimension,
as well as we have
that genetics in us.
So it's like taking family.
So it's much more
intertwined and at home
than seems to be some like
beings like from another world,
being like, aaaargh.
It's closer to home.
>> Right, but many aspects.
So it's multi-dimensional as far
as them being an aspect of us
having their DNA.
It's not just one thing.
>> Right.
>> Within that program--
>> --within that program,
within all of that stuff--
>> --intergalactic contact.
>> --that's gonna wake us up.
I mean, that's gonna jostle people.
That's gonna like set off every
trigger of the ego perceivable.
>> Well, it has.
I mean, if you talk to any of
the thousands of abductees--
hundreds of thousands,
and estimated millions--
then, it's rocked
some worlds out there.
>> Yeah, definitely
rocked some worlds.
>> Sounds like your world
was rocked a little bit too?
>> Rocked my world.
Changed my world.
And in the program,
which is commonly known,
semen and eggs, genetic material
is taken from these abductees.
And that is meant to create
other beings, meant to create
the five hybrid civilizations--
five different hybrid
civilizations-- as well as
the hybrid children, also
known as the freelancers.
And these particular
kids are the ones
going to be coming to Earth.
So it's five civilizations
that have their own planets,
have evolved on, as well as
these kids coming to Earth.
And all this has taken place in,
give or take, about a 100 year
period of Earth time.
>> Wow.
So, I mean, this is,
hybrids from us, from humans.
So humanity is
responsible for kind
of igniting five other
civilizations on other planets?
>> Yeah.
They each have their own planet.
>> They each have
their own planet.
And so, wow, humans.
>> We're their ancestors.
>> And we don't even know.
>> No.
>> Our DNA is
seeding these others,
which makes you kind of think
how many other civilizations
seeded humanity?
>> Oh, I like that tie-in.
>> And if so, were those races
even aware or conscious that
they were seeding another
civilization at the time?
So that's the big
question you always
see on "Ancient Aliens" or something.
Are we - we're aliens!
You know, where do we come from?
The missing DNA chromosome.
We had a genetic
leap from the apes.
What is that?
Where did that come from?
>> Yeah.
We're hybrids.
And distinguishing that-- I
guess at this moment, is good--
is that we're all
hybrids, and that it's
a part of the greater galactic
story that we seed each other--
that we seed consciousness,
that we seed beings.
So say, the abduction program
taken just in that context,
it might seem weird.
But in a greater context, it's
like, well who seeded us?
And with that, to my
knowledge or what I've gotten,
is that there's seven different
extraterrestrial genetics that
are involved in
the seeding of us.
And that have then gone forward.
And so we have those
lineages in us.
And that's why our
genetic material
is awesome for the
Grays to utilize
in creating the hybrid
civilizations, as well
as the hybrid children.
>> So you mentioned Grays.
Let's just kind of
identify that a little bit.
Grays, meaning, is that the
typical term for the beings
from the Zeta Reticuli?
>> Yeah.
>> And that's mostly these
beings that you see in movies.
>> Yeah, big eyes, big heads.
There's a lot different kinds.
You know, there's ones that are
super negatively-oriented, ones
that have worked
with the government.
There's a few different
kinds, different timelines.
>> So we can say--
and I'm glad you mentioned that.
So we see these Gray
beings, doesn't necessarily
mean just like with humans,
we have different color skin
humans.
Not all the Grays-- even
though they may be grayish--
are there some brown Grays?
>> I think that they're
all pretty gray.
But they could have
different, say motivations
or different energies.
So there are some that are
like incredibly benevolent.
And then there's
some that have really
taken a turn based on
this hybrid program,
and come to a little bit
more of a balanced place.
>> So you think initially,
the ones before they engaged
into this hybridization
program, were maybe not as nice?
>> Well, there they're
fifth dimensional beings,
but they're negatively-oriented.
So they have all the technology.
They have of the
genetic know-how.
They have all of that.
But they are
negatively-oriented,
and they're more hive mentality.
And so at the beginning
of the program,
it was a lot more intense.
They didn't know how to work
with humans because they
genetically modified their
emotions out of themselves.
But through this program,
we sparked something in them
that made them, to the
best of their ability,
understand more of
the emotional body,
and start to
understand how to work
with us in a way that doesn't
completely freak us out.
>> So probably the abductions
that are happening now are less
aggressive, a little more
compassionate than maybe some
of the abductions that were
happening 10 or 20 years ago,
in the early days.
In the Benny and Barney
Hill, the Whitney Strieber
and some of these early records
that we have of this happening.
>> Exactly.
>> Interesting.
>> Yeah.
>> Are there still bad
ones out there, you think?
>> Yeah.
>> When we say bad?
You know, I mean like ones
that aren't as compassionate,
I would say, like that.
>> And for the most part, most
of the Zeta Reticuli have died off.
>>Interesting.
That's why there was an
urgency to do this, you know.
Because they couldn't reproduce.
And so they needed
a way to continue on,
in a way that was continuing
on with them, which is us,
in a different way.
So, yes.
>> Interesting.
So we've got more than five,
or around five races out there
with humans kind of
helping to seed that.
What's the next steps?
Where do we go from here?
>> The next steps.
The next steps are that
there's many different possible
timelines of what
is going to happen.
So then we get into more of
the timeline metaphysical
probability of someone's
personal incarnational choice.
And through that,
there's timelines.
Because right now is when the
Grays split off from human.
This is like us right
now, in the future,
in a certain timeline
became a Gray.
Genetically modified
ourselves, went underground
in underground tunnels and,
like, evolved in a certain way,
with focus on the
intellect versus emotion.
>> Did they say why they went
to the underground tunnels?
>> Well, because they started
destroying the planet too much.
But my personal opinion is
that it's like the government
underground scenario.
So it's kind of future
government ended up
becoming that.
It's my own kind of take on it.
>> So Grays are humans?
>> Yeah, but just mutated
humans from a different parallel
reality Earth.
So it's not necessarily
like this Earth, you know?
>> So if you go
out to outer space,
you end up bumping
into Earth again?
>> Could be, in a
future timeline.
I mean, it's all so
intertwined, you know?
>> It's kind of starting to
make sense to me a little bit.
I'm seeing different things.
I'm hearing different things.
But we'll let the audience
decide if it makes sense
to them or not.
But I mean, that
totally makes sense.
You know, you have the
whole Denver airport
big underground
tunnel thing, with all
the craziness and
underground dulce.
And you have all of
this stuff, you know?
And George Bush buying up
all the mountains in Europe,
and like building
caves and caverns.
So I can see how
humanity could have gone,
or still, I guess,
could go that direction.
>> Yeah.
And then the other one,
the other direction--
>> The other direction--
>> --which is my
direction, my focus,
I would say your focus too,
is the complete and utter
transformation into
the fifth dimension,
and the shifting of Earth
to a healed space and like
a united humanity and oneness.
And galactic contact.
So that is the other timeline.
>> So they kind of saw,
since they lived that
timeline, they kind of saw
OK, this is what happens
if we make these choices
and we live in this timeline.
>> Yes.
>> So let's go back, and let's
tell ourselves a different
story.
And let's create a
different future,
because living in
underground tunnels
because the world's too
toxic to live in, sucks.
>> Yeah.
It doesn't end up working.
>> Interesting.
>> It hits me really deep
to think that the most kind
of negative-- like, it's
like, oh, the government, oh,
Monsanto--
that they end up
going so far down
into the depths of
darkness, that they end up
coming back full
circle, which is
a beautiful exercise in, like,
darkness to light, you know?
And a different
perspective on looking
at this simultaneous
government that we see.
All of the realities are,
like, all jumbled right now.
And then they'll
start breaking off.
But right now, it's like, OK.
I'm like, wow.
The chemtrails.
Like, you end up saving me,
like, in a different version,
you know?
And so it puts it
into perspective.
>> Yes.
Many different perspectives,
but yes, a perspective.
>> It puts it into
a perspective.
>> It does put it
into a perspective.
You have a little mothy thing.
There we go.
It's your friend.
Hi, friend.
OK, now you can
come say hi to me.
Thank you.
OK.
Do we just keep going?
>> Yeah.
[LAUGHS]
So getting back to
the hybrid children--
because that's your
focus right now--
can you tell us how that
started, and where are we at?
Catch us up to speed with
the whole children project.
>> Well, how it started was
through the mixing of the DNA
in the abduction program.
So they would use
the human genetics,
and then mix it with the Gray
genetics, do their stuff,
and then create
these kids from that.
And there's been
different generations.
The first ones were very
sickly and didn't make it.
The later ones did make
it and are thriving.
>> And what was the
reason for not making it?
>> The reason for not making
it was the lack of humanity.
>> The lack of humanity?
>> The lack of
nurture, you know?
It's this idea that science
and genetics, and even
their energetic
know-how of, like,
creating an energetic template
vessel for incarnation,
they could do all of that stuff.
But when it came down
to it, these kids
couldn't make it
because of a lack
of this missing link of
love, of like emotion
and of connection.
>> So literally, they went
so far in their intellect,
that their lack
of emotions has--
it's like the missing link
that they still, even that far
advanced, even
that far evolved--
thousands, if not millions
of years in the future--
they're missing
the one component
that we all know creates life.
Doesn't matter--
>> --what planet.
>> --what planet we're in,
what religion I guess you are,
from what part of
humanity you're from.
But we all know in
every movie, that's
the big lesson in everything
in all of our stories,
and our religions, and
our science fiction.
Everything is love.
It's all about love.
So that's the missing link.
>> That's the missing link.
>> --that they have forgotten.
>> Yeah.
And the human mothers--
there were some human mothers
amongst the fearful scenario
of being abducted--
could maintain
this love for their
alien mutated child.
And nurture them to the degree
that they could thrive--
well, could survive, and
then eventually thrive.
And so that altered the race.
And it also altered--
I mean, that was a big
shift, I think, even
in the human collective,
to be able to love.
I mean, it is your offspring,
but to love something alien,
you know?
And it's this mixing
that's happening.
And much of this is happening
in the sub and unconscious.
It's like hidden away memories.
But it is shifting
and now translating
into the collective
consciousness
in a really powerful way.
>> I'm just going to
mention something.
So actually, I
recently saw TED Talks
of this autistic boy
who-- or at least, he
was diagnosed with autism.
And he got over his autism.
And I'll put a link
into this video here.
But he actually was able to
overcome his autism by love--
his parents loving him.
It wasn't any kind of superfood
or anything that they gave him.
He says, I got
over the hardships
I had because of my
parents taking the time
to spend the time with
me, and be with me,
and nurture me, and love me.
And that's what healed these
autistic traits that he had.
>> Jeez.
>> And there's
videos of him, like--
it was hardcore.
It was messed up.
>> That's amazing.
>> So it makes sense.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, it's great.
So now, these
children are thriving.
And what's going on?
What are they saying?
>> Well, so now, they're
energetically and physically
connected to their
parents, which are us--
who are us.
And it is their sole motivation
to telepathically just inundate
us with these memories, and to
connect with us in dream time,
and to also just implant in
us this reality that we've
chosen to go towards.
It's like, OK, go more
in this direction.
Go more in this direction.
So they're really,
right now, our guides--
>> Yeah, OK.
>> --back to ourselves.
>> You know, I'm just thinking
about the first humans
to arrive on Earth, if
they came to this planet
in a similar-type fashion.
I wonder if there was
that kind of connection
to their home world that
they had to come in and--
I'm just trying
to imagine trying
to bring it home, in some way.
So if we can imagine
Earth and humans,
these first hybrid
humans being here
and still having,
energetically, their parents
off world on another planet,
and how that connection would
happen, it doesn't seem that
far out when you start to think
of it in those aspects.
>> Well, and it
is close to home.
I mean, we're in Sedona.
But the Phoenix
Lights '97, right?
Shalanaya mother
ship came over--
>> Wait, Shala--
>> Shalanaya.
That's the first hybrid race.
And they'll be the
first ones to land.
>> Oh, wow.
>> The first hybrid race,
but the hybrid kids will be
the first to contact beings.
And the hybrid kids
are on that ship.
Like, some of them live
on that actual ship.
And then Shalanaya
ships have actually
been seen on this property
by one of my good friends.
And so the kids, I mean,
they're right there, you know?
I mean, it's like they're
on an airplane or something.
Ah, behind the tree.
I can picture.
>> Peeking around
the corner, hey.
>> Yeah.
>> Go back to bed.
[LAUGHS]
How does this story end?
>> The story ends, well,
kind of how it begins.
Well, you can see how it
ends by the trajectory of how
it has started, that
I was told that I confirmed
that I have hybrid kids.
And after that session,
about three hybrid moms
came up to me.
And they already knew
that they had kids.
And at that time, it
was very like, whisper
about having hybrid kids.
It was very like,
tucked away and not
really outspoken about this.
And there were maybe
like different abductees
who knew about it.
But it wasn't like a
known out there thing.
And that next day,
it became very clear
that my soul's dedication
was to make the
hybrid children known.
And so for the rest
of that summer,
I didn't do anything else.
I stopped all other work.
And I just started
creating the hybrid website
for the community.
And I started
connecting with my kids,
because I couldn't
connect with anyone else.
I didn't even know that
I was going to connect
other people to their kids.
I didn't know that.
All I was starting
with was, like, OK.
I'm the parent.
I'm going to start
connecting with my children.
And I wanted a space to
be made for other parents
to have this be known, and
for it to be findable-- like,
for it to be known in that way.
And then later, I
found out that I
was designed to do that,
that there would be those
online platforms
that people would come to.
>> Interesting.
>> Yeah.
So then, it started.
And then, the first month, it
was like 100 unique visits.
>> 100 unique visits?
>> Per month, to the website.
>> Oh, I see.
>> Just very, very small.
And within a year,
it hit 20,000.
So in one year, hybrid alien
children went to 20,000.
And now--
>> Is this the Facebook page?
>> This is the website.
>> The actual website, OK.
>> So it's like
exponential growth.
>> I'll put a link in
here for everybody,
so they can see that.
Insert link.
>> Yeah.
So it's the exponential growth
has been the fascinating thing
for me to watch,
and how a few emails
trickle in here and there.
And then it's just like,
I'm inundated every day
with people messaging me.
And so the wake up
process and the next step,
as you were asking, is that
people are gonna remember.
People are gonna have
dreams about these kids.
memories about all of this.
Know the next stages of moving,
of the assimilation of moving
to these sacred sites.
All of this
information is coming
and is already happening.
And I see these people.
It's amping up in the collective
in such a big and powerful way.
It's really fun and crazy
for even me to watch.
Like, I didn't know
where this was going.
And so I'm just kind of--
I'm the driver, but I'm
also like the observer.
>> Absolutely.
It's great to acknowledge that.
So your work right
now is in addition
to working with
your own children,
you're kind of this
conduit, this go-to person
for people to connect.
And how do you explain
your work in that sense?
How do you help people connect
with their hybrid children?
>> I help them
connect by, I guess,
you can picture it as like a
cord, like a plug-in cord--
that, like, I have the cord.
And I just, like,
plug it in to them.
And somehow, I was
given the cord.
And it's a kind of
a hard cord to find
because it's deeply
buried in the subconscious
and unconscious.
So I just connect it.
So there's an energetic
cording that I connect,
that is more of like
a astral activity.
I don't do it consciously,
but it just happens.
And then I also bring through--
I get the clairvoyant
image of the child.
Or they talk to me through
all the different senses
that I perceive.
And I deliver whatever messages,
deliver about their essence,
deliver their image--
whatever the parent
needs to know that's
going to benefit them in the
next stage of their connection
with their child.
That's what I bring through.
>> Excellent.
And for every person, it's a
different message, I assume.
>> Yeah.
It's very different,
and it could be things
that they might
not want to hear.
>> Well, for example,
has anybody not received
the information very well?
In what case when you say,
not what they want to hear?
>> Well, I guess, maybe
that wasn't even accurate.
Because every person--
I've probably done about
50 in the past few years.
And every person
has completely--
like, it's really hit
them on a very deep level.
And they've all resonated.
Maybe the not what
they want to hear
is the shifting that they need
to do to be able to meet them.
Because it's not like you can
just stay at your 9:00 to 5:00
job, like, chowing down
on a burger, and, like,
they're going to move into
your house in the neighborhood.
>> So, explain, for example,
what are some of the shifts
that need to take place?
>> Some of the shifts that
need to take place are,
one is for the human parents
to follow their excitement--
to, like, really align
themselves with their passion.
Because only in
that state will they
be able to shift to where
they can actually meet them.
So one is the transition to
having them be more themselves,
which is a lot.
In some cases, it could be
visiting certain places,
that they need to go visit
certain places to make
a certain connection.
They might need to
go to a sacred site.
They might need to move
to a different place.
>> And the children actually
come through and say this?
>> Yeah, in some cases.
I use my own filter
in the way of knowing
how much is too much.
Because the kid would
push them all the way.
The kid is like, go, you know?
>> You look at the person and
you're like, where they're at.
And you're like, OK,
are they resonating
with this information?
Or are they are they
taking steps back?
>> Yeah.
So I give as much as
is going to be helpful.
Because if say, like,
give up your whole life
and go to Tibet--
>> Then they're going to throw
the whole out not listen to any
of it.
>> Exactly.
And the kid understands that.
And I have dialogues
with them too.
>> Do they knock on your
door afterwards and say,
why didn't you tell them this?
Or, why didn't you
tell them that?
And then you say,
well, because this.
And they say, oh, OK.
Do you do have those kind of?
>> Kind of, yeah.
>> The kind of
conversation, how it goes?
>> Yeah.
So I'll give you a scenario.
One of my childhood friends--
well, our families
were friends, I
met him maybe once
when I was, like, five.
And I never met
him, but we always
knew about each
other-- similar age.
And he's an artist
too, very creative.
And finally, there was something
when this hybrid children
thing started.
It was like, you need
to go back to Utah
and connect with this guy that
I had never met in person.
And so we connected.
And within 10 minutes, he starts
telling me about these things--
abduction experiences that
started happening right
when he hit puberty.
I'm like, OK.
I knew that.
And I very quickly
heard and felt
that he had these hybrid
kids, and that we particularly
had hybrid kids together.
And we were just
friends and stuff,
but they used our genetic
material together.
And so then I told him about
the hybrid kids and stuff.
But I didn't tell him
that I felt that yet.
It wasn't time.
And so I went back to LA.
And I actually channeled the
kids that I saw that were ours.
And there was a boy and a girl.
And then I went back
two weeks later,
and he said that since
he had been around me,
he had been having these
experiences at night where
these two kids would come
and knock on his door.
And every night
that week, his dog
had been needing
to go out at night.
And he would go into
this kind of dream state.
And these kids, like,
who he was terrified of,
would just knock on his door.
And he had these dreams
of, like, pushing the door
shut as these kids
were trying to get in.
And it was like,
no, don't come in.
And at that same time right
before I knew that in LA,
I tried to tune into the kids.
And they were like, we don't
need to be with you, Mom.
Like, we need to
take care of Dad.
>> Oh, wow.
>> So all of this was happening.
And like, it was
confirmed by him.
So there are some people
that, they're just like--
>> They're not ready for it.
>> No.
No, you know?
>> Well, after our session,
it's a lot to throw on you.
It's like all day yesterday,
I kept talking to Daniel--
my cameraman here--
about, like, yeah.
Maybe I don't know if
I'm ready for real kids
here in this third dimension.
But I might be ready for--
>> --for an alien.
>> --for an alien kid.
[LAUGHS]
As crazy as that sounds.
So yeah, I guess most people
would kind of the other way
around.
Even if you had regular
kids on this dimension,
even contemplating another
kid, that's like a major--
>> It's a major thing.
>> That's a thing
that you just, like--
I don't need that
worry/responsibility.
But it sounds like
these kids can kind of
take care of themselves.
If they're guiding us along,
they're more of the parents,
and we're the kids,
in many aspects.
But do they have basic needs?
Do they need to
be potty trained?
How does that work?
>> Their caretakers, the
other ETs that they're with,
they're taking care of them.
>> They're getting them up
to speed with how to lift up
the toilet seat.
>> Yeah.
They're being trained for Earth.
That's their classroom.
So they don't go to school, they
go to like Earth 101, yeah.
>> Which I've actually talked
to several abductees who--
>> --the classroom?
>> --or even, yeah,
the classroom.
And they're on ships.
And they see classrooms
where they're
teaching them how to buy
stuff at the supermarket.
And it's like-- and I heard that
like three to five years ago,
abductees talking about
this and having the same.
And it's not just one, but
several of these abductees
saying, hey, I was on a ship,
and I saw that too.
And that's so bizarre.
What does that mean?
It means there's
something coming.
>> Right.
So it looks like all the dots
are getting connected here.
Something's coming.
>> Yeah.
>> So is that what's
going to happen?
Are they going to join us?
You said they're in another
dimension on another planet.
Are they going to join us here?
>> Yes, they are.
>> That's the grand plan.
The Freelancers are going
to join us on Earth.
So the other civilizations,
they're on their civilizations.
But there were kids that were
held out of time, in a sense.
So they're not aging.
They're just, like,
held in time--
continuing on, but they're going
to be inserted into our reality
when the time is right.
And they will be introduced
to Earth as our children.
And they will be the
first step and conduit
into contact with
other civilizations.
>> Right, which makes it a
little easier on humanity
if there's an actual
alien that is part human--
>> --and their child.
>> --and is a child.
So you're not going to
blow it out of the sky,
or we're being
attacked by aliens!
How can kids be attacking us?
>> Right.
Unless they're maybe perceived
through a negative filter,
which would be the
Black Eyed children.
>> OK, I'm glad you
brought that up.
Because I was thinking
of bringing that up,
but I didn't want to bring any
negativity into this session.
So, Black Eyed children.
What are they?
>> Well, I mean--
>> People can go online and
search all the Black Eyed
children stuff.
But what is your interpretation?
>> I think it is my belief
that Black Eyed children are
a hybrid children perceived
through a negative ego filter.
There could be some
freak creepy children
coming into this dimension
or something that
are Black Eyed children too.
But after hearing that
experience with the guy
that I just told you
about, that the kids are
knocking on his door, and he
perceived their eyes as black--
like black kind of scary eyes--
and I'm going, OK, I
know where his ego is at.
He does not want
to look at this.
And then he is then perceiving
them as super creepy
and super scary.
And so I'm going, yeah.
Like, I'm thinking
that that is--
>> So the Black Eyed children
aren't necessarily negative,
it's the people who are
perceiving them have those
negative projections
that are giving to them.
So therefore, they're
telling the world,
I don't want you
to open the door.
They're going to come in.
And they're going to kill
you and cut you to pieces,
and put you in the freezer.
[LAUGHS]
Sorry, so don't do it.
Don't open the door.
Even though they're like
kind of cute and they need
help, and they're super
pysch, and everything else.
But they need your blood.
>> Yeah.
>> They're going
to suck you dry.
[LAUGHS]
Because that's how, typically,
the Black Eyed children
are perceived, in a lot of ways.
>> They are.
And maybe there are
creepy, like-- you know,
there are dark energies and
spirits that I've worked with.
>> You think of maybe a few in
the first batch didn't quite go
a certain way?
>> Maybe.
Yeah, they dropped them off.
And they're like, let's just
make this a horror show.
>> Yeah, let's just throw
them back at the parents.
Let's not deal.
So even up in the
craft, they're like,
we can't deal with these kids.
>> Genetic experiment
went wrong.
>> We gotta drop those humans--
yeah, especially the ones
that really aren't accepting
this information very much.
Let's just give
them a little taste.
>> Maybe.
I mean--
>> Oh my goodness.
>> Who knows?
>> Thank you.
I like that perspective on
the Black Eyed children.
It kind of makes sense.
So this other guy
you're talking about,
his perception was kind of the
standard Black Eyed children
perception?
>> Yeah, it was.
That's how he described it.
>> But you, at the same
time, were getting direct
communication from them saying,
we just want to communicate.
>> And like, darling
energies, you know?
Like, really sweet.
And I know dark
energies, you know?
I used to clear
poltergeists in houses.
Like, I'm OK with that energy.
And if it was that, that's cool.
I'd honor that, you know?
But it isn't.
But in some cases,
maybe, you know?
Like we said, it's a little--
>> I mean, and even if it is,
I think you can transmute it
in a sense by--
again, we create
our own realities
with wherever we
project on whatever it
is we're going to do.
So if we're going
to project that,
we're going to create
that in our own heads,
even if it's not really that.
And same thing.
It could be totally negative,
and you can transmute it
to something positive.
And that's a good thing.
I don't see anything negative
with transforming the negative
into positive.
>> Right.
>> So even if these demon
kids, black eyes, fangs,
and blood sucking--
even if you did show
love and compassion,
you can still transmute
it into something lovely.
>> Yes.
>> So there is no negative.
Even if it's negative,
you can still
transmute it into a positive.
So whichever scenario you go
down, why not open your arms
and give these kids a big hug?
>> And a cup of juice.
A cup of juice.
Every child--
>> I was going to
say glass of milk,
but we're going away from--
we're going to go
with a glass of juice.
>> Glass of juice.
Not from concentrate.
>> Not from concentrate, fresh.
>> Fresh juice.
>> We can do that.
>> Non-pasteurized, very good.
>> Organic.
>> Organic juice.
I like that.
Cool.
Well, that's a lot
of information,
and a lot to chew on.
I think the sun's going down.
It might be a good
place to wrap this up.
Thank you very much, Bridget.
This was awesome information.
And I'd love to continue to
see how this develops
>> Sounds great.
>> We'd love to see more of you.
>> Thank you, Reuben.
>> Awesome, thank you.
[MEDITATIVE MUSIC]
[LAUGHS]
>> We can have hot tea in there.
>> OK.
Good, good.