You are all naturally wired
for growth and spiritual expansion.
The expansion is accelerated by the ongoing
invitation from the level of the higher self
to look beyond that which is already
known by the person and mind.
And so, you will from time to time surprise
yourselves by manifesting certain circumstances
that tickle the current understanding of the self,
and nudge it into a broader, wider perspective.
The more you sense yourself, feeling either triggered
or intrigued by the information delivered to you,
the more you are signally to yourself the relevancy of it,
as a usable stepping stone in your personal storyline.
Where this relevancy lies is in the finding of your own
personal truth regarding the information given to you,
or whether it lies in the facing of certain fear-
based beliefs so you will be able to transform them.
You all play this game, both on
an individual as well as collective scale.
Now when it comes to open contact with the ETs, with multi-dimensionals,
with those aspects of you that you have chosen to temporarily forget,
to serve you on your journey of remembering on the Earth stage.
We understand that for many, and for a long time,
there may seem to have been hardly
anything more ‘out there’ than this particular idea,
and yet you have shown yourselves
in over a thousand ways along this journey,
that deep within, you all know and never truly
have forgotten your connection to the stars or to your greater selves.
This type of contact, it is within you already.
It has been depicted in cave paintings and ancient artifacts.
It has been reflected back to you
by those ancient and modern channelers
you know usually refer to as artists,
by their paintings, music, books and films,
lyrics from songs and poetry throughout the ages.
And this type of contact, though not always shared with the public,
already has shown up in many
astronomical and army based observations
and even is represented within your own DNA
and let us tell you there is no ‘junk’ in there.
It is all pure and infinite potential,
and once embraced it will come to
feel like a logical part of a much greater puzzle,
that, once you speak it’s language,
the language of your hearts,
you will continue to explore within your own evolution
as we are too exploring the infinite amount of wondrous ways
wherein All That Is expresses itself by meeting and greeting you.
Ever wonder if there's intelligent
life elsewhere in the universe?
Well, I have....I've been wondering since I was a kid.
My name is Reuben Langdon.
And on March 29th 2007 in the middle of the day,
I saw a number of strange objects in the sky.
Coincidentally, I was working on
the film Avatar at the time, playing an alien.
And ever since then I've been on a quest...
To find out if aliens really do exist and if so...
...are they here with us?
If beings of higher intelligence are here...
...what is their purpose?
Why don't they make themselves more known?
Why the secrecy?
I've asked these questions to many experts,
yet each seems to have a different theory.
So I thought to myself,
why not ask the aliens directly?
So that's what I set out to do!
Well, sort of...
>> So here we are
in lovely Sedona.
Amazing property here.
Thank you to Dana for
letting us use his place.
>> Gorgeous.
>> And thank you for showing
up in this awesome vortex spot
of crazy interdimensional
cosmic high-wave energy.
>> Perfectly put.
And you too.
>> Yes.
Well, I can't get enough
of this place.
So any opportunity to come--
and I'm glad our timelines
merged, pathways merged.
To meet at this spot in this land,
its such a sacred area.
You are from the Netherlands?
>> Yes.
>> And you're here in America
doing traveling and doing
your work.
>> Following my heart.
>> Following your heart.
So tell us a little
bit about that.
What is your work, your
play, your what you're doing?
And how does it all start?
>> Wow, OK.
So right now, I'm traveling
as an interstellar channel.
I do group Q&As with people.
And I'm channeling
my interstellar guide
Arjun, who is of the
Yahyel, as I understand it.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> And I also do private
sessions, one-on-ones,
that are a little bit different
than the groups because it goes
really in-depth.
And receiver is laying down.
And it's mixed between
energy work, Q&A
because there is
definitely dialogue.
And it accelerates
and streamlines
the self-healing properties of
the body if the receiver can
match the frequencies that I
could say the ETs are offering.
Arjun works with a team.
So it's never boring, or
it's never just one guide.
But he's my hub,
as I understand it,
and he translates
information through me.
I allow that to flow through
and share it with other people
because I'm basically
in love with this work
and with their energies.
And everything started
to come together
for me into this kind of work
about 2 and 1/2 years ago.
>> Fairly recent then.
>> That is fairly recent.
Actually, stepping forward with
the vocal channeling, I mean.
And years before that,
I was writing it down.
But I've been receiving
downloads of information
and having visitation
experiences
and physical experiences with
what I believe or understand
to be the interstellar
family members since I
was a child, since age 3.
So for me, it was
quite a journey
to understand what was going on.
And in Europe, I guess,
it's less common.
>> Is it?
The idea of contact and--
>> Yeah, it's not
spoken of that much.
Or at least it wasn't
in my childhood.
>> --abduction, temporary
detainment, all of these.
>> Exactly, yeah.
That was totally
unknown phenomena to me
until maybe at age 26, I
started hearing about that.
And I was like, oh,
wow, how about that?
>> So you had
personal experiences,
but you didn't really
think about that?
>> Yes, I did.
I realized that it
seemed to be just me.
>> You thought it was
just you until 26.
>> Yeah, and it was eye-opening
for me because, wow.
I just thought something wasn't
all together right maybe.
I knew it wasn't ghosts.
I knew it was other than
people that have deceased.
And of course, you
can channel that too.
So I knew that wasn't it,
but I couldn't pinpoint it
because of that.
I wasn't into sci-fi.
Because all films
with shooting in it,
I was super sensitive
to all of that.
So for a long time, I was just--
well, I learned how to
embrace it within myself,
so I found a way with it.
But I kept it to myself
for a very, very long time
and used the
information for myself.
Already as a child,
I had experiences.
I knew I was going
somewhere else in the night
and being brought back.
And I learned lessons.
And I could embrace
them so easily.
And the conviction of it was so
strong, it was so heart-based.
What just confused
me at the time
was that my teachers
in school were teaching
totally different things.
>> The teachers
of like regular--
>> The normal primary school.
>> Primary school, right.
>> So that was confusing.
>> Different things in
the sense of history?
Or what kind of
things were different?
>> History, but also
definitely the way--
I as a child was being
taught how you will
grow up and go into society.
It was very much--
>> Structured.
>> Yeah.
>> And this way, you're going
to be a lawyer, a doctor.
>> Yeah.
You study something, you
become that one thing.
>> Go to college.
>> You choose a profession.
You need to know
what you want to be.
It was very strict
in that sense.
>> And the messages you were
getting were not of that sense?
>> Follow your heart, do what
you feel fits your core energy.
And that is much more intuitive
than the professions that
are usually offered to you.
So very young, I
decided I wanted
to do something with art
because drawing was my language.
I wasn't speaking.
There was a part that I was
a really quiet kid, which
most people probably wouldn't
expect when they meet me now.
>> And all the teachers
were probably saying,
this is just a hobby, you
can't make money at this,
you can't do anything.
>> Yes.
You're not raised to
believe-- like the societies
or artists, bohemian lifestyle,
where is this ever going to go?
And isn't it time for
something more serious?
So that never worked for me.
So I knew that very young.
In school, there were lessons
coming from a teacher.
And I'm like, no.
And I didn't know
why I understood
that that wasn't the way.
But that became more clear
throughout my puberty.
The visitations
became more intense.
There was definitely a
time that I resisted it.
I thought this is
getting too crazy,
I don't want this anymore.
I was living a double life.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> But that was all--
I can see now when I
look in retrospect,
that was all because I didn't
understand what was going on.
And then at age 24, I
actually sought help.
>> Like medical help?
>> Yeah.
I thought I needed to
speak at least to someone
that I feel safe speaking to
and sharing this story because I
was keeping it in for so long.
But then I was in art school.
So art was a beautiful
and natural outlet for me
to share or to process more what
was going on in my life before.
And then I went to see a--
I think you call it
a psychotherapist.
>> Psychiatrist,
psychotherapist.
That works too.
>> The most easy one
that they send you to.
And he appeared to be
an ex-hypnotherapist.
Which was great because
he could really feel
into my story very intuitively.
So we understood each other.
And he just reflected to me
exactly what I needed to know.
And he said, you can
work with these "dreams,"
that is not the enemy.
It's you speaking to you.
And then it clicked so quickly.
I only needed just a few
conversations with him
to grasp it and suddenly be
like, oh, OK, this is it.
And only a few months after
that, I saw my first UFO.
And then everything
started accelerating.
>> Once you sort of accepted
it, then that created the space
and the pathways.
The pipes were free to--
>> Through which more
information could come without
freaking me out.
>> So it's really the freak
factor that sort of kept those
doors semi-closed?
>> I was super shy
and, as a child,
afraid of judgments
from outside.
I was raised Christian,
so this is super
leaning towards the
unexplainable, you know,
what from the Christian
side is just evil.
So I kept it to myself.
I knew it was good, I
knew it wasn't evil.
But I knew it was
other, and people
might respond to it that way.
>> Yeah, and you didn't want to
be demonized as some people who
do come out with this.
>> Yeah.
And it must have been
much harder in the past.
I mean, this is
heaven right now.
I mean, what you're doing,
you're interviewing--
>> Yeah.
We're having a conversation
about ETs and talking to them.
It's not a big deal.
>> Yeah.
Coming home, that's
what it is to me.
Because I'm like, oh, man,
now I'm surrendering to it.
I'm really going with the flow.
>> Very cool.
And so tell us a
little bit about Arjun,
the Yahyel, your understanding
of that alien race, society.
What kind of messages are
you getting in that sense?
>> So I understand
he's of a hybrid race.
They exist out of--
that sounds so technical.
They are result of the
future human race--
one future human
race, one timeline--
that found themselves eventually
at a dead end, you could say.
>> The Zetas, essentially.
The Zeta story.
>> Yes.
>> So we've covered this story.
>> OK, great, so
I don't have to.
OK, great.
So that's technically
what I understand
the Yahyel are-- the last,
the youngest race that
came out of that experiment.
They're very much
like us physically.
And Arjun looks-- he's a
little taller than I am.
He's blond.
He has a slight curl,
he has blue eyes.
First, I thought he was a
Pleiadian because of the look.
>> Yeah, we sort of have
this classification,
I've always wondered
this, maybe I'll
ask Arjun this later.
We have this idea of
Pleiadians being this way.
And then I've talked to
other Pleiadian channels,
and they're like, oh,
no, we have Cat people,
we have all these different--
there's many types.
>> Yes, I was also just going
by the pictures in the books,
I guess.
So I was thinking, oh,
this must be the Pleiadian.
Because he was so light.
>> And it's also, I
think an energy.
Did he ever say
there is other races?
Do we have black or
Hispanic-looking Yahyel beings?
>> They have colors.
>> They have different colors
and different hair color.
>> Yeah.
>> All right.
Again, we can go into that
later with those guys.
>> But he's known
me my whole life.
We made a pre-my birth agreement
to do this if I wanted to.
So this is always a
free choice agreement.
I decided to do it, to
test it out, in a sense.
So I did art school,
I was an artist first.
And then I became a
life coach, overcoming
my fear of working with
people, in a sense,
and really wanting to share
the heart's message that
was already kicking in there.
And from a life coach, I
went to this channeling work,
which basically took the life
coaching over in a few months,
very quickly.
And I started to
come out with that.
>> So you're sort of life
coaching through the channeling
work.
>> In a sense, yes.
>> You are guiding people.
>> It's the same mission, if
you want to look at it that way.
>> Just helping people
along with their stuff.
>> Yeah.
And I just have a lot
of assistance now.
And Arjun works with a
big bunch of other races.
So there's kind of a
steady healing team
present when I do the
groups or private sessions.
>> Have you had direct
communication with those guys?
>> Yes.
Actually, one I know
from since I was a child.
He's a Mantid being.
He's one of the three in
this study team, I call it.
>> Three Mantis beings?
>> No, no.
There's three beings--
Sirius, Mantid, and Sassani.
And these three work with
Arjun, who is Yahyel.
So they work together
a lot, I understand.
It's much more flexible and
interwoven-- is that a word?--
>> Yeah.
>> --than maybe you would think
when you just dive into this.
They're not super
separated races.
They do a lot of stuff together.
>> And the Mantid being, is he--
>> I remember him from
visitations in my childhood.
Arjun is my hub, so we are
really, really close, also
even genetically somehow.
Throughout my family line, with
the DNA, there is a connection.
And that's why it's easiest
to have this one study guide
and translate the
other ones to me.
>> I see.
So it's with Rob Gauthier.
He uses TReb to access all
these other different beings.
>> As his hub, yeah.
>> As his hub.
And we joke about it.
He goes fishing with TReb.
And in that process, all these
other beings can come through.
And he's sort of
oblivious to it.
But he has many beings coming
through him all the time.
>> Yeah.
So all I see,
basically-- well, I
do get the images
of the other beings
if there's a cross-connection
going on like that.
But if I have a question
in the background,
I can actually have
a Q&A with a person
or facilitate the Q&A between
Arjun and the questioner
and have a question of
myself in the background.
And in my mind--
maybe it sounds weird-- but
I'd turn my head to the right.
He's always on the right side.
>> Arjun.
>> Yeah.
And I will see his expression.
And he can actually answer
my questions in the back.
And my attention
goes to the left.
There's this--
>> Left-right.
>> Yeah, movement always
happening when I go
into channeling as well.
I kind of fall to the
left, and then Arjun
comes from the right.
>> Does the Mantoid
being have a name?
>> No.
>> He's just Mantoid guy.
>> Yeah.
And I haven't asked
for a name either.
I did ask Arjun for
a name at some point
because we didn't use a name
either in the beginning.
So for months, it was just
my Yahyel guide or parallel
version of myself, because he
is a future version of me.
I didn't really ask
for names in the team.
Although the Sassani is a
female, and her name is Nanuk.
>> Nanuk.
>> Yeah.
And I got that name while I was
painting her face, because I'm
painting my team at the moment.
And I want to have
portraits of them,
and I'm working on that now.
And it's fascinating
because I get
to see in my head
what they look like.
But then maybe sometimes
they want to dress up,
they want to look
a little different.
That they let me know, OK,
just add this and this symbol
because that's the theme
I'm representing for you
or for a client, for instance.
So art is still a big part
of my work in a sense.
It's very visual.
>> Can you describe the Sirian
and the Sassani being at all?
>> So when I was
painting Nanuk's face--
she's the Sassani being--
she inspired me, you could
say, to put a sun and a moon
on her forehead.
And later, I got a
dream that explained
how she was about balancing
energies, male and female.
And that's part of her
role in the healing team.
And she's really
connected to nature.
So they all have their own
little niche, something
that they're really good at.
And the Mantid being is really
amazing with bone structures,
skeleton, the doctor's kind
of work, realigning the more
tough stuff, in a sense.
And I don't know another
translation for it,
but electro currents-- he's
really strong with that.
>> Electromagnetics?
>> Yeah, in the body.
And he works on the
brain very strongly.
We have a particular
thing going on.
He was there since
I was a child,
and we did a lot of
frequency matching.
So I understand how he works.
And he's part of the
energy, you could say,
that moves my hands when
I do a healing session.
The movements that
go with the healing
amplify the work that is
being done on an astral level
because they use my energy body.
So in a sense, they wouldn't
necessarily need my body.
But because we are physical,
I'm like the portal, in a sense,
physicalizing the movements
here, getting even closer
to the other person.
>> Yeah, movement is so huge.
>> Yeah, it's really big.
>> And moving energy, we
don't necessarily do that.
But just in this
motion of the hands--
>> It's really big.
>> Especially martial artists
really understand this with
energy work.
Chi Gong, Tai Chi,
Kung Fu, all of
these different
physical movements
actually move energetics.
>> Yes, exactly.
>> Create the space.
>> And that can
come very precise.
And I love to work
with them in that way.
And the Sirian being is--
this is really hard
to put in words.
It's really the bigger
electromagnetic field,
boosting it with light and
rebalancing in that way.
Everything has a level
around you in a sense.
I do sometimes
work with my hands
up very high and
sometimes much closer.
And the being that fits in with
that part of the energy body
will assist.
Eventually, everything is,
of course, one and connected.
But they do really
know how to streamline
certain parts in the system.
And when there's a group
Q&A, they're there,
and they work in the back
for those who from the heart
wish some assistance on
maybe whatever kind of topic
is with them.
>> And they speak through Arjun.
>> Yeah,
there's information
coming through.
>> So did they ever come forward
and say, hi, I'm Mantis guy?
>> No, not their role.
Very clearly not their role.
>> So it's really just
communicating through Arjun,
through you.
>> Adding to the information for
the questioner to get a clearer
picture of what their higher
mind wants to come through
to their conscious minds.
Because that's their common
goal-- to reflect to anybody
their own inner
rhythm, in a sense.
They're just putting it
into words, the things
that we with our rational
mind don't focus on
that much, I guess.
Because we can, but
we weren't taught to.
So it's still, for most
people, blind spots.
And for me as well sometimes.
I really need some
good reflections.
>> And the work you do
with the energy healing--
and you did a session
for me yesterday--
that work, using
your cosmic clan
to communicate with my
cosmic clan and then help
reflect that.
That's sort of how--
>> Yeah.
It's all coming together and
coming out as one storyline,
the information
that's coming through.
>> And it's not necessarily your
cosmic clan saying this per se.
It's just that they
are maybe better
communicators to my cosmic clan.
And they can say,
OK, his cosmic clan
is saying this, so do this.
>> Exactly.
So it's not that they're--
we have this idea of
how psychics work.
And they can read our minds
and go into this stuff
and do other stuff.
But in reality, what's
probably really happening
is just my cosmic
guides are communicating
with your cosmic guides.
And then you just have a clearer
channel to your cosmic team
than I do.
>> Ah, I don't know.
>> I mean, I would say you do
because you're able to have
those dialogues in
the work you're doing.
>> I think everybody can.
>> I think everybody can too.
>> But of course, I
will say it's both.
Because some people need a
little bit more training back,
which is really what I
would want to call it--
training back into that
actually natural state.
Because that's our nature
to have that very open.
>> And the whole idea of
shamanism and shamanic
practices with our
native cultures,
that's sort of what they, from
my understanding training with
them--
when someone would go
to visit the shaman,
in essence, they're
doing the same thing.
[WIND CHIMES RING]
The shaman is connecting to
the other person's guides.
And the guides are telling
them to do this work.
>> Yes.
>> As opposed to, I'm doing this
work because I'm psychic and I
know better.
It's not that at all.
>> I even don't like that.
I avoid even the word
"healer" on my website,
for instance, because
I'm just a facilitator.
I'm letting stuff through.
I never know what's
going to happen.
I don't have a preset idea
about what somebody would
need because I don't know that.
That other person
actually knows best.
So all that is being
asked for in that moment
and being allowed
in is a reflection
of their own inner wisdom.
>> And I think as we define and
understand these terms better,
we can tell this
story now in this way.
I think maybe before,
we didn't have
the understanding,
or the knowledge
to go that deep into it.
So we just said, yeah, I'm a
healer, and I'm healing you.
And then we go, yeah,
you're healing me.
But in reality, nobody's
healing anybody else.
>> It's all self-healing
eventually.
>> Eventually,
it's self-healing.
And so I'm just giving--
it's the permission slip thing--
I'm giving you permission to...
it's tricking myself in essence.
I'm like, I'm doing
the healing work.
But just because of
the way my mind works
and the construct
of my reality....
I need this physicalized, outside
thing to do the healing.
>> But that still takes away
a little bit of the idea of--
you used the word "need"
in this description.
>> Yeah, but I guess I'm
not saying that I need that.
I'm just saying that that's the
way of a lot of our old ways
of looking at things.
And many people too-- you
know, going to the doctor,
getting the surgery, taking
the pill, all of this
is really an illusion.
>> Yeah, it's a belief
system, all of it.
>> It's a belief system.
All of it is just there for, you
know, pharmaceutical companies
to make lots of money.
And this is why they are so
keen on supporting the illusion.
>> Yeah, but you
cannot do it alone.
>> You can't do it alone, no.
This is disempowering,
is sort of the name of the
game for those structures
that are in place in order
for us to be reliant on them.
And that's what
they feed off of.
It's sort of
vampire-type energy that
can grow because that's the
archetype of that energy.
>> And then there's the trap, a
little bit, to think that that
is just being pursued
in the center,
continued even in
nowadays healing work,
even if you're a very
new paradigm about it.
I've heard this, so I
want to throw this in.
And Arjun-- because I have
my own doubts about this,
before I started doing
private sessions,
I wasn't sure if I wanted
to be a part of that idea
that somebody would
come to me for help.
And so I asked him, so
how do you look at this?
And he's like, well,
you've all decided
to be with a lot of people
here, a lot of reflections
of yourself.
So it's also
playful, and joyful,
and beautiful to look
in each other's mirror.
It's what happens
when you fall in love.
It's when you pick your friends.
It's even when you
pick your family,
even though that doesn't always
look like such a pretty mirror.
But all of that
is part of a dance
that you chose to be a part of.
So that helped me also
understand and embrace
even the old paradigm
medical system a little more,
to be like, OK,
it is what it is.
And whatever direction
you navigate to most,
just choose that.
And I also go for regular
reflections, I would say,
with colleague
interstellar healers
that are channelers, who
facilitate realignments
to get some more insights
on my own blind spots.
Because there are always
things that you're
learning about and expanding.
>> It's always good to
have another perspective.
>> Totally, yes.
>> So go get a second opinion.
>> Yes, exactly.
I love more angles to a topic.
The more the better.
And then I will pick the one
that resonates most with me.
>> Exactly.
No one is better
than the other--
>> No, it's all good.
>> --for the collective.
But for the individual, you
may have better resonance.
>> And that was the
whole journey, I think,
for me to collect the
guts, I would say,
to be faithful to what I
feel resonates most with me.
And just like I said, I
fell in love with this work.
>> You've sort of awoken to
the Yahyel channeling by going
to another channeler?
>> Yeah, in a sense.
So I've been receiving all
these downloads, mainly
in night times, or just
before waking, astral travel
experiences.
and divine synchronicity
helped me to actually attend
to one of his group sessions--
And while I was in the audience,
I didn't have any questions.
I was just feeling at home
and being in a bliss state
being with these
energies, because it
felt so much at home,
but not really questions.
And I was sitting there,
and at some point,
the sounds kind of
went down, the lights
dimmed, in my experience,
even though I was
sitting between other people.
And I felt super drawn inwards,
so I had to close my eyes.
And I felt other
beings around me.
And to have this
experience in a waking
state, that was new to me.
So I felt very
clearly that there
was work being done on me.
And I could fully relax in it.
It felt super loving.
I felt like, oh, I'm in good
hands, this is beautiful.
And then a picture was
given to me of, basically,
a cat sitting on my head.
And the energy that surrounded
that was very giggly-like,
joyful, "this is funny."
And I thought, OK--
it's like, this is you, and
the cat is on your head,
and it's funny,
and I'm like, OK.
And that whole thing
lasted maybe 10 minutes.
It was a little bit
out-of-time-ish for me.
And then that first half of
the channeling also ended.
And the sounds came back
into the room for me,
the lights went on
again, you could say.
And I was left with
that feeling that a cat
was sitting on my head.
Like an actual pressure,
I could really feel it.
And I was hesitant to
move because I thought
it might fall off, even though
I knew it wasn't really there.
And a year later,
in the Netherlands,
I went to see an
ET channeler woman.
And she lives in the
Netherlands as well.
And I actually went to have
my back straightened out.
I had some issues there
between my shoulders.
She said she did
channeling and worked
with a team that does
also physical healings
or, like we understand,
a realignment
of your own
self-healing abilities.
And I was curious about
that, so I went there.
And a month before
I went to see her,
Arjun actually
started speaking out
loud to me, which
was quite a surprise
for me because he was
coming closer and closer.
I'd seen his face.
I knew he was with me
during meditations.
And then at some point,
I asked in my mind,
I just opened conversation-- and
he had been waiting for that,
I understand that now--
asking, who are you?
And I got this huge
spelling out, Yah-Yel.
Like for him, it was more
logical to first pinpoint--
this is who we
are as a race more
where I am from
then to use a name,
because they don't use names.
So I was instantly confused,
thinking, is that his name?
But that's actually a race.
How does that work?
>> Did you hear about
the Yahyel race before?
>> Yeah, I heard
about that by then.
>> By Darryl or
other channelers?
>> Yeah, through Darryl.
And so it confused me.
But also that the answer was
so super crispy clear and loud,
that confused me.
So I instantly like,
whoa, backed away
from it not knowing what to
do with it, left it at that.
And a month later, I
went to see this woman.
And she started
channeling for me.
And maybe two minutes
into working on my back
with her team--
>> Was it a private session?
>> A private session, yes.
So I was laying on
this massage table.
And she started
to look at my back
and what could be done maybe
according to her guides.
And then Arjun was just
jumping up and down like,
hey, hello, I've been trying
to get to this girl for quite
some time now.
And she said, oh, there's
somebody here for you.
And then she just
started speaking for him,
you could say.
Oh, I have to throw this little
thing I forgot to tell you.
Just before the
session, she has a cat
that is basically
identical to the one that
was put on my head.
But I did not make
that connection.
>> I was going to
ask, what kind of cat?
>> It's a Nordic Forest cat.
They're pretty big.
They have long fur, a
little bit longer snout,
cute head, so pretty big.
And it jumped on
the table with me.
And it laid down
next to my feet.
And it was just there
rolled up and purring.
And then she started channeling
Arjun for me, who said,
you know, you're ready from head
to toe to do this kind of work
yourself if you want to
because we have this agreement.
And then he started
explaining that he is Yahyel.
And I started to
understand, oh, wow.
Or she got it through.
She translated it as she
thought his name was Shayel
because maybe she didn't
know about the race,
so this was funny.
But at least, it gave
me the synchronicity
to understand that what happened
a month earlier was actually
not my imagination.
And I felt a lot of
things happening.
It was like I was
floating off the table.
I was really buzzing.
And they were giving me all
this specific information
about my childhood, how
they'd visited me before.
And everything started to
come together all of a sudden,
very quickly.
It took me about three days to
get used to the entire idea.
And then, as a
life coach by then,
I picked out some
open-minded clients.
And I said, so are you
up for an experiment?
and I started to see what
would come through
and that was an enormous
journey for me and
it really sped up the entire
process and
now here I am...
>>>Very good.
>>It took over the practice
basically
the effects were so strong
that the normal life coaching
in a sense just
within 4 months.
>> Tell us a little bit about
your art and how that was
an influence in maybe
transitioning to where you are
now.
How did that come about?
>> I think it was always there.
>> Because I've
seen many of your--
a lot of your art incorporates
extraterrestrial themes.
And when did that start?
Just from when you
were very little?
>> I have some childhood
drawings in which I'm already
attempting at that age to draw
the classrooms and where I
believe I went--
what I call astral
school, where I
got the lessons about
universe and how things work.
I would make drawings
of birds with the sky
inside the bird instead of
the bird inside the sky.
Because everything was a loop.
And I got that.
And I have these drawings.
And I made them at
age four or five.
And I'm so surprised.
I actually rediscovered
these drawings--
I thought they were gone--
only three years ago.
And I'm like, wow.
A lot of stuff is also being
thrown out, kids stuff,
but this is still there.
And it's always been my
outlet for translating
what was coming in.
So in my diaries as a
teenager, starting 12,
I was also making diagrams
of how I understood
the cosmos looked like.
And I was having
questions like, there
must be an edge to
this whole universe,
so what is outside of that?
And then intuitively
understanding
that the more you go outside,
it must look the same
as when you go really inside.
And then going into research
biology and fractals--
and I was doing that
for fun at age 17,
getting books from the library
just because I felt drawn
to this kind of information.
But it made no sense at all,
not even for my profession
as an artist.
You don't have to necessarily
read, for instance, philosophy
also.
I was really into
Nietzsche and Jung.
And I wanted to understand
how the mind works.
And then I discovered--
>> Well, there's a lot of
artists out there that explore
those themes.
>> Yes.
It is very intuitive.
It is another language.
>> Is it Da--
I don't know, my appreciation
for art is there,
but I forget everybody's names.
But is it the guy who writes
the melting clocks all the time?
>> Salvador Dali?
>> Yes, Dali, that's right.
And then is that
the same guy that
does those weird dimensional
drawings like the stairs going
this way and--
>> Escher.
>> That's Escher, yes, great.
So these guys, I think,
they're probably--
>> I was obsessed by that.
But I really do feel it's
one of the languages that's
very close to the
interstellar speech.
Plus is music, by the
way, and even movement.
Yes, sound, movement,
and visuals.
And if you really
dive into that,
yes, I think it's
maybe only logical
that you end up wanting to
know more about philosophy
and how things work.
But I was a bit nerdy in that.
I would really go for the books
and dive into the websites,
and go explore, and
feel that it makes
sense, and wanting
to do something
with that information.
I don't think all artists
necessarily have that.
>> Well, we really are entering
this time in humanity where we
can grasp these concepts.
We sort of had hints of
it throughout our history
with the art.
But now with science going into
the quantum fields and quantum
theory, we're doing
experiments in those realms.
We're really starting to
figure out the universe.
>> I love it.
>> And I was just posting
an article yesterday,
these experiments of how the
present can change the past.
And we can see this in photons.
And this experiment's been
repeated over and over.
And they call it the eraser
effect, where what we can do
here now can actually
literally change the past.
And we've known from these
channeling works and art
and everything else that the
only thing that really exists
is the now anyways.
So I find it fascinating
that it's all interconnected.
>> Me too.
>> And it's great that you
subconsciously tapped into that
at a young age.
>> Yeah.
And that you can change
the past from the present,
I got that very clearly at
age 26, around and about.
And I started rewriting
my childhood literally.
I made a new diary.
Like I piled up all the old
ones and I made a new one.
I tore out all the
drawings and I threw away
most of the writings.
I kept the dreams, by the way.
It's like this is
what I want to keep.
And these stories
where I was venting,
that timeline of my childhood,
I let go of very deliberately.
I was like, OK, this is a part--
I want to switch to
another timeline.
So I started to rewrite it,
and that was so powerful.
And it's through this
kind of playing around
with the information that I got
for myself that I eventually
ended up discovering techniques
like tapping and using
that as a life coach.
Because I had experienced
in my own life
how powerful these
techniques are and how
you can really use them.
>> And essentially, from
my understanding now,
because I've worked with
tapping and plant medicine work,
we're essentially going
into these quantum states
and rewriting the story,
shifting timelines per se.
>> On a cellular level,
actually opening up--
there's these little portals,
in a sense, in your body.
So when I do the
private sessions,
I get to see these details.
And I want to actually
see if I can make
Photoshop examples of that.
>> Well, there's a great video--
I post this all the
time-- out there,
this YouTube channel called
Upriser, what's his name?
I forgot the guy's name.
But he goes into explaining
how DNA in itself
is sort of a dimensional
doorway for bringing
through information
from another dimension.
Gravity as well,
but really the DNA
strands and how they
work in the molecules,
with hydrogen within water--
you know, two hydrogens
and one oxygen molecule--
creating portals to bring
through information.
Like gravity, it's all
interconnected into science.
And we're now merging these
worlds of art, philosophy,
science.
And I think quantum physics
is that mechanism we have now
that really is like, yeah,
this is how the universe works.
And I think our space brothers
and sisters are like, yeah,
they're finally getting it.
>> Yes, they are.
But they're also
so super patient
with those who don't yet.
I love that.
There's so much love, wow.
It blows me away continuously.
>> So what's next?
What's your plan with
this tool of channeling?
Where are you going with it?
What do you want to do?
>> Oh, that's a funny question.
I never really think
into the future
that much because I think
that's really weird.
I mean, I almost feel my brain
cramp up trying to do that.
That never worked for me.
So I don't think ahead.
>> So you're sort of living
the Yahyel philosophy--
>> Already, yeah.
>> --of synchronicities
and living in the moment.
>> Let's see what
happens, totally.
Planning ahead really
never worked for me.
This is why as a
child at school,
I was already having issues with
the way they see the future.
This is what you're going to
do, and then logically, you
would go to m-m-m.
So I'm still not planning
anything, only like loosely.
Like OK, I feel it's time
to move maybe location,
so I'll move to a
more foresty location.
That's a plan that
I have right now.
But there's no stress on
it, there's no deadline.
And I know it will come to me.
The house is basically
already there.
I just have to discover it in
a here and now timeline, which
will be there eventually.
So the channeling also is
teaching me to surrender
even more to the here and now.
Because it's such a here
and now state to be in,
there's nothing else, everything
else disappears for me.
>> In the channeling state.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, many channelers
these days don't go into that
deep trance so much.
Are you present and aware?
>> I'm present, but I'm moving
in and out of the amount
of presence, I guess.
I can move it to the back
a little more and kind of
lose track of where
things are going.
But I'll still get a hint, OK,
now this dialogue is finished,
we've gone to the next.
And then I wake up again, pay
attention to new storyline.
And I have to be more present
when I'm doing it in English,
as it's my second language.
In Dutch, in my first language,
I can drift a little bit more.
>> Go on autopilot.
>> Yeah, a little more.
But it's in and out.
And if they increase the tempo,
I'm more on one word at a time,
translating one word
at a time, instead of--
I've had moments where I don't
know where the sentence is
going at all, just focusing
on the correct pronunciation
of every word.
But I'm still conscious.
>> And then do you surprise
yourself when you go in those
one word at a time moments, and
then afterwards, you're like,
oh, I actually made
a full sentence?
>> Yes, I do.
I'm like, wow.
>> People understood
what I said.
>> This actually went somewhere.
Yes, I have these moments.
Sometimes the sentences are--
you know, if you
would read them,
they have 12 commas in them.
Like, whoa, where is
this ever going to end?
And then it still makes sense.
I love that.
>> Yeah, since
starting the series,
and investigating channeling
and going into it,
and having my own
channeling experiences,
I have the same thing.
I've channeled information,
and in my mind, I'm like,
this is not going to
make any sense at all.
>> Exactly.
>> It's gibberish,
what is this--
in the moment that
you're doing it,
because it's more of a feeling.
You're just like, OK, I get
it, but the rest of the world,
they can't get this.
And then you go back
and you review it,
and you're like,
holy smokes, it's
actually using
semi-correct grammar even.
And you're like, wow,
that's incredible.
>> Recognizable.
>> So for all those watching out
there, this channeling stuff,
there's something to it.
Yeah, it's funny how
sometimes I have conversations
with people who aren't familiar
with what channeling is.
And they think
it's just a big act.
And I'm like, no, you can't.
I mean, there are
actors who channel.
You know, I think
actors do channel.
>> It's a form of channeling.
>> When you get into that
state, it just comes naturally.
And the better ones,
the better actors
do get into that
channeling state.
But to make it up--
and I guess we are making
it up as we go along.
But it's the ultimate improv-- right?
>> Yeah.
>> --where you're just
completely surrender and just
whatever comes out.
But the information
that's coming out
was not scripted and not
pre-learned dialogue.
It just comes out, and
it's quite phenomenal.
>> And that's why, I think,
I felt so pulled towards
meditation and
emptying the mind out.
I fell in love with
that very young,
so I started practicing
that and then the chanting,
was a Buddhist for a while.
And then at some
point, Arjun just
stepped forward and let
me know, OK, you're ready,
let's do this if you want.
It's full surrender.
>> I'm so glad you have chosen
this path to do this and share
the information and bring
forth these beings that we can
hopefully soon, sooner than
later, meet face to face,
in a physical interaction.
>> Who knows.
>> But in the meantime, we
have this wonderful gift.
>> Yes.
>> And thank you for bringing
this out and sharing it.
>> Thank you for sharing it
in this way with the world--
>> This is my channel
with the cameras.
>> --on an even bigger platform.
Yes, it all intertwines.
I love it.
>> Well, we'll get into some
channeling then and see where
it goes from there.
>> Yes, OK.
>> Awesome.
Thank you.
>> Thank you.
[MUSIC PLAYING]