It is the idea of many of
our species...
What we would say in
other star systems
coming into understanding
that there is a balance
and so we allow all to
happen the way it is
and to interact the way it will be.
Otherwise we ourselves
cannot expand if we do not
understand one another's
perspectives.
We, or the Anunnaki
the creators, are expanding
in just the same as
human consciousness is,
and that was previously misunderstood.
Living in
this third density has been
beneficial for your learning
because now you can
become the teachers,
and expand even more fully
into the source energy
that we are all trying to
what you might say
make sense of
or understand within
our hearts.
Because you see that
there is a paradigm
allowed here on Earth,
or a sort of "Game Shift",
you understand
perhaps the mindsets
that can trap you into
that space.
There are others elsewhere
that have fairly similar mindsets,
perhaps you can be their guides
and teach them ways to expand
past what you call "The Matrix"
to "The Game Playing"
but how would you know
if you hadn't had some of
that in your perspective?
Ever wonder if there's intelligent
life elsewhere in the universe?
Well, I have....I've been wondering since I was a kid.
My name is Reuben Langdon.
And on March 29th 2007, in the middle of the day,
I saw a number of strange objects in the sky.
Coincidentally, I was working on
the film Avatar at the time, playing an alien.
And ever since then I've been on a quest...
A quest to find out if aliens really do exist and if so...
...are they here with us?
If beings of higher intelligence are here...
...what is their purpose?
Why don't they make themselves more known?
Why the secrecy?
I've asked these questions to many experts,
yet each seems to have a different theory.
So I thought to myself,
why not ask the aliens directly?
So that's what I set out to do!
Well, sort of...
>> OK.
So I have a few visuals.
I feel like my strongest one
is a woman from the council,
as well as, I would
say, an insectoid.
>> OK.
>> I would say Gray,
but it's tall, skinny,
and it has more
of antenna-style,
instead of a human face,
if that makes sense.
>> Mm-hm.
Maybe closer to a Mantis?
>> Yeah, similar to
that type of breed,
or if that's what you call it?
So depending on
the question, those
are the two collectives
that want to answer.
OK, so depending on how
far back or what question,
the Draco also wants to respond.
He says, most particularly, if
he references the shift over,
which-- what we
were talking about,
when the beings came
in and basically took
over our consciousness, he knows
a lot about that time period.
>> OK.
Well, let's start with Atlantis.
>> And I hate to put
a timeline on things,
but I'm guessing around
25,000 years ago?
>> OK.
OK, so the woman says further
back than that, my love,
but yes.
A very special
time period indeed.
What is it that you
would like to know?
>> Is that-- because I've heard
from other channels and other
guides that humanity
carries a lot of trauma from
the Atlantean periods.
So I guess my
question would be, is
much of what we're dealing
with on the planet now,
is it tied into the
Atlantean energy?
>> She says, I'm not sure
if I would call it traumas,
though it does take some healing
to transform what has been
learned during this time
period and where you are moving
toward.
She says, you see, during
the Atlantean time period,
consciousness had
grown exponentially
and experiments
were taking place.
And yes, humanity as
well as other species
had to learn that this is not
how expansion was to occur
in the most beneficial way.
So those that
understood this opted
into a alternative experience--
an experience where
they could learn
in a slightly different way.
So you may call it
traumatic in the sense
that what once was known
was erased or taken,
but we would also like to
call it a teaching or learning
opportunity for the expansion of
humanity that they opted into.
>> Was the Annunaki
DNA injection,
was that prior or after
the Atlantean experience?
In our linear sense of time.
>> She says, right prior to
the diluvian time period with
the Annunaki, but there seems
to be a disconnect with what
she's showing me.
I'm seeing if she
can use verbals.
Basically, there seemed to be
an Atlantean time period further
back from when the
Annunaki actually came
and created their hybrid human.
And then she's showing me
that, with the diluvian waters,
they erased all of this.
But some Annunaki saved
some of the humanoid
to carry on that genetic
map that they created.
>> When you say "diluvian," can
you go into more detail about
that?
What does that mean?
>> She says the great flood
that we have known to be called
the great flood.
She says, this is a common
misconception in understanding
the human evolution,
because there were humanoids
in the Atlantean
time period, but we
would suggest that they were
more 5th dimensional beings.
They were not essentially
what the human is today.
That human is the
creation of what
the Annunaki created right prior
to this diluvian time period.
>> But the Annunaki borrowed
some DNA from that time period,
or from that energy?
Or is that just, I guess, the
Atlantean karma that we're
dealing with, is that just more
energetic as opposed to DNA?
>> OK.
That's a good question.
She says, with reference
to your question,
I would say that this
is more energetic.
It is a consciousness that
was tampered with in order
to bring in the
consciousness of a humanoid.
She says, once again, the
Atlanteans were, she says,
like a type of human species.
But they-- she's saying they're
not what you exactly think,
and I'm asking her if she can be
more specific with the details
of how this all occurred.
She says, basically, it's a
different type of humanoid.
It's a higher-evolved human
conscience that was there.
It's different than what
the Annunaki created.
>> Is it a mixture
of different beings?
Where there Pleiadians,
and Mantoids, and--
>> She says yes.
>> --Lyrans, and they were
all just having a big party?
>> She says yes, but there
were also very select that had
a specific type of DNA.
But then things started to get
mixed in an experimental way,
she says, not in
necessarily a mating way.
The Annunaki efforts
evolved into a mating
energetic manipulation
of the DNA.
>> So did the Annunaki
come after the Atlantean
destruction?
Was this great diluvian
flood, was that a reaction
to the Atlantean experimentation
in technology and energy?
>> She's saying we think the
Atlantean happened before
as far as linear time period
compared to when the Annunaki
came and actually
manipulated the human DNA.
And there seems to be a
disconnect with the human in
Atlantean time period
versus the human
that the Annunaki created.
There's a little bit different--
>> Energy?
>> --energy, and the dimensional
frequency that that human is
capable of being a part of.
>> What density was the Atlantean
experience?
>> OK.
She says it's the fifth
dimension, fourth density.
>> OK.
>> She's saying, part of the
confusion could be the shifting
of the Earth, and the
part of waters rising.
She's saying that
the flood that we're
speaking of, the deluge
right after the Annunaki
manipulated the human genome--
>> Oh, this is a second flood.
>> There seems to be
different floodings.
The great deluge, she's
saying, was intentional.
The flood that took out
Atlantis, she's saying,
was a shifting of the planet.
And then there was another
shifting later down the road,
after the deluge,
if that makes sense.
>> Yeah.
>> She's just basically
apologizing for the timelines
of trying to construct in our
minds how it all played out.
But she understands it
with the evolution of how
the Earth has cycled through.
She's saying that there
were other things that
happened during the
Atlantean time period that
took the destruction.
Chemical warfare, wars.
The waters could be
manipulated, but they
weren't used for this
specific purpose as they
were in the deluge
that we speak of,
the great flooding that was
meant to wipe out and reset
the human species.
>> She says, in a linear format,
it would be Atlantean time
period in a fifth-dimensional
state with wars of chemicals,
experimentation,
and these sorts.
And the Earth changed
and shifted accordingly.
And the waters rose, and even
the land shifted and changed.
And then we could say that, for
some time, Earth was desolate.
And that's when
the Annunaki came.
And they created the humanoid
based on their needs.
And she says things began
to spiral out of control,
in a sense, where they were
repeating the Atlantean time
period with their
experimentation,
and understood
that now they would
have to deal with the
energy accordingly,
and created a flooding
to reset the species.
>> Mm-hm.
So the Annunaki actually
created the flood.
>> She says yes.
>> Was this coming from
the higher-ups because they
So were they ordered
to do the flood?
>> She says they didn't--
it was not an order.
They felt that a
reset was necessary
in order to undo the karmic
energy that they had done.
She's bringing me back to
Atlantis, which is telling me
that they understood
that the energy that
was created in Atlantis with
the experimentation led to--
I don't want, if you say bad
karma, or a learning curve.
They didn't want to do
that, so they decided,
let's reset everything, and
let's just make it right.
And so they created
this flooding area.
OK, sorry.
She's doing a lot more
visuals than verbals.
She's showing me, though,
that many were actually
sent away from where the
flood was to preserve.
But they also felt like they
were getting outnumbered,
in a sense, and were
trying to just select
a few of the genomes that
they wanted to preserve.
She says it basically, in
their minds, was a reset
so they wouldn't have to do
some of the energetic balance
that Atlantis had to
come face to face with.
>> But it still sounds like
we're repeating ourselves over
and over again.
>> Yeah.
She says it's been very--
she says karmic.
It's been very karmic.
>> It sounds almost
like "Groundhog Day."
>> She says you cannot create
a species and say, oh, no,
what have I done?
Let's reset.
She says, you cannot do this.
And so the creators-- the
Annunaki that you call them--
have had to go through their
own set of learning processes
to redo the human species,
and not in the way
that they had previously planned
in annihilating the genome.
They must help them into
higher consciousness.
>> So they're our guides now.
>> She says, many have stepped
forward to try to help.
>> Mm-hm.
Does the Annunaki civilization
that came initially
to create this species,
does that still
exist in a fourth density,
or in a physical form?
Fourth or fifth?
>> She says, not in the way
that you would understand.
It has surpassed.
They have, she says, tried
to help in many instances.
And they have evolved to be
more light beings, in a sense.
They have stood by
humanity on a larger scale,
and have tried to help.
And for this, they
have evolved greatly.
We would say that they
are further in dimension
than what you speak of.
>>Almost a collective?
>> She says yes, but they still
desire to help humanity evolve
because of the karmic cycle
that had been created.
Because their greatest
desire is expansion as well.
>> It's been said that we have
DNA from various species--
Pleiadian, Reptilian, Lyran.
I'm sure there's many more.
Even Arcturian, and-- are all
of these different types of DNA
mixed in into the
Annunaki DNA already?
Is that where we get it from?
Or did they take
from these other--
>> She says they didn't take.
Borrowed for other trades.
Their DNA is not 100% your DNA.
Your DNA is unique
in the fact that it
comes from all
different star systems.
And they knew that in order to
create the perfect humanoid,
they needed to do this.
>> What was their goal?
I keep hearing it sounds like it
was more complicated than just
to create a species
to mine their gold.
>> She's saying
conquering other worlds.
I'm asking her to clarify
what she means by that.
Being able to
inhabit this world,
and to conquer it,
and move on to others,
it is almost like having
children and letting
them rule the planet.
She says it wasn't
meant to be negative.
It's just to have a planet--
a dominionship, and then to move
forward into other planetary
regions, and to rule that.
>> It sounds almost Reptilian.
Is that consciousness
prevalent in the Anunnaki?
>> She's smiling.
She says, it's not only Reptilian,
but yes, you are correct.
The Anunnaki are very--
kinship?
Very ruling-ship type.
And they create
and procreate based
on the fact that they can
pass down to their family,
she says, like, regions.
>> Heirs.
Heirs to the kingdom.
>> Yeah, in regions.
And in this case,
it was a planet.
>> Mm-hm.
>>It sounds--
because that still
has a hierarchy-type,
ownership-type energy to it.
It sounds like
maybe the Anunnaki
have moved beyond that now?
>> She says we believe
that they have.
They are working hard
to undo the mindsets
and the consciousness that
are now unbeneficial to you
that they have created.
She says, you do see yourselves
often as hierarchical beings,
and have organized
your world accordingly.
This comes from the Anunnaki,
and they understand this,
and they are working
to unfold this.
She says, but there
are benefits to having
a hierarchical system, and
they understand this as well.
The key is to maintain
that we are all unified,
and we all have our special
role within God source energy.
It sounds like, maybe because we
have this Anunnaki hierarchical
energy, that maybe
we were open to--
...to inviting a Reptilian
energy at some point.
>> She says you are very
correct in believing this.
The Reptilians have a very
compassionless perspective,
and so their idea
is to dominate.
But keep in mind that
the Anunnaki as a whole
is not just Reptilian.
They are-- she's saying
a unique species.
I'm asking her to pinpoint
if I can get a region.
>> Sounds almost Orion.
>> I'm getting like a
conglomerate of maybe just--
I feel like there are
Reptilian in this region,
and also, like, blondes.
>> Pleiadians.
>> Yeah.
And I feel like they're
working together,
and that's who we
call the Annunaki.
And I even feel like there's
Insectoids involved with this.
So we have Reptilian,
Insectoids, and the Humanoid,
or the Pleiades part of Orion
being the Anunnaki creators.
>> What are the Insectoids'
roles in this mix?
>> Donating DNA.
They helped with
constructing the genome.
They help with
intuitive abilities.
The empathic and intuitive
side of the human
comes from the Insectoids.
The survival skills often
come from the Reptoids.
And being able to, she says
survive under harsh conditions,
these type of things.
You need these things.
Even though they can
often feel dense,
you need the DNA from
these type of species.
She's bringing me back to
part of the question earlier
that we spoke of, the Reptoids.
>> When did they come in?
At what point in
our history did we
allow that energy to come in?
>> OK.
OK, so she wants to talk
about the hierarchy,
because that helps
understand it.
She's saying that all these
beings understand hierarchy.
It's not just the Reptoid.
Even the Pleiades
understand that there
must be some type of
hierarchical collaboration
formed in order for order--
>> Structure.
>> Yeah.
She says it's not saying
that others are greater
or others are lesser.
It's just the way to
keep organization.
She says, now, that
being said, if the higher
look down upon the lower
as lesser, and the lesser
feel that they are lesser, that
is when the domination occurs
and the consciousness can shift.
But let me talk
about timeline first,
and then I can
explain to you some
of the other beings behind
the agendas that-- what
you would call Reptilian.
>> Mm-hm.
>> She says, let's call
them the serpent species.
>> Yes.
OK.
>> But this doesn't necessarily
mean that they are Reptoid
in nature.
It means that they are of
the serpent star system.
I'm asking her if it's
like that Alpha Draconis.
>> Right.
>> She says yes, but
it's also bigger.
Something that the
ancients knew of.
They called it the serpent
star system, basically.
And there was a serpent
species because they
came from that location.
I'm asking her to give
me a linear time of when
the consciousness transitioned.
And she's just showing
me a lot of dragon stuff,
and I'm not understanding.
Let's see if I can get
her to give me numbers.
She's not giving me a time
period of when consciousness
really changed.
I feel like it might
be such a slow process
that it's hard to give a date.
>> Sure, sure.
Was the Annunaki intervention
pre-dinosaur era, or after?
>> I want to say pre.
>> She says, but it also
depends on the regions.
Some regions didn't
inhabit the beings--
and she's referring
to the dinosaurs--
for quite some time.
And even then, more humans
were able to occupy the area,
or land dominated species.
>> Mm-hm.
So were dinosaurs more of
human's natural evolution?
Or was their
genetic manipulation
with the dinosaurs
coming to Earth?
>> OK, I'm asking
her to slow down.
There was some natural evolution
process with the dinosaur
species, but it basically
was put forth on the surface
to start as a testing point
to see what type of species
could survive, what
type of evolution
would occur on its own,
what type of things
need to tampering in order to
survive these type of things.
She says, and this is why
we say that time periods are
difficult, because there were
areas where dinosaurs were only
able to survive for a brief
time, other places where they
were able to survive
and thrive quite freely.
And so the areas and the regions
helped dictate the time period,
as well as where
humans were able to go.
>> Mm-hm.
And I assume that's the
same for humans too.
Different pockets of
humans, different areas,
could survive longer.
>> She says yes.
That's very good to think that,
because in different regions,
your genetic genome
needed certain, she says--
I might call it upgrades in
order for you to survive.
In order for you to
think, or to have
the ability within your body
to survive longer than needed.
>> Mm-hm.
So getting back to the
Atlantean Annunaki karma,
then the dinosaur karma,
is it true, as our
scientists are figuring out,
that an asteroid created
the extinction event
on planet Earth, the
reset for the dinosaurs?
>> She says, we think that
they are on the right path.
Obviously, there is a
little bit more to it.
There were chemicals
that were set forth
to create fires and erosion--
I feel like maybe that
could be earthquakes--
>> OK.
>> --in order to
offset the species.
>> To reset things a little bit?
>> With the dinosaurs
specifically is what
she's showing me.
I feel like there's a
couple different times when
this happened, based on
what she's showing me.
>> So maybe more than
one extinction event.
>> Yes.
And this one doesn't
seem to do with water.
It seems to do more
with gases and fire.
There's a lot of burning
around the regions
that she's showing
me, and earthquakes.
>> And I understand that
all this is for different
evolution--
for the evolution of various
species, and animals, plants,
humanoids, dinosaurs, et cetera.
Why does the Earth itself
need to have all this stuff
going on?
What is it getting
out of all this?
>> She's saying that it just has
to go through its own planetary
cycle, just as a cell
would gain expansion,
or she says maybe what
you would call evolution,
through going through
a little bit of stress.
Strain and division,
these kind of things,
it's just part of the way
she says the universe works.
>> Sure.
>> It isn't to hurt
Gaia, she says.
It's to help it
transition, and to reach
into higher consciousness.
Many of other
planets do the same.
>> Mm-hm.
Just to go back to our history
a little bit more, then,
and the different energies
and beings. These other races,
this borrowed DNA that we
were created from, did they--
I'm assuming they also
signed up for that.
Loaning their DNA.
What was their intention?
What were, say, the Pleiades'
intention, and Reptilians,
at that time?
Or Zeta.
Do we have Zeta DNA?
>> She's saying no, not
the Annunaki creation.
Perhaps in a roundabout
way, as Zeta DNA
can be shared in a roundabout
way with other species.
But you have not
been transplanted
with their direct DNA.
But there had been
multiple experimentations
on the Zetas' part prior to
the Annunaki taking control.
>> Oh, interesting.
>> She says, to answer
the question about the DNA
exchange, they were all to be
a part of the interactions,
and all to share it, and have
their regions accordingly to--
she says maybe what
you call family.
For example, let's say that
a family from the Pleiades
had a region to
control and dominate
on the Earth's surface.
And a Reptilian
would have an area.
She says the Insectoids that we
speak of, they were mixed in.
There was a mixture.
They were in agreement
to divide, dominate,
and to be in their regions.
And this also remains still up
into the galaxies as well as
Earth.
It was a contract for,
she says, like the souls.
They agreed upon it.
There was no good or bad.
There was just-- she says it
was almost like a big family.
>> Mm-hm.
So to create a place,
a meeting ground
to mix the energy so we
can get along better.
>> Yeah, well,
what's the intent?
The intent, she says, to create.
>> Just to create.
>> Just to be godlike,
to create something.
But they needed other DNA.
They couldn't do it
solely with one DNA
on the surface of Earth.
It wasn't applicable.
>> So the Earth environment
itself is pretty unique, then,
in the galaxy?
>> She says, in
this instance, yes.
They needed multiple
types of DNA.
Even mammalian.
Mammalian was used.
But it was understood
that only--
she's showing me leaders.
That there would only
be a certain group
of leaders for this.
So they did the
exchange accordingly.
She's saying that part
of also the exchange
was for the leaders
to not inhibit
certain parts of the planet if
they could exchange the DNA,
and they would be protected, if
that makes sense, in regions.
>> The regions
would be protected.
>> Yeah.
>> Right.
>> I feel like I-- she's
showing me a lot of dolphins
and mammalians in the waters.
They were not to dominate
the waters in the way
that they did the land.
And for that, they
could exchange DNA.
So there were these
contracts and agreements.
>> So that would be
the Sirian energy?
>> She says yes.
>> OK.
So where are we
going with all this?
[CHUCKLES]
What's next?
>> So why is this so important?
>> Why is it so important that
we have this galactic soup here
on Earth?
>> She says, well, for one case,
for one thing that we really
want to drive home, so to
speak, in the human species
consciousness is to understand
there's no good and evil.
The serpent species
has been termed
as the evil, the
benevolent, the Pleiades,
and they have been
working together.
She says, but what you have
are individual consciousness,
perhaps, or beings
that individually
selected to dominate
in an unbeneficial way.
>> And they get blamed for--
>> She says yes.
Basically to-- she
says, we want to go back
to the serpent
species, because we
have spoken that they
are not all Reptilian.
The serpent species
also has beings
that have used the domination
for evil purposes, quote
unquote, she says, to
take over consciousness.
But they don't
look like reptiles.
So basically, we've
pinned the reptile
as the bad, the benevolent
blondes as the god good.
>> Of course, because
that's what we look like.
>> Yeah.
>> [CHUCKLING] We're
good, you're bad.
Anything that looks different.
>> But I almost feel like
they were good, so to speak.
They were trying
to be creator gods.
And other species from
the serpent species
used that power to dominate
the human consciousness,
if that makes sense.
Using an archetype is
only going back so far.
It sounds like there's more to
the story than just archetypes.
>> She says yes.
Consider once again the
part of your question
where you brought
in the dinosaurs.
They are survival,
but their DNA is
key in the planetary creation.
And so when you
consider this, you
consider that the human
is a large part of this,
so to hate them would
be to hate yourself.
>> Absolutely.
>> She's saying, also consider
what we speak of the serpent
species.
And also, when you
do your research,
go back and find that there is
serpent species, serpent race,
these type of callings--
names.
She says, see if you can't
tap in and see the visuals,
and see that not all
are actually reptiles.
Some look, she says,
more mammalian.
All kinds.
All kinds, she says.
Even some bird.
>> Yeah.
>> They represent the Reptilian
agenda that you now reference
in today's timeline, though.
The conquering the
human consciousness.
And so when you hear Reptilian,
this is what you think of.
When you hear
serpent, you think,
oh, the Reptilian domination.
But the serpent species is
actually a broader idea.
>> Well, we do know,
in our own evolution,
how birds are linked to
the Reptilian energy.
The Avians are quite
close in the family.
But my understanding
is that the Pleiadians
have a lot of that
energy already
as well-- the bird energy, or.
>> She says they do.
They do.
And remember, they
work together.
They understand one another.
OK, so she's showing
me some visuals
of the Pleiades actually
having large families.
They sort of--
I'm getting spacey because--
OK, she's trying to
get through to me.
Hold on.
>> Mm-hm.
>> They were the first advocates
of one male, several females,
because they understood the
lineage and the importance
of carrying on down
the bloodlines.
This came from your
Orion star system,
but it has turned into
something negative.
But that which you call God
came from this sort of idea
that lineage could be carried
down through the bloodlines
and to--
>> Can you back up and
explain that what we call God?
You mean the male figure of God?
>> Yes.
>> OK.
Basically, she says,
like, Abrahamic covenant.
>> OK.
That idea of God,
the image of God,
she's saying that she
just wants humanity
to understand that there
are beings of Orion that
have a very male dominant
type of energy that
have brought that to Earth.
The rulingship of
the man, basically,
and passing it down through
the bloodlines into the males.
She says, mainly,
though, because also,
a man can have several
children with different wives
and pass his seed along to
ensure that his kingdom would
be maintained accordingly.
And he can pass down his
lineage and his ideas that way.
But that comes from not
necessarily Reptilian.
She's saying, that's
an Orion energy.
She says, not saying that
we live like that here.
We're just saying that that
was incorporated with that idea
from us, from the Orion.
>> It was part of our DNA.
>> Yeah.
>> That we carry that energy.
And I guess we're
working through that.
And it's not serving
us anymore, so we're
evolving past that now, or--
some of us.
[CHUCKLES]
>> She says you're moving
past the rulingship.
There is still the idea behind a
man being able to have children
from several other wives
that can also be beneficial
because we are still
mammalian, in a large sense,
and we are working
toward building
more of the community
based on that idea.
She's saying, but
it also all goes
back to your original
concerns and questions
with the Reptilian
and the rulingship
now, that the rulers and the
kings and the queens, that
is a Reptilian idea.
She says it's not necessarily--
>> OK.
Yeah, I understand
now what she's
trying to convey, as far as, I
had this concept of hierarchy
and ruling being
a Reptilian idea.
And sounds like that's--
there's some aspects of that
in the Reptilian lineage,
but that's not a
Reptilian, so to say--
that aspect particularly isn't
just from the Reptilians.
>> But my understanding of that
Reptilian archetype as a very
male, masculine energy.
And then I've also understood
that the Pleiadians
has been more of a
feminine, a softer energy.
And the merging of the two,
the Annunaki, and then us,
creating, adding extra
spices in there, it seems.
>> She says, that is true.
One thing to note, though,
is that the male side
in the Pleiade region
is more like a mentor--
teacher.
And that can take on
that feminine side,
but also understands
the male role.
The feminine side of
the Reptilian, she says,
is gaining wisdom and
working that into knowledge
with teaching the youth.
Those type of things.
Creating a better lifestyle for
communities with technology,
and that kind of
business, she says.
So there is a little bit
of both that is different.
But we have interpreted the male
energy is dominant, and maybe
perhaps controlling, because
that is what the humans have
perceived it to be for so long.
>> It's what we
experienced here.
Or at least our history and
what we remember so far.
So I'm assuming as we
uncover our history,
we can break free of some
of these stereotypes of what
a male is, what a female is.
>> She says yes.
She says, one more thing to
add is the serpent species
as we spoke of-- or
Reptilians-- don't
tend to hide the
masculinity in that sense.
The Orion side, they
understand that,
and they allow it to occur.
But they also know how to--
she says mask it in a sense
with their ability to teach.
But there still is a
bit of a masculine side
that they incorporate,
or have incorporated
into the human experience.
>> Again, where we're going with
all this, getting back to that,
it seems like humans
are going to have--
maybe not the way the Annunaki
had originally intended,
but we still are going to have a
strong presence in this galaxy.
>> She says yes.
That is key to, say,
teaching, because you
have entered into the 3D world
that has benefited you greatly
in understanding and learning
in a subconscious way.
And now that you are fully
awakening and becoming
conscious, you now can
become the teachers
and allowing others to
understand their full capacity.
So in a sense, it has been
very beneficial for you
to experience the world
in the way that you have.
It has been-- she
says, what we have
called an excellent
simulation of learning.
>> Mm.
And these other races
that are part of us that
are observing humanity
now, and have been,
I'm assuming they're
learning a lot just
by the observation process.
>> She says yes.
Yes.
They've realized a
lot of their mistakes
because of how we've dealt
with what they've taught us.
And they have evolved
because of it,
because they are working
to undo some of this,
and expanding themselves
into other areas of thinking.
She says, initially,
it was done to protect
the human race, the human
species, the DNA that
was created, these type
of things, and to let you
have the best life possible.
But of course, things
transpired the way
they did, where beings
took over consciousness.
And they see both perspectives.
And that is important
in expansion.
>> When you say beings
took over consciousness,
is this the integration of the
downgrade into third density?
>> Yes.
She says it's back into the
serpent race, which is not
necessarily the serpent,
but beings that wanted
to take over consciousness.
And then now you have lower
dimensional Reptilians that--
she says, and others.
She didn't want me
to limit it to that.
But others that like to maintain
control over the consciousness.
>> And because of
the energy where
we're at in our evolution, that
was sort of an easy gateway
into that?
>> She says yes.
They understood the
cycle of the planet.
They understood
that when the planet
cycled in a particular way,
that it opened a gateway--
as you spoke of-- to enter
into lower consciousness.
And the Annunaki and
higher beings of dimensions
were forced to leave
because they could not
re-enter in the same way
that they w-- they were not
able to appear to humans
like they had before,
and guide them.
Everything was subconscious,
she said, at that point.
>> So almost like
getting contact now,
for many of us who are
having dream experiences.
When things become
too dense, then that's
really the only gateway in.
Where, maybe on some
parts of the Earth,
where the actual physical
area is in a higher frequency,
then those can be gateways of--
doorways in for higher
dimensional beings, physically.
>> She says yes.
And also consider, there
were several attempts
before this transition, while
we were making contact with you
with the humans to
try to pull them out
of this sort of mindset
that they were getting taken
or putting a hold on to.
But the humans
wouldn't allow it.
They still worshipped
the gods that
led them into avenues
that were unbeneficial.
They still desired trade and
money over spiritual things
at this point, and we
could not reach them.
She says, so we were asked to
leave by the consciousness,
basically.
>> So it was our own doing.
Wasn't an outside source.
I mean, it wasn't out--
>> She says, in a sense, but you
had helped to push you along.
You had the choice
all along, though.
>> Sure.
Do we always have-- we always
have that choice initially,
don't we?
>> She says yes, but it can
be very, very difficult.
>> But now, it
seems the choice--
that doorway has come
to us again, and now--
at least the timeline
I choose to be in,
it seems that we are
making that choice
to let in our higher frequency
brothers and sisters come in--
>> She says yes.
>> --and make the shift
the other direction,
because we've--
>> She says many of us are
wanting and hoping to come back
in the same way that we had
that contact with you prior.
And we're hoping
that you remember
that some part of
your consciousness
remembers that you once had had
contact in that similar way,
and that everything was OK.
>> Was the last gateway
for this energy,
was this back in
the Egyptian days?
>> I feel like she's
showing me Rome.
There was a gateway
in Rome, and--
>> In Rome.
OK.
>> Yeah.
I don't know what year's the are,
but I feel like it's further--
so would it be Brutus, I
think, is what she's saying?
Brutus and Augustus, I think.
Which is--
>> By the way, I
totally failed history.
[CHUCKLING]
>> It's like 100 AD.
>> I think I know why I
too, because I was just not
interested.
Now it's interesting.
>> I think, though, based
on other channelings--
I'm just going to step
aside from her for a sec--
Christ consciousness was
one of the last hopes
to try to bring
that out of people
and understand their power.
>> Oh, OK.
I see.
Right.
>> And there was a lot of
ET interaction at the time,
and a lot of beings still
coming as angelic forms.
And then shortly
after that, there
was the close of the gateways,
like you talked about.
>> Right.
And then probably
prior to that would
have been Egyptian days, yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> And what role did the Buddha
energy on the planet take?
Because that was
slightly before Christ,
but after the Egyptian era.
>> She says to bring peace.
Peace within the self.
Connection within the self.
Also a preparation
for what was to come.
To be able to match up to what
not only Christ consciousness,
she says, but the one
last loop to understand
what the human was capable of.
>> Mm-hm.
The one last loop.
Could you--
>> She says like what
we spoke of before.
Before that gateway was closing,
they anticipated the close
shortly after Christ's death.
>> So this was so-- it was like
a pre-dimensional door opening
to prep people to--
>> Mm-hm.
It sounds like it was a
time for peace, and to prep.
>> I see.
>> She says, to help turn
off the program for moments
of time.
>> Mm.
And in the Tibetan
energy, there's
the Buddhist influence now.
But it seems like there's more
ancient stuff going on there
prior to Buddha's influence.
What kind of gateway
are we looking at there?
>> She's just showing me a
lot of visuals with African.
>> Oh, OK.
>> I don't know how
that correlates.
Let me see if I can get
her to just tell me.
There just seems
to be a correlation
with some type of
tribe in Africa
that branched off somehow.
I don't know.
It might be beyond my
library of understanding.
>> Sure.
Recently, we've uncovered the
big temple in Gobekli Tepe.
Turkey, I believe.
Seems to be predating the
Egyptian civilization.
Where did that
civilization go?
>> OK.
OK, so I got a lot
of Grays, actually,
that she's showing me.
There are reptilian-type
beings that she's also
showing me connected.
Very ancient.
The beings that she's showing
me, they almost look also
insectoid.
Let's see if she can give
me any other information
on the temple.
I heard-- she said something
about facilitating compound.
>> Pyramids sit there--
>> That's what she said.
I asked her, what was it for?
What was it?
A facilitating compound.
I feel like they're trying
to build something there.
She's showing me that
these beings are--
OK, so how do I put
this into words?
They are meeting
together at this temple,
and they are
constructing things.
Almost like a meeting place.
Very ancient.
The beings are very ancient.
You said it was pre-Egyptian?
>> Mm-hm.
>> OK, that makes sense.
Let's see if she can give
me anything else about that.
[INDISTINCT WHISPERING]
So facilitating
with the connection
of interdimensional
beings as well.
Basically designed
as almost a loop
to gain clearer connection
for furthering construction
of communities and towns.
A way of life.
Even some mining, she's saying.
It's using for mining.
OK, so she's showing
me that some animals
were brought for
genetic alterations,
genetic assistance.
She says, all kinds of things.
This temple's very old.
I asked if it was a
spaceport of any kind.
She's saying no,
that it was more
of a place of
communication type.
I don't see any
spacecrafts landing.
>> Was the Giza pyramid area,
was that more of a stargate,
in a sense?
>> She says yes.
That's an energy gateway.
>> OK.
Different species coming in,
and going, and doing things.
>> She's saying one
thing different.
The pyramids had to interact
and line up a certain way.
The one that you're
speaking of--
>> Gobekli Tepe.
>> Yeah.
That didn't have
to align perfectly.
It was designed to be almost
a direct communication.
>> OK.
A communication device, but not
a portal for physical beings
coming and going.
>> She says it did have
portal capabilities,
but it was more of
a transcription.
Transcription device.
Is transcription writing?
>> Yeah.
I have transcribed.
Yeah, to describe.
>> So they were probably getting
information, and using that.
She's just showing me visuals.
There's not much else.
There's a big light
coming from it, but.
>> Hm.
How about the Nazca
South American area?
We recently exca-- there's
been some excavations
and some bodies
have being found,
sort of Reptilian
three-fingered beings.
>> OK.
I'm asking if she can--
or if there's a being
that can help use words.
Basically, the visuals
that she was showing me
were these structures aligning
to be a teleportation device.
And then beings were able
to come through that.
OK, so she said they were also--
I feel like she's saying
they were here to help mine.
>> Back in the Annunaki days?
>> Mm, that's not clear.
>> OK.
Based on what she
was saying, there's
something to do with
teleportation and mining
with those beings, as far as
what I asked about the role.
Timelines, I'm not sure about.
I feel like they're
earlier than--
she's showing me before the
first people along the Aztec.
So there was different
timelines for Aztec people,
and the Mayans, prior to that.
So I don't know how that
all plays in to history.
I feel like she's
even showing me
that it's even before the
humanoid was even built.
I feel like it's before-- yeah.
>> Even before the
Annunaki came through?
>> She says no.
>> Oh, OK.
Just right after, to assist
the teleportation devices.
>> They were assisting
the Annunaki?
>> She says yes.
They were given land
rights for assistance
because they had certain
knowledge of teleportation
that the Annunaki
needed help with.
She says, or we could even
just say beings on the planet,
because not all of
them were creating
the human at that time.
There were other
beings that could come,
but the Annunaki
established Earth
as their planet
for the long run,
and so created the human
to establish their domain.
But other beings were coming
and going at that time,
and this was one of them.
>> When did the quote
unquote quarantine--
that, let's say, loose term
we use for these beings
to stop coming--
>> So she says that there are
two parts to that question.
She's saying that she's
giving me the 1950s, 1960s,
that there were some
more rules put in place
with actual visitations.
But then, going back to where
we could physically see them
on a day-to-day like
we were talking about,
that is in the Roman time
period when things transitioned.
>> Oh, so prior to the Roman
era, there was more ET--
>> Yeah.
So--
>> --traffic?
>> Yeah.
[CHUCKLING]
So let me see if
I can get her to--
about 100 to 200
years after what
we know as Christ's death,
that's when things transitioned
where there were no more
visitations from light beings
in this quite the same way.
She says, but when you
speak of visitations
from other planets--
like we spoke of other
beings just coming--
there were more stricter
guidelines put in place,
she says, after the
1950s into the 1960s.
>> Is that because we had such
a flux of ET activity after
the nuclear bombs?
>> I'm asking her why that
is and she's showing me
the presidents.
She's showing me the
president had some--
OK, there's also some
from other countries.
She's showing me
they basically--
I don't know how
it all went down,
but there were some
rules put into place.
She's saying that Earth has been
quarantined in different ways
at several different times.
And because of what
we spoke of prior,
the light beings were not
able to come visit the humans
in quite the same way
because it had dropped down
into lower density.
And then, as you speak of
other density beings that
could resonate with a
similar frequency on Earth
and come down and make some
type of contact were forbidden.
And the threat was,
if they continued,
more chemical use
would be chosen.
>> So it's kind of been a trade,
then, on both sides for, OK,
we won't intervene if
you don't intervene.
[CHUCKLES]
>> Mm-hm.
>> Interesting.
>> She says it was
like, don't bother us.
If you do, more chemicals
will be expelled.
I'm asking her how did
that happen, though.
She just said
communication lines.
However they're communicating.
>> You mean, how did these
agreements come through?
>> Yeah, as far as
with our governments.
How did that all happen?
She says through
communication lines.
So I would assume that
might not be face to face,
but however they communicate.
>> Sure, sure.
Now, more people are having
experiences, and interactions,
and dreamtime experiences.
Are we at another gateway, or
was 2012 one of these gateways?
>> OK, so she's
nodding yes to 2012.
It was the start of
the opening, she says.
The door knob turning and
opening was what 2012 was.
And now we are slowly pushing
that door open more and more.
And then she visually
showed me the door
opening with the visual
of several different kinds
of beings, and
that's where the hope
is, to open that door to a point
where we can visually see them
once again.
She says, and have contact
and visual experiences
as we once had.
Can see tell us about
the hybrid children?
She says there are several
different programs of hybridization
Which one which one?
>>  The Zetas?
>>She says the Zeta star system has been
incorporated or Interacted with
your Earth for quite some time.
They have not been so benevolent.
But yet they have brought many
benefits to the human species
such as sciences and
mathematical reasoning, these
type of things, and they also
work well with other beings
that have brought this,
so you can say the interaction
has been beneficial
to have their type of
species along the Earth
for a time.
What we have found is they
are unable to reproduce and
they are in need of DNA exchange,
and so there have been interactions
as such she says.
In the future the exchange
will also occur where...
they will give you more
information on technology
and how to use it in
your benefit as well
as how to integrate
other perspectives
into their consciousness,
mainly more of the human perspective,
emotion, happiness...
They don't understand
the joy that humans can
feel, but they seek it.
And in order to incorporate
it they are using the DNA
in a sense to bring
that energy in.
>> And that's the hybrid children?
>>This is what the hybrid children will be like.
They she's saying they all
they have done several
different experimentations of
where the hybrid children
can procreate amongst each
other as well as other species
to create a broader perspective
for their own species.
Initially, it wasn't so they were
still trying to understand how
to incorporate the DNA
into their own species
in order to procreate on their own.
They have established it
now where they are able
to match to other species if desired.
>>So the human DNA was sort
of a facilitator to connect
with other species as well?
>>She says, yes big time,
because we have
such a variety.
Yeah.
But it always is in exchange
for something.
She says we never will take
unless there is a...
...she says like a universal exchange.
>> Sure, yeah, energy exchange.
>>Yeah.
>>Many people now claim to have
interactions with their hybrid children
in dream time and these things, is there...
will there be a time on
the planet here where we
can physically interact with
these children or is is this
more just of energetic
thing to shift the planet energy.
So and further our future,
these type of interactions
can actually really happen?
>>She's saying right now it is done consciously
such as you have a human
experience and
that is collected and they
can understand the
human emotion and help raise
their young as far as physical
interaction...
she says yes, we do
see this in the future.
This is partially why the
hybridization program began
in order for the understanding
that it can be integrated one with
another and have this type of interaction.
How the timelines pan out -
that is difficult to explain...
for it also depends on the human
consciousness in the interaction.
What is it they perceive the
quote Zetas to be like,
if that can evolve then
yes, integration can happen very soon.
If they can learn to trust more
freely and open their hearts
and minds into understanding
that there is connections
that can be made.
Then we see this happening
more sooner than later,
and the children are helping
bridge that connection.
>>It's my understanding the
Zetas were interested in
the human, the individualistic-
ness of the human
experience,
but yet they saw
a lack of logic in our
dualistic ego selves,
having sort of two
consciousnesses
in one consciousness.
Can you elaborate on that a little bit?
>>In order to answer this question,
she says I want to explain
that the Zeta consciousness
has been in a state where
one wasn't one without
the other.
Because they understand how physics,
mathematical
interactions
always have to have an
opposite and equal reaction.
You have to have two together
sort of idea.
There is no concept in
the logical mind
of that single perspective creating...
she says it's own break offs.
It typically will always
have a combating or
another perspective to
interact with, and so
logically this does not sense
to their consciousness
for quite some time.
But what they are finding is that in expansion,
there are aspects of
themselves that they
are missing that the human can
help them experience, and
some of that is through
an individual human experience.
Understanding that the human is a
break off of many.
>> Mm-hmm.
>>It can split into many
and this is what they
are very excited about
and trying to incorporate.
If you cannot logically in a
sense think that it is possible,
your consciousness, even if it
is of slightly higher density,
it cannot evolve past that
until it comes to the
conclusion that it must
incorporate it into
itself in order to evolve,
or in this case
to the point where it could
potentially die off if it
doesn't seek elsewhere
perspective.
>>So in other words we can
learn from the Zeta
experience that if we get
stuck in one direction,
too focused in one way, then...
we won't be around very
much, for very long.
>>Yes, she says most definitely yes,
thank you,.
It is the idea of
many of our species,
what we would say in
other star systems coming
into understanding that
there is a balance
and so we allow, all to happen
the way it is and to interact
the way it can be.
Otherwise we ourselves
cannot expand
if we do not understand
one another's perspectives.
>> So getting back
to our history,
it just sounds like the human
soup of all these different
beings over our history
of interaction, and DNA,
and energies,
it's just been one big
evolutionary experiment.
>> She likes that you say
the evolutionary experiment.
Yes, because we--
or the Annunaki,
the creators-- are all
involved with the creators
are expanding in just the same
that the human consciousness
is.
And that was previously
misunderstood.
>> And I guess, ultimately,
the goal of all of this,
is it to integrate back
into source, oneness,
through all these different
paths of integration?
>> She says yes.
And with that, to
understand that living
in this third density has been
beneficial for your learning,
because now you can
become the teachers
and expand even more fully
into the source energy
that we are all trying
to, what you might say,
make sense of or understand
within our hearts.
>> So kind of like an
Alcoholics Anonymous.
It takes the former alcoholic
to help teach the others about--
because they've
been in their shoes,
to teach them how to get out
of or stop the addictions.
>> She says yes.
And because you see
that there is a paradigm
allowed here on Earth,
or a sort of game shift--
let's see if I can have
her better term that--
matrix-style living, you
understand perhaps the mindsets
that can trap you
into that space.
>> The enslavement programs.
>> Yes.
She says, there are
others elsewhere
that have fairly
similar mindsets.
Perhaps you can be their
guides and teach them
ways to expand past beyond
what you call the matrix,
or the game playing.
>> Right.
>> But how would you know if
you hadn't had some of that
in your perspective?
>> Sure.
And is that why--
I'm sure the Pleiadians,
and we know the Orions,
and I'm sure the reptilians,
all of these different races
that we're interacting
now with, at some point
in their evolution have had
these enslavement games.
>> She said, I will agree
for the most part, yes.
>> But lastly, Antarctica.
>> Antarctica, OK.
>> Pyramids being
discovered in Antarctica.
I have a feeling this is a
huge piece of our history.
>> OK, so she's nodding yes.
And she says, this is
about to be revealed.
It has been quarantined
in a sense for a reason.
Notice it has no
dominion over it.
It is a free-for-all
peaceful state.
This has been arranged for
a very special reason--
to protect what it is that
can come about, you see.
We are very excited for this.
Yes, give it time, and more
and more can be revealed.
>> And sorry, one last thing.
Our Inner Earth families,
our ancient civilizations
that may be with us here,
but sort of in hiding.
>> She says this is partially
why this area was quarantined,
or why it has been protected.
This is a gateway to a
lot of those regions.
It has been revealed to some.
Some have had physical contact.
But believe this
is true, she says.
valid in the sense
that there can be
physical contact made.
Believe in your hearts that
that is true, she says.
When you believe
and are open to it,
you can match up to a sooner
timeline to experience it
in your reality.
>> Right.
It's all about belief
that brings in that--
>> And welcomeness, she says.
>> And welcomeness, yeah.
>> I do feel like
they're related somehow.
>> Mm-hm.
Can I ask where your
lineages come from?
>> She says, I am from
the Orion as well.
I work heavily with the
humans at this time.
They are going through
some great shifting,
and I help as a mediator.
I help as a translator
to help your human mind
understand certain concepts.
Forgive me, for I
am trying to learn
how to communicate in my
best way to the human mind,
for I see things as
the larger picture,
and you see things
as a small scope,
and I'm trying to shove
the larger picture
into that small scope in a
way that you can understand,
and also see the big picture.
>> I think you're
doing a great job.
Thank you very much.
[CHUCKLES] I'm
definitely getting it.
And I'm sure the
people watching here
will better understand
this reality
from sharing your perspectives.
>> She says, thank you so much,
and know that you can come
at any time and call upon the
Council of Light of the Highest
Good to help your individual
souls evolve in just the same
as we are trying
to help collective.
We do hear what you might call a
prayer, or an intent of action,
a seeking for your own soul.
Let us guide you into the
path that can help you
and to put you into a life that
is more fulfilled. Only if you
set the intent to
let the doors open,
and you get to select the door.
It is not us to tell
you which way to choose,
but we can give you different
ideas and avenues for you
to choose.
She says, this is what we
are very excited for you,
Reuben, because this is what
essentially will be happening
for you in this next year.
You will have many
doors, but you
get to choose which
path you will take.
Some of them, she says,
could be lighter than others.
Know this.
And that is when
perhaps the intent would
be of my highest good, we
can guide you to that path.
>>Well I hope we can
continue these conversation
in the future, and I appreciate
all the sharing, and knowledge,
and the in-depthness
of our history.
It sounds like we're just
on the tip of the iceberg.
>> Yeah.
She actually-- when you
were talking, she picked up,
like visually a grain
of sand, and said,
we have just touched on a small
bit of basically a large part
of the beach.
But she says, we have outlined
the most important parts.
The details can come
later as long as you
understand the bigger picture--
As long as you can
understand the bigger picture
behind humanity and
origins, and how it all
plays out into where
you're going in the future.
>> Yeah, I was actually
surprised that she came
through.
I was a little bit
hoping for the reptile,
but didn't go in that route.
>> He wasn't necessary
in this conversation.
>> [CHUCKLES] He was
not in the conversation.