As we go deeper into contact work
it becomes much more than
just about contacting ETs,
it really has a lot to do with the
evolution of consciousness
and the evolution of your planet.
We cannot separate the two.
The process that consciousness
takes from the experience of
separation to the experience of
reintegration.
Coincidentally it's the same process
that happens during the
contact experience -
simply...
When you live a human life,
your life seems continuous and solid,
but if you start meditating or
you start spiritual practices,
you'll start to notice that the quality
of reality changes,
your consciousness expands,
and you begin to travel to
another realm
in your conciousness.
Ever wonder if there's intelligent
life elsewhere in the universe?
Well, I have....I've been wondering since I was a kid.
My name is Reuben Langdon.
And on March 29th 2007, in the middle of the day,
I saw a number of strange objects in the sky.
Coincidentally, I was working on
the film Avatar at the time, playing an alien.
And ever since then I've been on a quest...
A quest to find out if aliens really do exist and if so...
...are they here with us?
If beings of higher intelligence are here...
...what is their purpose?
Why don't they make themselves more known?
Why the secrecy?
I've asked these questions to many experts,
yet each seems to have a different theory.
So I thought to myself,
why not ask the aliens directly?
So that's what I set out to do!
Well, sort of...
>> All right.
Hello to you,
this is Sasha.
>> Hi Sasha.
>> Nice to see you today.
>> Nice to see you.
Thanks for being here and being
part of this big adventure
show that I've got going on.
>> It is our pleasure.
>>First, I'd like to sort of
ask...
...what density do you reside in?
>> We are within what you
would call the higher levels
of fourth density.
>> Oh.
>> So we still have
physical bodies.
>> OK.
>> But we know that our planet
and our people is making--
on our way to making
the transition
to no longer having bodies.
>> So-- so almost--
well, fifth-- my understanding--
and I could be wrong--
but fifth--
fifth, sixth density would be
more losing the body sense.
But on the fourth
density as well?
>> In the scale that we use,
which is seven densities--
>> Right.
>> --the fourth density is
the last density in which
physicality is expressed
as a separate body.
>> OK.
>> As you begin moving
into fifth density,
then you become more
plasmic in nature.
>> I see.
>> So you could kind
of say light beings.
>> OK.
>> But as you go
farther and farther,
deeper and deeper
into fifth density,
then it becomes less
individualized and you start
moving more toward collective.
>> Would-- are dream states
be a fifth density reality?
What density would you
classify the dreams in?
>> Well, this is a metaphor
that we've used in the past
for another project.
We're going to resurrect it
here because it's very useful.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> If you consider the idea of
a golden lake to be your state
of oneness in
complete integration,
the state of sleep is the time
when, in a sense, you revisit,
or reconnect, with
that state of oneness.
So we wouldn't say that it is
necessarily a separate density.
The dream state is another
expression of consciousness
as you are reconnecting
with your true nature.
>> I see.
So it's not even--
it's almost in its
own classification.
>> Exactly.
>> Sort of like angelic realms.
Well, angelic realms I've
heard are borderline somewhere
around seventh--
sixth, seventh, eighth
density sort of thing.
But is that-- do they
have a classification?
>> Well, based on
what you're saying,
it seems we're using
different scales.
>> I see.
Yes.
OK.
>> So obviously, the answers
are going to be a little bit
confusing.
For us, it's a
seven density scale.
>> OK.
>> So we consider the angelic
realm to be more sixth density.
>> OK.
All right.
This is good because
I-- you know,
having, again, this scale
or base to ask questions
from and sort of
go back and forth,
it helps the audience sort of
put the pieces of the puzzle
together, formulate
their own ideas.
>> Yes.
>> Because a lot of the same--
sometimes, we use
same terminologies,
but, like we just noticed,
that it might be just slightly
a little bit different.
>> Yes.
If we will-- if we can say
just a little bit more about
density, just to give
a broader perspective--
>> Yes.
>> --for those
who are listening.
The best way to describe our
version of the communications
about density is to liken
it to the idea of a rainbow.
So when you have the
original white light that
then passes through a prism
and becomes a rainbow,
those seven light
frequencies that you see
are kind of representative
of the idea of the densities
of consciousness.
But if you look at
them very closely,
a rainbow for instance--
>> Yes.
>> --there's not a sharp
division between each one.
>> Right.
>> There's a gradation.
>> Correct, yeah.
>> So consciousness, thus,
moves from its original state
of oneness through the
fragmentation and through
series of different
types of expression.
The densest being
third density, which
is where humanity is leaving
from, because it's egoic based.
>> OK.
>> And then, you begin moving
out of that ego-based reality
and back into the collective.
>> I've also--
wonderful analogy.
I've also-- most
of the analogies
I've heard it's sort of
related to the chakra system,
which, again, is
related to the rainbow.
So it's--
>> Yes, exactly.
>> It sort of goes full circle.
>> Exactly.
>> So, you know, I've heard that
our plant and animal kingdom
are second density
consciousness.
>> Yes.
As we are moving
into fourth density,
and we're sort of in that
blending of the rainbow phase,
I would say early phase,
where are our animals--
are they blending into
the third density?
>> Ah.
OK.
There are two ways
to look at this idea.
One is a linear way and
one is a holographic way.
>> OK.
So if you are to look at it from
the perspective of linearity,
which is what humans
are more familiar with--
>> Yes.
>> --then what you would see
is that the other species
and the other consciousness
around you is moving also.
So from the linear
perspective, you're
going to find that the
species on your world
that you might consider
the higher second density
species, such as the primates,
and certain bird species, et
cetera, they are, too,
making a transition
to third density, which means,
then, the development of ego.
So you're starting to see even
in dogs and certain animals
more symptoms of ego.
Ego, of course, not
meaning a negative thing.
Ego is simply a mechanism
that grounds you
in the experience of separation
for a higher purpose.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> OK.
So in that sense, then,
that's the linear--
>> Right.
>> --perspective.
Now, if you were to look at
the holographic principle
of this idea, we're
going-- again,
we have to speak in metaphors.
>> Yes.
>> We're going to ask you to
imagine seven rooms that nest
inside each other like boxes--
like those Japanese boxes.
Yes?
>> OK.
Right.
>> And the bigger box that
contains the smaller boxes
would be more representative
of seventh density.
>> OK.
So from the holographic
perspective,
you exist in all of those boxes,
thus in all of the densities.
And it's simply a
matter of perspective
about the you that is choosing
to notice the experience it's
having at any given time.
But it is all simultaneous.
So in that sense, there's
no movement, linearly--
>> Right.
>> --from one
density to another.
It's a complete expression,
a complete experience
on all levels, simultaneously.
>> Right.
I saw-- would that relate to
platonic solids or geometrical
shapes--
>> Exactly, yes.
>> --as well?
There's a great video
I just saw online--
maybe I'll post it,
here, in this video--
where all of these platonic
solids were inside each other.
>> Exactly.
>> And they sort
of pull them apart.
>> Exactly.
The platonic solids are
a wonderful metaphor
for the density energy
and also for the evolution
of consciousness as it
moves from separation
back into integration.
There is one workshop
we do where we actually
equate each of the densities
to different platonic solids.
>> Oh, perfect.
OK.
>> It's the same idea, yes.
>> Oh, excellent.
And would that mean,
then, our first density
minerals and, you know,
rocks and these sorts of--
is water, I guess, consider
a first density being?
>> Yes.
Yes.
>> Would-- would that sort of
move into the second density,
then, and start having
sentient consciousness?
>> Well, the thing about
first density-- again, we're--
we're challenged by
the two perspectives,
linear and holographic.
>> Right, I guess what I'm
saying is in a linear sense.
>> In a linear sense.
>> Yeah.
>> In a linear sense, we have
to say that the first density,
consciousness, is a
little bit different.
>> OK.
>> Because the first
density consciousness,
being the first manifestation
into the reality of separation,
is the building
blocks of creation.
So it's your periodic
table of the elements.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> It's all those--
that stuff of creation.
>> Right.
>> Now, the higher forms, then,
like high first density would
be the mineral
kingdom, as an example.
>> Oh, I see.
OK.
>> And--
>> Oh, OK, OK.
So--
>> Yes.
>> So just like with our--
for, like, you guys
being on a higher
end of the fourth
density spectrum--
so you still have
physical bodies like us.
The craft that you
probably fly around in--
and where we're just
now entering that phase,
but we're still in that
fourth density classification.
OK.
>> So it's a spectrum.
>> Right.
>> It's an entire spectrum.
But the difference
you're gonna see--
because you humans are now
entering the fourth density
beginnings.
>> Right.
>> And we're toward the end.
The biggest difference
you're going
to see between the two of us is
what we call the egoic anchor.
>> OK.
>> So ours is not as
heavy, so to speak.
>> From your time of evolution,
if you can remember this
or have records of this
in your era, what was,
in relative years--
earth years, your
linear evolution
from beginnings of fourth
density to where you are now?
>> Well, the-- our--
looking at it linearly, we
went through very similar type
of evolution that you are
going through now, however,
we would say that our
challenges, as a species,
were different than yours.
So for us, a lot
of our challenges
had to do with
self-forgiveness, guilt, things
that we were holding on
to as a young species
that we then had to
learn how to transcend.
And for a very, very
long period of time,
those challenges for my species
really stopped our evolution
and almost destroyed
us as a species
because when you keep putting--
pushing down the
emotional things that
need to be explored, you can--
well, our species created
a plague, so to speak.
>> A plague, oh, wow.
>> Plague, yes.
Similar to what you might
call an immune plague where
a disease within our immune
systems was destroying us
and we had no idea what it was.
And we had to use
our connections
with, you might call
them the angels,
or the guardians of our species,
the guides of our species--
we had to connect with them
to find out what it was.
And what we found out was that
our pattern, as a species,
was that we were refusing
to look at and integrate
what you call the shadow.
>> OK.
Oh, I see.
>> So we were keeping
that separation.
And once we could
learn to integrate
the shadow and the
light within us,
this was a significant
nexus point
in our fourth
density evolution--
third fourth density evolution.
Once we were able to
make that integration,
then the plague healed
itself and our consciousness
began evolving.
>> Into fourth density.
>> Yes.
>> And was that a long time ago?
Or time wise, in a
linear sense, are you
able to put a time stamp on it?
>> Oh, it's very difficult
because, as you know,
timelines don't line up.
>> Sure.
>> But it was long enough ago--
if we were to pinpoint
a time on your world,
it would have been before
late, late dinosaur time.
>> OK.
So we're talking
thousands of years.
>> Millions.
>> Millions of years.
>> Yes.
>> In fourth density, right
now, since that evolution to it.
>> Again, the timelines
don't line up.
>> OK.
Right.
Yeah, I understand.
>> It's very-- it's really
impossible to answer.
The evolution--
generally speaking,
the evolution of
a physical species
does take a very,
very long time.
Now, it depends on the species.
It depends on the
genetic work that's
been done on the species.
It depends on what they're
holding on to, what
they're willing to let go of.
So everyone's
process is different.
>> Right.
Through these interactions,
I've learned that we all
create our own realities.
Is it possible for an
individual to go into a timeline
where the collective
evolution of the species
is accelerated, if the
individual is willing to do
that work, so to say.
And then-- and not
bypass the collective,
but go into a timeline where
that collective evolution
is super fast?
>> Well, that's really the
only way to change timelines.
It's not-- as you said, it's
not a matter of bypassing,
it's more a matter of resonance.
>> Right, OK.
>> So we've given--
we believe you've
heard it on tape,
we've given a little bit of what
we call the quantum map, which
talks about how the reality
stream or the time stream
is very similar to like
the blinking of eyes.
You don't notice your
eyes are blinking all day.
>> Right.
>> But that is
how the physical--
the physical universe continues
to express itself is through
bursts.
And each time-- it's like an
in breath and an out breath.
So each time there is
an in breath, which
is like the blinking
of an eye, you
realign with a new
frequency structure.
And that's how time--
that's how you, in a
sense, jump timelines.
We do have to say, though, that
the ego cannot direct this
at all.
>> Right.
>> So.
>> So, so it's a release of
the ego in order to do that.
>> Exactly.
>> Right.
So it's not-- and,
consciously, there's almost--
it's almost-- you can't--
almost can't do it consciously
because of--
>> Exactly.
>> --the ego is part of
this conscious mental mind--
>> Exactly.
>> --where we have-- where
we're trying to guide,
where we're trying
to steer the ship.
>> Exactly.
>> And you have to sort of let
go of the steering wheel to get
there.
>> Exactly.
The ego has-- it has
very significant needs.
>> Right.
>> And it will always, let's
say, default to those needs--
>> Right.
>> --before it will default to
the evolution of consciousness.
>> Right.
>> Because then it
dies, so to speak.
Yes.
>> It's almost like going to
the mountain and doing the hard
training.
And, then, you know, after
all the hard training,
you realize that, you know, to
get to this enlightened state,
there's no training necessary.
>> Exactly, my dear.
Exactly.
>> Excellent.
So it-- I kind of
want to go back
to the Pleiades and
your star system now.
We have this definition
of the Pleiades--
>> Yes.
>> --of, you know, the--
is it the Six Sisters?
Seven Sisters?
>> Seven Sisters, yes.
>> Seven Sisters.
And there's obviously--
because if you
look through a micros--
or a telescope,
you can see a lot more stars
than just the seven stars
that we see.
>> Yes.
>> We-- we realize we did take a
tangent off into something else
from what you were asking.
Basically speaking,
we're actually
going to jump back
and answer part
of this question and the other
question that you had before.
Basically speaking, the beings
that you know of as Pleiadians
are not indigenous to the area
that you know of as Pleiades.
All right.
>> OK.
>> So we have, basically,
two genetic lines.
One comes from the ancient Lyra.
>> OK.
>> And one comes from the
ancient Lyra combined with
Earth genetics.
That's another story,
perhaps for another time.
So there's two
different lines that
eventually colonized in the area
that you know of as Pleiades.
So not really the Seven Sisters.
However, in the
ancient days, when
my people would visit
your people on Earth,
and we would be asked
where are we from, well,
if we pointed to
those seven stars--
>> Right.
>> --in that direction,
they got the point.
>> I see.
now the idea of humanity
being a mixture well
of course, it's no surprise to
you that you know that there is
a genetic connection between us.
>> Yes.
>> And it comes from many,
many different sources,
some of which is the Lyran--
the original Lyran
template DNA and Pleiadians
evolving from that.
And then, also, working
with the genetics on Earth.
But we find this idea
of simply looking
at it genetically
to be extremely
limiting because nobody
is indigenous to anywhere.
You are originally one.
>> Correct.
>> So again, we have
to use metaphor.
>> Yes.
>> If you take
holographic film--
and the nature of
holographic film
is that if we were to
take a picture of an apple
and then cut up the
film in tiny pieces,
each tiny little piece would
have the complete image
of the apple.
And it doesn't matter how
small you cut those pieces.
>> Right.
>> So consciousness is
fractal in that way.
>> Yes.
>> And therefore, no matter
if you are a lowly human,
so to speak, on Earth,
here, at this time,
you are fractally and
holographically every other piece
as well.
>> Correct.
>> So in that sense, then, the
question is difficult to answer
because our default
setting is not linear.
>> Right.
>> And yet language is linear.
>> So you mean the Pleiadian--
where you are in
your evolution--
>> Yes.
>> --is not linear, correct?
>> And in our human
system, our human OS,
is sort of in a linear sense.
>> Yes.
>> So we're trying
to match those.
>> Yes.
But you're really shifting.
>> Yeah.
My understanding is
that the Pleiadian
is a very feminine energy.
Is that correct?
Or is it very balanced,
in that sense?
I always perceived, or
felt, more feminine energy,
archetypal energy, related
to the Pleiadian energy.
>> Yes.
Well, what you're going
to find with-- again,
not a simple answer
to the question--
what you're going to
find with my species,
as well as many
of the other core
species in your galactic family,
is that there's generally
three eras of development.
The first era is more
of the infant species.
And it is in that
first era where
the issues, let's say, of each
species that need to be healed,
come up.
All right.
And then the second
era tends to be
the healing period when
the integration starts,
the healing happens.
The third era, which is,
of course, the mature era,
is when awakening, as
a species, happens.
So my species,
particularly, is felt
as feminine in all three eras,
which is really interesting.
And it's kind of rare because
many of the other species
are more felt masculine.
>> OK.
>> But the reason we are felt
more feminine in all three eras
is because as follows.
First era, we already
told you that the tendency
for my species was to not
want to look at the shadow.
So we were kind of floating
around in the spiritual bubble.
>> Right.
>> All right, which is actually
an unbalanced feminine energy.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> OK.
Then, when you go
to the second era,
and the integration happens,
integration, or the act
of integration,
by its very nature
is feminine because
it's inclusive.
So all of that integration was
creating a movement inward,
which is a very feminine energy.
And then, of course,
in the third era,
which is the awakened
era, you have a species
that is very balanced
male female energy that
is in an awakened state.
And to a separated
consciousness on Earth,
that state feels very feminine.
>> So that's why I--
we're-- you know, myself and
other people get that feeling.
>> Exactly.
And-- and this is going
into some other races,
but I was told that--
my understanding is
that the Anunnaki
were a hybrid race of Pleiadian
and Draconian energies.
Is that-- do you see it
from that perspective?
>> No.
We're going to be a little
bit of a rebel, here.
>> Sure.
>> Because the word Anunnaki
in your Sumerian language,
as far as we understand
the definition,
means those who have come down.
>> OK.
>> So Anunnaki is
meaning, basically,
those who came from the heavens.
>> OK.
>> So they were not one species.
>> I see.
>> They were many.
Oh, OK.
That-- well, that clears
up a lot of stuff.
A lot of questions I had.
>> Yes.
>> So that-- that
is interesting.
You know, we were trying
to figure out why--
where did the Anunnaki
get all this DNA
the old story of enslaving--
making humans for slaves--
>> Yes.
>> --for mining gold.
>> And that was only one
particular family that did
that.
>> OK.
>> But as you know, they're the
ones that get the bad rap, yes?
>> Right.
Right.
>> The rotten apple
spoils the bunch.
>> I see.
So speaking of DNA and when that
race of beings, or that family,
took all these various DNAs
from different star systems
and created the human
structure, um,
how did that work
in the beginning?
Or was there this--
again, this--
there had to be an
agreement of sorts,
otherwise it wouldn't
have happened.
>> Of course, there's
always an agreement.
>> Yeah.
>> However, again,
we have to say that--
we have to look at it from
a non-human perspective.
Now, you're quite familiar with
other channeled information
and such talking
about, basically,
if something is happening,
or something is arising,
there must be a higher purpose.
And that is not, in any
way, meant to be a cop out.
All right.
It's simply the way
the universe works.
>> Sure.
>> There is no mistakes--
>> Absolutely.
>> --in creation.
Now, in those
ancient days, we have
to say that your Earth,
or your solar system,
could be likened to what you
call the wild, wild west.
>> Yeah.
Feels like that
today, still, but--
>> Well, yes, it is.
It is.
But it's a little bit
more colonized now.
>> Sure.
>> So it was an isolated place.
And because of that
isolation, a lot went on,
that was very fragmented
with groups, one group having
one agenda, one group having
another agenda and conflicts
and things such as that.
All because these
forefathers of yours
were a very young species.
This doesn't happen
with older species.
Only with younger ones.
>> I see.
So you sort of answered
the question earlier,
that, yes, there was some
sort of higher purpose.
And therefore, these other
races sort of lend their DNA
for this higher purpose.
>> Yes.
>> It wasn't stolen or
taken and put-- you know,
I'm going to go drug the
Arcturian and then grab some
DNA or some mojo--
>> Yes.
That makes a wonderful
science fiction movie.
>> Sure.
>> But it's not quite
the way things work.
>> Sure.
>> One of the things that we've
said to many people, sometimes,
that ask questions about this
is that from the perspective
outside of the Earth, or from
a fourth density perspective,
let's say, this idea of the
sharing of DNA and the shaping
of cultures using DNA is
actually a very natural
process.
It's kind of like pollination--
>> Right.
>> --on your world.
And when you look at
it-- when you remove
the victim-perpetrator idea--
>> Right.
>> --which is really only
applicable in a very polarized
third density reality, then
the whole paradigm changes,
actually.
>> Right.
>> But the question,
then, is why?
Why do people have
these experiences
of being a victim and
things such as that.
>> Sure.
>> Why do those
buttons get pushed?
Well, when you are a
third-density species,
in a sense, you
can say there are
many passages, spiritual
passages, that you
have to go through in order
to evolve your consciousness
on the way to fourth density.
One of those passages has
to do with the healing
of the clinging to the idea
of victim and perpetrator.
And many civilizations get
stuck there for millennia.
And so when you
have-- well, we're
bringing in another
tangent, here.
>> No, that's fine.
>> But when you have the
situation with the Zetas
and the so-called abductions,
it triggered the same issues
humanity has been playing out
for so many thousands of years,
but this time from space.
Are there victims?
Are there perpetrators?
And on the individual
level of those
who were claiming abduction,
the reason it's happening
is because they have to
pass through that gate
in order to shift
their consciousness
and integrate the polarity
within themselves.
And then, on a
collective level, it
happens on a collective
level, as well,
that changing of the paradigm.
And therefore, a passage
into fourth density
can be made, or one of
the steps of the passage.
>> So without the
Zeta abduction,
temporary detainment,
experience, then,
we wouldn't even have the
opportunity to heal that wound
to move into fourth density.
>> Exactly.
Or you would have
re-created something else.
>> Some other scenario.
>> Yes.
>> Yeah, we would have.
But at least we got
to have it in that way
so we could connect
to our cosmic family.
>> Exactly.
>> As opposed to, you know,
making another story on Earth.
>> Yes, because in the
Orion civilization,
they didn't create that-- the
healing of that through the ET
contact.
They created it through
a domineering empire.
>> Right.
And that was the Orion Wars?
>> Yes.
>> Was-- was the Pleiadian--
your society involved in those
wars?
>> Shamefully, yes.
We're making a joke.
>> Right.
>> Now, again, those
conflicts lasted for a very,
very long time.
So there was a period of time,
when my species was very young,
that our mindset was
kind of like a teenager
in your human counting.
You know, gung ho, do this,
jump in without thinking
of the consequences.
>> Right.
>> And so we did that.
And as you say in
your vernacular,
got our asses kicked.
And that brought up
the issues of the guilt
and all that kind of stuff that
we had to work on as a species
in order to make our shift.
So in that way, there's
nothing extraneous.
>> So now, obviously, that
period of time is over
and, hopefully, the Orion--
and we say now.
And obviously time--
and I guess, you know,
I'm just-- where you
are with your evolution,
you've cleared that up.
You've been through that.
You've had this-- we have the
story of the Orion Wars to tell
to-- so we can keep--
you heal--
>> Yes.
>> --some future generations.
Because hey, we've been
there, we've done that.
>> Yes.
And there are some residuals
finishing up on your world,
as well.
>> Right.
With the Orion Wars.
>> Yes.
>> OK.
And because again-- so I've--
you know, I've
heard this analogy
that everything that's
happening on Earth is sort of--
the micro and the macro, so--
>> Yes.
>> --you know, if we go
back just 20 years maybe
in our timeline, then the Orion
Wars are still happening kind
of in a way, depending on which
timeline we're in, I guess.
>> It really depends on what
you are connecting with,
energetically.
>> Right.
And so that-- instead of looking
at it from a linear sense,
the vibrational frequency
of where we're at,
if we're vibrating
at that frequency,
then, yes, the Orion
Wars are still happening.
>> Exactly.
>> OK.
>> For instance, people in your
world who live in the Middle
East, who are embroiled in
extreme polarity and extreme
control--
>> Yeah.
>> --are directly connecting,
still, to that era of Orion.
>> Right.
>> Whereas, perhaps, you,
in your daily life, are not.
>> Correct.
I see.
So instead of seeing time
linearly in that sense,
it's just more of a
vibrational frequency.
>> Yes, and it's very fluid.
>> Right.
And that-- so we can sort of see
time in our daily lives, too.
And if we can see everything
as a vibrational frequency,
then, maybe we can get through,
navigate through this frequency
soup, I like to call
it, a little bit easier.
>> Yes.
You're in a very--
as you well know, you're in
a very interesting time right
now, because in a sense you have
one foot in third density, one
foot in fourth.
You're taking the foot
out of third density.
But because it's a
spectrum, and there's
a gradation as the
energy changes,
you're still going
to have challenges
with the old way of doing
things as the new structures are
arising.
>> Right.
>> So this is really the most
tenuous time and also the most
challenging one.
>> Right.
But also the most--
>> Exciting.
>> --exciting because the
shift, the daily shifts,
are happening at such an
exponential rate that we really
can take notice.
>> Yes.
>> And see these changes.
>> And that's exciting.
>> Exactly, yes.
>> Exciting.
>> And it's exciting
for us to watch, too.
>> Right.
Exactly.
we're having this conversation
with Lisa and Ron,
earlier, about the-- we
call it the Mandela Effect,
is the internet terminology
for what seems to be,
from one perspective, a
shifting of timelines.
>> Yes.
>> And it's almost
now been labeled.
Now, we have a
collective name for it.
And we're seeing pieces
in our history shifting
from the way we remember it.
>> Yes.
>> And we're going back and
reviewing movies and tangible,
physical things, that the
way we remembered them,
they weren't that way before.
>> Yes.
>> Is this the actual
shifting of timelines?
>> It is the you--
as we were just talking about a
moment ago, time is more fluid.
>> Right.
>> When you are rooted,
let's say, in third density,
time feels and is perceived
as being more fixed.
But now you're moving more
into a fluid sense of time.
And that means,
then, that you are--
again, it's a metaphor.
It's the limit of the language.
>> Sure.
>> You are spending more
time in the quantum state
of consciousness where
all possibilities exist.
>> Right.
>> And you are, thus, able to--
remember, we were talking
about the blinking in and out,
or the in and out breath.
>> Right.
>> You are able to shift the
timelines much more rapidly.
But in the past
when you did it, you
didn't remember
the previous one.
But now, as you are spending
more time in the quantum,
you're becoming more
familiar and comfortable
with that energy, that
you're starting to remember
the other parallels.
Not in a schizophrenic
way, but in a way
that's meant to just tell--
that's meant to just show you--
>> Right.
>> --look how fluid you are
becoming, you are unlocking.
>> And that's where the
excitement-- you know,
this is--
>> Yes.
So now, you're beginning
to see that the future--
you've always seen
the future as fluid,
but now, you're seeing
the past as fluid, too.
>> Exactly.
And-- and we can rewrite
the story if we want to.
>> Yes, but the ego can
never rewrite anything.
>> Ah, the ego.
Yes.
>> Yes, yes, ah, the ego.
>> Interesting.
>> This is where people who do
manifestation work get stuck.
>> Ah, yes.
>> Because the ego
takes over the show.
>> Right.
I can see that.
I can absolutely see that.
So we want to rewrite the
story, but we can't really
rewrite the story.
We just have to--
we can't rewrite the past
story, but we can rewrite
the now story with our choices.
>> Yes.
You can rewrite the now story.
Now, when we talk about now,
we're talking about now.
>> Right.
>> And now.
And now.
We're not talking about
one second from now.
>> Sure.
>> All right.
So the only thing, then,
that you have in the now
is your experience of the now.
>> Right.
>> So therefore, what you
are really rewriting is
your experience of the now--
>> Right.
>> --which really has to do with
your interpretation of the now.
>> And that, depending
on that interpretation,
will set us on a specific
vibrational frequency.
>> Exactly.
>> And then, depending on
that vibrational frequency,
we see the past rewrite itself.
>> Exactly.
So if your interpretation of the
now is one of victimization--
>> Sure.
>> --guess what
you're going to get.
>> We're going to get a past
history of Zetas abducting you
every night against your will.
>> Yes.
>> And if you are at a
vibrational frequency
of non-victimization,
empowerment, then,
you're going to be going on the
ships and donating your stuff
instead of actually being
taken against your will.
>> Yes.
And even-- getting out--
getting out of the ET stuff--
even we're talking about,
is your boss picking
on you at work?
>> Sure.
>> So we're even talking
about the human stuff here.
>> Right.
Right.
And then, shifting
that perspective,
shifting that now moment,
now all of a sudden your boss
is not picking on you, but got
a greater plan or, you know,
something, some other story.
>> Exactly.
And this brings in
the whole other aspect
of the emotional body because
the ego, the insidious ego--
we say that with love
because the ego is simply
a neutral mechanism.
But the insidious ego
will continue its dialogue
with you that will
tell you, well,
if you're not shifting this
now, you're not very spiritual.
You're bad.
You're failing.
And that that just
further entrenches--
>> Right.
>> --the anchor of the ego.
>> So it's just a big lesson
of allowance and acceptance.
>> Exactly.
Exactly.
>> And just being, really.
And not the knee jerk reactions.
>> Exactly.
And watching yourself
so that you can
see your habits and patterns.
And that's the key
to your freedom.
And by embracing those
emotions when they come,
as opposed to pushing them away.
>> Exactly.
>> Ok.
Now I've heard different
stories on the Zeta race
is, I've heard in one scenario that the
Zeta's have died off, that they, you know,
they created the hybrid races, they couldn't
continue to reproduce so they eventually died off.
And I've heard other stories now
that the Zetas are continuing their evolution
because of their interaction with humans,
they've actually activated their emotional
bodies and are thriving quite well.
And I don't know if they're back to
reproducing, but at least they're on that path.
And I'm assuming there's two different
timelines that these are happening?
How does this work?
Well, as with any species, if there is an
aspect of the species that refuses to
change, that portion of it will die off.
>>Okay.
>>Alright?
But, as we were talking about
before, regarding the three eras of
most of the physical species that you're
connected with, the Zetas also have their three eras.
So the first era was the era of their species crisis,
and when they weren't able to reproduce and the
emotional body was cut off etc.
The second era started to take place as the
interactions with humans began, and all
through the interaction period, for their species,
it meant the reintegration with the
emotional body through the work with humans.
But also through the creation of
the hybrid species because... And you know
the whole story, the drama about learning
to nurture them and things such as that.
>>Right, yes.
>>And all of those challenges they
had in the second era helped their integration process.
Then the third era
Zeta, we would call the awakened ones.
Mmm hmm.
So this is a very, very high level Zeta
consciousness that... then talking about
parallel timelines, in the 80's and the 90's,
very few people on Earth were
tapping into that third level Zeta
consciousness, because people were still
processing the more polarized victim consciousness.
>>Correct.
>>But we would say really beginning
five to ten years ago on Earth, your...
many of you are now starting
to tap into the third era Zeta
consciousness when they have awakened.
So their emotional bodies, mental bodies, all
of that, came into alignment and
integration.  And they've become like an
elder race that is very... acting very much
as mentors for younger species now....
Wow, how does that all work?
I guess, to put it in a, in a linear... And
again,  this is our linear minds trying to
figure this out, because we have very
advanced future versions of the
Essassani and Bashar coming in and talking to us;
the Yahyel, we have other
channelers bringing in different beings
from the Yahyel civilization.
And I'm assuming that they look
up to the Zeta, that third tier of the
Zetas that we were just talking about. >>Yes.
>>That they're interacting with them on
that level. >>Yes, like grandfathers. >>Right
grandfathers, because I'm sure
their vibrational frequency is at that
higher level, so they're ... in their reality,
in their timeline, they still exist.
Yes.  They didn't die off.  >>Yes.  >>And yet
we're humans in this level and, you know we're...
how does that interaction... I don't know...
Could you go into depth a little bit about that?
>>My goodness, we're not sure exactly, because there's
so many tangents we could go off at.
Is there a specific curiosity and we can start there?
>>I... The... It's... It has to do with time and
the sense that we have these different
aspects of the Yahyel and the Essassani, and
even the Zetas, coming back at this
particular time, that version of them.  Why not...
And even the version of yourself, why not
an earlier version of, of the Pleiadean...
>>Ah, all right.  >>And then we, and then we have
higher density, dimensional
collectives of the Pleiadians also visiting us.
>>Yes, well, it's back to what we were
talking about earlier regarding
frequency compatibility.  >>Okay.  >>And also
what you're calling in to push you to
move to another level.
>>Okay, I see.  >>So you have, you have one aspect
that is the challenge aspect that pushes
you, and you have another aspect that is
more of a mentorship level.  >>I see.
>>Okay, so for instance, you on your world, you
have some UFO lore, if you wish to call
it that, from the 60's or 70's -
the Billy Meier Pleiadian contacts?  >>Oh yes, yeah. >>Alright,
and so sometimes people ask "Sasha, do you
know Semjase?" Okay.  Well from
my perspective, my time, she is a past
figure.  >>Okay.  >>Long, long gone.  >>Right.  >>Not
in physical body any more, but in your time
stream in the 70's you were pulling
in those Pleiadian contacts because that's
what you needed.
>>I see.  >>Now you're pulling in different
types of Pleiadian contacts because
that's what you need as well .  So the
Essassani, the Essassani especially, and the
hybrid species are playing a very
important role that has to do with
alchemy.  What do we mean by that?  Well the
idea of alchemy is the bringing together
of two seemingly conflicting ideas that
create a response when they come
together to create a third idea.  >>Right.
>>And this is, let's say, energy dynamics
101 in terms of species evolution.  So
whenever you get to a planet that is
moving from 3rd to 4th density, they
are going to have to integrate the
mental and emotional bodies, and they do
so through a form of alchemy.  So the
Essassani, in a sense, are the alchemists or
the representations of successful
alchemy.  >>Okay.  >>And you see it at a... through
the combination of Zeta and human, but
also through what they actually
integrated, which is the mental and
emotional bodies.  >>I've heard
Bashar speak that the Essassani are
closely related to the Sirius energy.
>>Yes.
...in terms of Bashar, you will
find that the flow of energy for the
Essassani evolution moves toward a higher
non-physical Sirian vibration for its
future selves.  So you find that a lot of...
there's a lot of future incarnations
that move from the Essassani to the Sirian.
And we would call that third era Sirian
beings, again, the awakened ones.  >>I see.  And
humanity,
it seems like we're in a crossroads
right now, because we have so many
directions we can go with our evolution.
>> Yes.
>>We can go towards the Sirian direction of
evolution; we can go towards the
Pleiadian direction; we can even go
towards the Draconian... >>Yes  >>...way of
evolution, and in specific time
lines we are doing it all simultaneously.  >>Exactly, yes.
>>Okay.  And its really up to us individually
to see which one we want to be a part of.
>>So we go back then to what we were
talking about a few moments ago, about...
Because the ego cannot control the
trajectory, all you have is the current
moment.  So in the current moment your
trajectory becomes clear.
So this is some work Lyssa, Germane and
myself have been doing with those, with
using the Galactic cards to help bring
the focus with people to what is
happening for them in this moment now?
And lets say it's an emotional
pattern that's more anchored in past
Pleiadian, or an emotional pattern that's
more anchored in past Zeta, then these
become icons almost or, or archetypal
stories that can help you move through
in this moment now whatever your
challenge is, and it ripples through time
in both directions.  Because ultimately...
Again, going back to the seven rooms,
seven concentric circles, you are the one
and your fragments are inside the one, so
you're never really outside of anything
and everything is you anyway.