So I started channeling 20 years ago,
it's crazy when I think that it's been 20 years.
And probably about eight or nine months
after I started channeling.
I started getting information from this
group called the Pleiadian Collective
and they’re 9th dimensional beings.
They do not have physical form.
They are beings of light and rather incarnating to a planetary body.
They actually align with a stellar body.
So they align with Alcyone
the central sun and the Pleiades system.
And they are a little different than the other beings
that I work with
because I actually do work with a lot of different beings.
I work with beings from Lyra, from Sirius, and Zetas.
Let's see,  Arcturians...so I do work with a number of beings
but the Pleiadians always come through first and foremost
and sometimes these other beings will show up and they
may show up today and they will blend their energy with the Pleiadians.
So you might notice that the energy shifts a little bit
because these beings have come in and they always take point
because it's somewhat easier for them to receive the...
...for you to receive the information from the Pleiadians.
They have such heart-based energy.
And they're also a little different
because they work with tone and sound.
So that's why they're dialect is different than my own.
It's not any one particular dialect.
It's just tones and sounds that resonate with you at a cellular level.
So over the course of the next several days,
they'll continue working with you
and in addition to getting the information it's
as if you're getting a healing as well,
so you want to make sure you drink plenty of water.
Just help move the energy through the body.
Ah yes hello dears. This is the 9th dimensional
Pleiadian Collective and it is a pleasure and an honor to
have the opportunity to connect with you all.
because you're going through a phase right now where it
is vital and in in your development
that you become more and
more aware of the subtle frequencies around you and as
you become better able to
perceive these subtle frequencies.
It makes life a lot easier for you
because you are learning how to operate more from
a state of being which will then guide you
to your doing state and if you're not
conscious of the subtle frequencies, you can often miss those
breadcrumbs that the universe is providing you to take
steps in a divinely guided
way to get you on your path
of higher service.
Also know that we are working with all of you energetically and
you can connect with us at any time.
You don't need Wendy.
All you have to do is put yourself in your heart center.
Think of something that makes you smile.
Ask for assistance and we will do our best
to put the information in your field until you get it or you
no longer want it.
We are helping you to elevate your frequency.
The one thing that we always do any time that
we work with you, we work with harmonics at the
very beginning, in our opening greeting and we
actually do an attunement with you.
We don't really talk about this a lot, but we help you to alter your
vibrational field and help you to realign anything
that maybe misaligned or not
in in alignment with your true heart's desires.
So your own guides are here
feeding us information and what you need we will
say there are no silly questions.
So
just know that your
curiosity your fearlessness is
appreciated by many.
So we'll go ahead and dive in and see where you'd like to begin.
How may we best be of service to you today?
Ever wondered if their is intelligent
life elsewhere in the universe?
Well, I have....I've been wondering since I was a kid.
My name is Reuben Langdon
And on March 29th, 2007 in the middle of the day,
I saw a number of strange objects in the sky.
Coincidentally, I was working on
the film Avatar at the time, playing an alien.
And ever since then I've been on a quest...
To find out if aliens really do exist and if so...
...are they here with us?
If beings of higher intelligence are here...
...what is their purpose?
Why don't they make themselves more known?
Why the secrecy?
I've asked these questions to many experts,
Yet, each seems to have a different theory.
So I thought to myself,
why not ask the aliens directly?
So that's what I've set out to do!
Well, sort of...
>> So Wendy, welcome.
>> Thank you--
>> Thank you for--
>> --for having me.
>> --being here and uh.
Can you tell us,
can you tell me,
and tell us, I guess everybody
that's watching, first of all,
how did you get into
the channeling process?
And how did you
come into contact
with the beings known
as the Pleiadians?
>> Oh, gosh.
OK.
So, yeah, I think a couple
different things there.
So it was around 1994 and I
started having some visions.
And I didn't really
know what they were.
They weren't the
happiest of visions,
but I wasn't frightened by them.
And so I started
doing some research
for that to see if it was
past-life related, because that
was what my instinct was.
And so as I started
that research
to find out more
about past lives,
I came across channeling.
And I didn't know what it was.
I didn't know
anybody who did it.
But I just knew it
was something that I
was supposed to be doing.
And so--
>> When you came across it,
you came across it as you saw
somebody else doing that?
>> No.
I came across it in books.
>> Oh, OK.
>> And there wasn't a lot of
channel material out there
at the time.
There was the Seth
material and Sanaya Roman
had some books out.
But really, there
wasn't a whole lot.
And it was very familiar.
And I just knew it was
something I was supposed to do.
So I found some
books and I started
doing some of the
meditation exercises
and the visualization exercises.
And I was trying to
channel verbally,
but it wasn't really
happening for me.
I was having really
visceral experiences,
like my eyes would
flutter and water
and my hands would tingle.
But I couldn't form the words.
I couldn't get the words out.
And so I'd put it aside and
then I'd come back to it.
And in the interim, I did
a lot of work on myself.
I studied meditation and
did a lot of inner work.
And then I'd come back
to it periodically.
And I'd have kind of
the same experience.
And then one day, I knew
I was supposed to sit down
with a pen and paper--
>> OK.
>> --and I started
doing automatic writing.
>> Excellent.
>> And that I did--
well, for the first
two years, I wrote down
every single question
and every answer.
And about nine
months or so into it,
it was becoming very
cumbersome to write.
And so I put down
the pen and then
just started to
channel verbally,
because I was hearing it well
before I was able to write it.
And I still use
automatic writing today
because it's much easier for
me to remember the information.
It's a bit like a
lucid dream for me.
So at least I have
the written notes.
And I can go back to it.
But about nine months in, that's
when the Pleiadians showed up.
>> Interesting.
>> And they were waiting
for me to channel verbally
because they work
with tone and sound.
>> OK.
>> And a lot of people will
ask me where I'm from when they
hear the Pleiadians,
especially at the beginning,
they sounded a bit more British.
And then they started
working with new tones
and then it sounded a
bit more Australian.
And it's not any one dialect.
>> Right.
>> It's just tones and
sounds that resonate with you
at a cellular level.
And it was really
interesting for me
because when they started
channeling and working
with the new tones, it was using
all different kinds of muscles.
>> Oh, wow.
>> And I was like, OK, can
we tone it back just a bit?
>> Right.
>> Tone it, no pun intended.
But it really affects
us vibrationally.
And I could tell that
there was a big difference.
So we get a healing
when we work with them.
Not only do we receive
the information,
but the tones and sounds help to
alter the cellular structure--
>> OK.
>> --and create more balance
and harmony in the body.
And how did I first meet them?
I think I've been working
with them all along.
>> OK.
>> And I know that there's
an aspect of me that is part
of the Collective.
There are about 2,500
beings in the group.
And there is an aspect of
me that is a part of that.
And they're in the
ninth dimension.
And they don't have physical
form, they're beings of light.
And they align
with Alcyone, which
is the central sun in
the Pleiades star system.
And because they don't
have physical bodies,
they don't incarnate,
but they align
with a purpose, or a function.
And they're here to help us
with records, and information,
and to kind of
oversee what we're
doing to help us
along the way so
that we can start
taking ownership
and guardianship of the planet.
And there's another
role that we're
about to step into at
the galactic level.
>> Well, so you mentioned
earlier that you formulated
questions and answers.
Were the questions
also being channeled?
>> No.
They were things that
I wanted to know about--
>> OK. Got you.
>> --problems I was
having in my life.
And I think, early on,
everybody has the same couple
questions.
Tell me about love.
Tell me about money.
Tell me about career.
>> Right.
>> And then it
evolves from there.
But they started helping
me with my own stuff.
And that's kind
of like the carrot
to get us to keep channeling.
And that's also one
of the hardest things,
I think, for people, what
do I want to know about?
We've forgotten how to
formulate questions.
be curious, how to ask,
because we're so
conditioned just
to go along kind of mindlessly
making our way through our day.
>> Yeah.
>> So that's a big step
in working with them is
formulating your questions.
Because if you don't
ask, you don't get.
>> Right.
>> And it's one of
those tricky things.
It's like, well,
I don't know what
I don't know until I know it.
>> Right.
Yeah.
>> So where do I want to start?
What questions do I want to ask?
And what do I want to know
more about, especially when you
get to the more complex
questions, the bigger
universal questions--
>> Sure.
>> --because that can't be
revealed until you're ready
for it.
And once you formulate
the question,
that's kind of their
signal that you're ready
and they can give
more information.
>> Excellent.
Well, that's what we
want to get into today.
We have lots of questions
about the universal history
and story.
So right quick, before we
introduce the Pleiadians,
have you had any physical
contact in the light sense?
I mean, have you
seen these lights?
Have you had experiences
in that level?
>> With them, my strength
is as a clairsentient,
so I feel a lot of
things in my body.
I occasionally will see
things, as a clairvoyant,
literally seeing lights,
and auric fields,
and that kind of thing.
More of what I see in
the clairvoyant sense
is with my inner eye.
>> OK.
So like eyes closed and just--
>> Yeah, what I would
see in my mind's eye.
>> OK.
>> So when I do see them,
they're usually blue,
blue light.
Sometimes they have
geometric forms.
Sometimes triangles.
>> Hmm.
And so let me
clarify, so you can
see the geometric forms and
the lights, but you feel a--
almost like a human presence
or something like that?
How could you describe it?
>> I feel a frequency.
>> OK.
>> And yet, you could say
it's like a human presence.
>> OK.
>> It's like, well,
let's see, how can I--
>> Like I know my cameraman
here is standing here.
Is that--
>> Yes.
>> Is that a good analogy?
>> So you know what
his energy feels like.
>> Right.
>> And you wouldn't necessarily
have to turn around just
to know that that
person is standing--
>> Sure.
>> --behind you.
And they often
describe it as it's
like hearing somebody's
footsteps coming down the hall.
After a while, once you begin to
know what that person's energy
is like, what their
patterns are like,
you know who it is
by the sound of--
>> Of the footsteps.
>> --the footsteps,
>> Interesting.
>> --what the gait's like.
So it's kind of the
same thing with them.
I know it's them
when they show up.
Sometimes they show
up with other people.
And I can feel them,
but I know that they
brought other people along
because the frequency's
different.
And sometimes they're
making an introduction,
so they're beings that I
haven't worked with before.
>> And so when we say people,
we're talking about other light
beings?
>> Sometimes they're
light beings.
Sometimes they're physical.
Sometimes they're fifth
dimensional, sixth dimensional,
seventh dimensional.
And they do have bodies.
They're not as dense as ours,
but they do have physical form.
>> OK.
>> And I do work with
a variety of beings.
The Sirians that I work
with, they're physicals.
They're fifth dimensional.
But I don't necessarily
work with them
in a conscious way
where they're standing
physically in front of me.
It's more telepathic
communication
that I have with them, at
least in my waking hours.
>> And have you had physical
contact then with other beings,
non-light beings, body--
>> Yes.
>> OK.
So--
>> Sirians?
Or--
>> No.
Different beings.
Some of them are insectoids.
>> Oh, interesting.
>> And then the Zetas as well.
>> OK.
>> And those are my
physical experiences.
And another group who I just
recently had an introduction
to, I don't have all
the bits and pieces
as to who they are,
exactly, but they're
kind of a cross
between the insectoids
and what we would
traditionally call the grays.
They look different.
And it's not the same species.
But they've shown up for me.
>> Interesting.
Do you find once you've opened
yourself up to, let's say,
this channeling experience
back in the '90s--
was it '94 you said?
>> When I started,
it was in '94.
And I had kind of my
breakthrough in '95.
>> Do you think that has
opened the door to other being
experiences?
Or do you think we're all
getting these experiences
and we're just
not tuned into it?
>> Well, both.
I think we're all
connected to our guides.
We've got two guides that
are with us 24 hours a day,
7 days a week, who
are helping us.
And then we've got our
solicited friends--
>> Everybody?
>> Everybody.
>> Oh, OK.
>> And I laugh because people
think that channeling is just
something that a few people do.
But everybody does it.
And to me, it's like
being an interpreter.
I recognize frequency
and I translate it
into a recognizable form,
whether that's writing
or whether it's speaking.
But I think any form
of creative expression
can be a form of channeling.
And my own experiences
with beings, I think,
started much younger.
I think it started in childhood.
>> OK.
>> But I didn't really
have an awareness,
a conscious awareness of that
until I started opening up
in my early 20s.
And I started having some
past-life experiences.
And at the time, I
didn't really understand
that's what was going on.
I was accessing some
of that information.
So once I made
conscious contact,
then some of the things that
had happened earlier in my life
made a lot more sense.
I understood, oh,
that's what that was.
>> I see.
So you think if we all
could tap into this,
then this channeling
experience, or our guides,
humanity would be a little
less hectic or frantic maybe?
>> I think so.
>> Or more because now there's
so much more out there that
we're not aware of.
How about in your life--
I'm sure this could go on into a
much deeper conversation which,
hopefully, we can have later--
but quickly, by opening
yourself up to this
channeling experiences,
has it been a positive
influence in your life?
>> Oh, definitely.
>> OK.
>> Yeah.
Yeah.
I can't imagine not doing it.
To me, it's normal.
>> Got you.
>> And I always say it's
going to be the new normal--
>> Sure.
>> --because it's just expanding
the connection that's already
there.
We're never disconnected
from anyone or anything.
So it's just kind of opening
up to what's already around us
and using what's available
to us, the tools.
And I think the guides
are going to get into it--
and I'm already hearing they
are-- but part of it's
understanding why we're here
in 3D, the purpose of 3D,
the playground.
And its opening back up to
other potentials and other games
that we can also participate in.
>> Excellent.
Well, with that said, can
we introduce the Pleiadians?
>> Sure.
>> And can we start asking
some of those questions?
>> Sure.
>> Excellent.