If you're the type of person that
is only going outside and
sitting under the stars to
be able to
see a ship and have no
spiritual experience at all
but just be able to touch
the ship...
Then your consciousness is staying
in this level so to speak
below the spaces.
Now there's lots of UFO
hunters out there in the
world,
who are experiencing contact
from that perspective
but we can say it's not very
satisfying.
So when we do this work
with you
what we're doing
is helping to give you tools to
make it easier for you to pass through
those spaces between the film.
And when you pass through
and you move into a more
expanded reality, that's when
the weird stuff starts happening.
Stuff that doesn't adhere to the
definitions of physical reality
that can be exciting for some people,
it can be scary for others.
Ever wonder if there's intelligent
life elsewhere in the universe?
Well, I have....I've been wondering since I was a kid.
My name is Reuben Langdon.
And on March 29th 2007, in the middle of the day,
I saw a number of strange objects in the sky.
Coincidentally, I was working on
the film Avatar at the time, playing an alien.
And ever since then I've been on a quest...
A quest to find out if aliens really do exist and if so...
...are they here with us?
If beings of higher intelligence are here...
...what is their purpose?
Why don't they make themselves more known?
Why the secrecy?
I've asked these questions to many experts,
yet each seems to have a different theory.
So I thought to myself,
why not ask the aliens directly?
So that's what I set out to do!
Well, sort of...
>>  Um, we have...
I feel like, you know, again, looking in
our sky we have, you know, we have
the Draconian way of doing things, we
have the Pleiadian way of doing things,
the Sirian way of doing things,
the Sassani,  the Yahyel, the ... You know, all
of these different ways.  And, and ,
>> Because you know, when
you're, when you're looking at
consciousness as it is expressed
in 3rd density or even early 4th
density, you can still see the idea of
separate paths - the Draconian
way or the Pleiadian way or the Sirian way.
>> Right.
>>But actually as you move farther and
farther into 4th density, the paths
become a big... a much wider road
that contains them all, and that's when
you start to see the path has always
been the same, it just was shaped and
smelled differently, so to speak...
but it's always been the same path.
>>So in your guys' evolution.... state right
now, you sort of just are maybe
more awoken to that idea, that the path is
the same and therefore it...
>> It doesn't matter...
>> And our perception it may look like we
have all these choices...
>> Exactly...
>> but in reality we're just going to end
up going the one that we're gonna feel
excited about.
>> Exactly, and of course my reality
structure is very different, so when
children are born in my world we know
right away what their path is, what their
highest excitement is, as you've said.
And that is nurtured, and the child is
taught from a very young age to
express that, and this is one of the
reasons why in the contact work we do,
we often bring children for the contact work with
humans, because those in our society who
will be the future ambassadors of
contact on many worlds,
display those talents and those joys very early on.
>> So you're not forcing everybody to be
a doctor and a lawyer?
>> No,
(laughs)
>> exactly, exactly.
>> And I feel like we're moving out of that.
>> You are moving out of that.  We know
it doesn't look that way, but you are.
>> When it comes to working with all
these different energies,
and in past channelings you've talked
about the Association of Worlds.
>> Yes.
And is your society part of this Association?
>> Yes, yes.
And is...?
>> It's not like Star Trek.
>> It's not quite like Star Trek, no.
But Star Trek is a wonderful metaphor for
you to understand it.
>> Right, I get it.
And in the Association, you've
sort of moved out of
battling and wars, and you can't really be
part of the Association if
you have that sort of
dominating enslavement idea?
>> Yes, however... forgive us for being picky
but we're going to just be picky
about the words.
It's not a matter of "You
can't be in our club,"
>> Okay.
...so to speak.
Literally those who are still in
3rd density still experiencing
battles and conflicts
simply don't resonate with
the idea that we are.
>> Okay.
And would this be the same
with higher density Draconian
densities that are, sort of, again,
battling out the Orion war idea?
Are they...?  Did the Association of Worlds
exist during the Orion wars?
>> It was in a different form.
>> Okay.
Because the Orion wars were
really so very long ago,
>> Right.
and because of that the only
"elder species" were few and far between.
>> Oh, I see.
>>But it was... they did
have a version of it,
but even then, it was the
very clear idea that
you cannot interfere,
because all 3rd density species have to
go through their process, and...
>> So was the Orion wars
primarily a 3rd density event?
>> Yes.
It was a 3rd density event,
and it also carried
over into the beginning phases of 4th
density as well...
>> I see...
Until it became impossible to
maintain the separation any longer.
>>  I see.
Yeah, and again so going
back to the densities,
The idea of higher density
versions of different races
and I'm gonna...
I keep bringing up the
Draconians because I feel
there's a lot of resonance
with that archetypal energy
right now on planet earth,
because we are, we have
such a mixed bag of that
and we all, you know
the reptilian DNA is in us,
if I'm correct? And we are
working through those...
that karma so to say.
Karma in a different way...
>> Yes.
... than we're familiar with.
So at these higher density
versions of Draconian energy,
do they still hold those same archetypes
that we're familiar with
in 3rd density?
>> No.
No.
You're going to find that
the idea of "battling" ...
>> Yes
>>It wears itself out in the
early phases of 4th density.
>> Okay.
>>So when you're talking about
higher-level Draconian
consciousness, it has gone
more into deep
unconditional love.
>> Mmm, okay.
So if you go to a 6th - 7th
density Draconian being,
vast differences between...
>> Oh, yes...
>>between the 3rd density
version.
>> Yes, vast differences.
>> Okay.
Probably we can't even
conceptualize what that is?
>> Exactly.
But it's still,  it's a very
unique evolutionary path
very separate from
the Pleiadian perspective.
>> Yes, exactly.
>>  I see.
I've gotten this download.
I had a visitation from a
Mantis being...
and this goes into...
The download that I got I'm still trying
to digest, and maybe you
can help me with this?
Is that the Draconian energy was
sort of wanting to experience itself,
wanted to evolve past 6th or 7th
density.  That the Draconians, that
energy archetype, sort of had a hard time
going past that density,
that version of existence
because of its grasping
onto a physical form.
>>To us
because the 4th density
is the last...
>> Oh, that's right!
...in the way we measure
>>There is, once you move into 5th,
6th, or 7th there
no longer is physical bodies.
>> Okay.
>>Now there have been many species who
tried very hard to cling to
physicality and not move
into the non-physical expression
in 5th density.
>> Maybe that?
>> It could be that...
>> That version.
I guess the main thing I got and I sort of
assumed because of my
understanding of densities,
but the main thing I got was
the Draconian energy,
because of it's resistance to
go into a non-physical reality,
but there was still a portion
of that energy that wanted
to move in to that...
>> Yes.
...energy. Therefore it called upon the
Mantis beings to help move,
help design a plan,
and that's sort of what
humanity was, is,
is a plan to help move that
consciousness into
a non-physical reality, evolution.
I don't know if that makes any sense?
>> Well you, but you brought something
up that is very key here.
>> Okay.
And you're calling
them Mantis beings.
>> Sure.
>>We call them Founders, same idea and
if we can...
we'll just give you our
definition of them from
the bigger picture.
>> Mmm-um
>>So when the one consciousness
began its fragmentation
that eventually became the souls
that have the individual lives.
One of the first fragments from the Source
was a collective, beings that we call
Founders, that are kind of the architects.
>> Mmm - um
>>and when humans feel or
perceive their energy,
they see them as Mantis or
insectoid,
that's one of the ways they appear.
>> Right.
>>Another way they appear are
the very tall willowy beings that...
>> Was this Barbara Lamb's ...?
>> Yes, the spring onion beings,
Founder beings.
>> Perfect, okay that
ok, makes sense now.
>> Yes, and so these beings
known as the architects,
are overseeing so to speak
the building of the structure
of the physical stage play,
let's say, and so whenever
a civilization or a species
gets "in trouble", so to speak,
we have a tendency to call them for guidance.
>>  Okay.
>>The Orions did, the Pleiades did,
the Sirians did, the Zetas did,
the Dracos did.
>>  Right okay,
yeah, the Zetas, I got that too that...
Did the Zetas even have the
technology to travel
inter-dimensionally to our timeline?
I don't ... I got that the Mantis
helped out with that a little bit.
>> Yes.
Zetas though are...
they are quite unique as
you well know, and because they were able
to harness such intense
energy of mentality
they could do things in terms
of the traveling through time lines that
no other species could do.
>> Oh really, okay.
So that's one of the reasons
why too they could do that.
>> Fascinating.
And these Mantis beings often
in abduction scenarios,
temporary detainment scenarios,
show up sort of in the background.
>> Yes, exactly.
>>And so I'm assuming this
is probably why,
and seen with many different races too.
Oh, there's a Mantis being
with a Pleiadian, or...
That is why, they're like overseers.
>> Fascinating.
And not in a controlling way of course.
>> And are they in a specific
density or they sort of can
manifest in any density depending
on who's in trouble?
Well, we say primarily
7th density because
even though they're manifesting
seemingly as "a being"
it's really a collective.
So they cannot manifest
physically, which is one of the
reasons why in a sense,
now we're using this figuratively,
they could "channel through"
more physical beings.
So if you have Zetas
accompanied by a Mantis,
it's not that the Mantis
is physically there,
but the human is perceiving the energy,
and can interpret it.
>> Right, yeah, my
sort of download was not a physical
interaction, it was more of a data drop.
>> Exactly.
At least that's the way it felt.
It's very, very unique and I've...
to date it's been my really only
conscious interaction with
an extraterrestrial presence
in that sense.
Well, how many
days do you have in Sedona coming up?
(laughs)
Hmm, we'll see about that.
>> Alright, very cool.
There's a lot of talk about
inner earth beings,
especially recently, it's sort of
been in the consciousness, there's been a
whistleblower who's been talking about
interaction with inner earth beings
and we're finding out this new
history that these beings have been
there for millions of years
pre-dating humanity and, sort of,
staying low key.
Now, are they, those beings
4th density beings?
3rd, 4th density beings or...?
>> Mostly 4th density beings.
>> Okay.
There are some that are 5th
density so they're
not necessarily perceived as
solid objects in space, but
as light energy, and they're much like what
we said about the Anunnaki, they're really
a collective, a collective of races.
>> Okay.
So yes, so there's many
different races...
in the inner earth.
>> Yes
And because at different
densities, different frequencies,
if for example, are we only
now able to perceive them
because we're shifting into this
fourth density?
>> Yes, yes.
>>And if we were to try let's say
in our past timelines of
3rd density,  even a hundred years ago,
if we were to try to burrow into the earth
and try to find these beings,
we would just hit rocks per se?
>> You would not really have
the contact except in
the cases of those spontaneous moments
of openness, where you're actually not
digging, so to speak, but you're
open to the contact.
So when Admiral Bird flew over
the North Pole and saw the
big hole and in, you know, then
we have all these lores
of and stories of journey
to the center of the earth.
>>  Yes.
You know these these sorts of stories.
>> Yes
So that was just because the
heart space was in the right
space to go into that.
>> And the timing and
many many things...
Nexus point of timelines
many things,
but not necessarily repeatable.
>> Okay.
Once the ego gets involved, yes?
>> Right.
Do you guys interact with
those 4th density beings?
>> Yes there are certain ones
that we do because, you know, humans
this is not aimed at you of course, but
humans have a tendency of thinking they
are the only things
walking the earth, yes?
>> Right.
But the earth is quite populated
on many levels of other dimensions,
and in the ancient times
because there were so
many beings on the planet,
and during the times when
those groups left, many stayed
behind and began to
build their own colonies.
So you have especially one very
populated colony is what
we would call Sirians,
ancient Sirians that stayed and
experience their ascension process here...
>> Oh, wow...
... on your planet.
And very often they're seen as blue.
>> Okay.
And on one... so on a specific density
reality they're there.  Yes.  And they...
>> Yes.
>>And they... do they coexist with us?
>> They do?
>> Yes, and when you are in the space in
your consciousness to connect
with them you most certainly can.
We've spoke to many who have.
>>  Okay, and do you work with them?
>> Sometimes, yes.
>> Okay.
Especially when we're
doing contact work in areas
where they are active and
they actually tend to be
active in seismically active places.
>> Oh, okay.
>> Volcanic areas.
>> So their origin is Sirius,
but then they migrated
to Earth at some point in our history?
>> Their ancestors came here when the
Sirians were here and some of them stayed.
Some of them also... now of course in
the cosmology that we've presented, the
Sirian beings, the Orion beings, the Zeta beings,
they all come from Vega lineage.
>> Okay.
So the very, very ancient Vegas who
colonized Mars, also some stayed behind
came to Earth as well, so that's why
we say there's a mix.
>> I see.
So is Vega sort of our elders?
>> Yes...
>> In that sense?
>> Yes.
>> What is most known in your galactic
family is what we call Vegan Mysticism,
which is a school of spirituality that
was birthed in Vega millions and
millions and millions of years ago, that
passed to the different civilizations in
your galactic family and
also seeded on Earth.
So the seeds of it on Earth most
specifically you see within some of the
ancient Sanskrit and Hindu times.
>> Oh, okay.
And various seeds around the world so
it's quite prolific, Vegan Mysticism.
And do... going back to
the Sirians, did they...?
Were they around during the time of Atlantis?
The ones that stayed here on Earth?
>> Yes, they were.
And so Atlantis... was Atlantis...
I assume it was a mixed density bag of tricks?
>> Yes, mixed density bag and mixed
density... Sorry, and mixed... >>Races?  >>No, a mixed
drama going on.
>> Okay,
lots of things going on.
>> Lots of things going on,
and all of us, most of us
I guess humans have had
experiences from or
simultaneous lifetimes there...
>> Yes...
>> That we're working through that karma now?
>> Yes.
>>And so the Sirians were there
and they...
and then that sort
of event happened,
cataclysms things like this?
>>All sorts of things.
>>And if it happened in
3rd density reality
did it also happen in these other...?
If if there's mixed densities
interacting with each other
did it happen across the density board,
the cataclysms, the destruction?
>> Ah, we see what you're asking.
Well when we say "mixed densities"
we have to define that.
>> Okay
>> Right now on Earth you
have mixed densities,
even though it's not...
you don't see it.
>> Yeah no, we do, we have the,
the low end of the 3rd,
and the high end of the 3rd,
and the low end of the 4th.
>> Exactly and even... and you have 5th
density versions of yourselves and 6th
because again it's the concentric... it's
the boxes, the concentric nesting boxes.
So in the Atlantean time, physically
speaking you did have a mix of 3rd and
4th density beings in a sense
populating the same space-time,
but you also had the other
non-physical influences as well, so...
And lots of different dramas because
everyone was playing out whatever it was
they needed to play out for their own
evolution.  So it was one of those nexus
points of evolution that were very
important to, let's say,
show you the
trajectory for the next
phase of your evolution.
Because you could have, as a
species, shifted at that time.
So I was wondering in our
native cultures, in the past,
we have had--
across the world we've had,
obviously, we've had pyramids,
and we've had native
cultures with high ideals.
Native American Indians,
Peruvian, Amazonian tribes
that have really, when
we look at it now,
a highly evolved sense
of being and way of life.
>> Yes.
>> Were those cultures,
where those beings,
at a higher density?
Were they fourth density?
>> Well.
>> Or were they still third?
>> It depends on the era.
>> OK.
>> Because civilizations
have a tendency--
physical civilizations will
have a tendency of cycling from
third to fourth density,
sometimes repeating it.
>> OK.
>> Until the time is
right for the shift.
>> I see.
>> OK.
But you're going to find that
with the indigenous species
on your planet, or
the indigenous races,
excuse us, on your planet that
even though they are halfway
around the world
from each other,
your struck by the similarities.
>> Correct.
>> And pyramids and practices
and things such as that.
Two main reasons for this.
One is because of the
ET influence, of course.
Another is because a lot of
those structures and practices
came from Vegan mysticism,
which came to Earth from Mars,
originally.
>> OK.
>> So that's why there is--
if you could really see
the history of
your solar system,
you would see the continuity.
>> Right, the linear--
>> And then, going all
the way back to Vega.
>> I see.
So the Vegans, did
they colonize Mars?
>> Yes.
>> They colonized
Mars very early on.
They colonized Mars
well before the Earth
was even stable for colonies.
>> Oh, OK.
And the destruction of Mars--
I've heard that there was--
some say there was
a nuclear event.
There was-- where--
or is that just because of
the density that we're in,
we perceive it that way?
>> Yes.
Actually, we've given
a session on this,
but Germane, who
gave the session,
has never really spoken
specifically about it.
However, what he has said
is that there were a--
there was a series of events.
Some were cataclysmic
with asteroids and things
such as that.
Some were political.
Some things-- so everything, a
perfect storm, you might say.
>> I see.
There's the idea or
the talk of Maldek
being a planet within
our solar system
that now makes up
the Kuiper Belt.
>> Yes, yes.
Similar history to Mars.
>> OK.
I was going to say, did Mars
come after the destruction of--
did Mars-- does destruction--
>> It was parallel.
>> Parallel, OK.
>> Yes.
>> And then, our moon, did
it come from the Maldek
civilization?
Or is that-- because I've
heard different variations
of the moon being
artificial, put into place.
>> It's not artificial, per
se, but it's been, let's say,
terraformed.
>> Terraformed.
OK.
>> Yes.
>> Was it native to our planet?
Or was it sort of put there?
>> It was not native.
Let's say, it was a wanderer.
>> OK.
A wanderer and it
found its position.
>> Yes.
>> And it fixed.
>> OK.
Was there-- so is
it its own celestial
being with consciousness?
>> Yes.
>> Light?
>> When we think of artificial,
we think that there's been some
sort of outside manipulation--
>> Yes.
>> --done to it.
>> But even that outside
artificial manipulation,
in a way, is still part
of that consciousness.
>> Yes.
>> Like Earth right now, we're
making genetically-modified
foods and chemically enhancing
and doing all kinds of things.
But it's still
naturally artificial.
[LAUGHING]
>> There you go.
Yes.
It doesn't mean
it's not harmful--
>> Right.
>> --necessarily.
But, you know, it's the whole
idea of what consciousness is.
Consciousness
permeates everything,
so can you ever take a slice
and make it not consciousness?
No.
>> I see.
>> It's just a difference of
whether it's dormant or aware
of itself or not.
Now, in terms of
planets, however--
>> Yes.
>> --and especially suns, you're
going to find that what you
call the core of the planet
or the sun is an entry point--
exit and entry
point, dimensionally.
So this is why celestial
bodies have consciousness.
Because the consciousness,
literally the consciousness
of creation, breathes
itself in and out
through those
portals in the center
of the core of whether
it's a sun or a planet.
So-- and we're talking--
you know, we're not
necessarily talking
about a rock flying in space.
>> Right.
>> We're talking more about
a planetary body that even
perhaps has a slight
gravitational field.
>>That doesn't
necessarily mean the size
of the--
>>Yes it's not really
dictated by size.
>> OK.
>> Because gravity has much
more to it than just the size
factor.
>> OK.
And--
>> More often than not,
you'll see the correlation.
>> OK.
>> But it doesn't mean one
is caused by the other.
>> OK.
That's what I thought.
And in our sun's case,
as you were saying,
it's sort of a portal
and we're getting--
that's our life
force is the sun.
Now, if we were to move
to another solar body
galaxy, or solar system, and--
would we then shift our being?
Would we no longer become human?
Would we become a new--
because now we're getting
our energy downloads
from a new celestial being,
would we become a new species?
>> OK.
So this is definitely
hypothetical.
>> Yes.
>> Because at this point,
humans cannot go and try out--
>> Sure.
>> And try it out, yes.
And also because
of the limitation
of human consciousness to
traverse space right now.
Because right now,
human consciousness
is tied to the
gravitational field
of its planet and its sun.
And this is a metaphor--
a macrocosmic metaphor
for how the ego is the
anchor for you on a planet.
>> OK.
Because the ego is
like a black hole.
Same function, so to speak.
However, as you move into fourth
density, deeper and deeper
into fourth density, and
the anchor that is ego
and individuality becomes
metaphorically lighter,
therefore, you're
able, in a sense,
to escape the
gravitational field
and not be influenced
so much by it.
So space travel becomes
no longer traveling
on the surface of space.
It, instead, becomes
traveling through space
or becoming one with space in
a very, very different way.
So we had to lay that
groundwork in order
to answer your question.
>> Sure.
OK.
>> Right now, if you were to be
picked up and taken to another
planet in another solar
system, it would be very,
very hard to make
the adaptation.
>> OK.
But if you were more
deeper into fourth density
in terms of your evolution, thus
your egoic anchor was lighter,
it would be easier for you
to go through a metamorphosis
if you were planted, so to
speak, in another solar system.
It would be easier.
>> And is that--
going to the hybrid
programs for the Zetas--
is that-- part of that
creating new beings, so to say,
and populating new planets
and new star systems,
or new solar systems,
with new DNA?
>> Yes.
It's one of the reasons
why hybridization
is the better chosen
method than colonization.
>> I see.
>> Unless the circumstances
are such that where
you're colonizing
is very similar--
>> Right.
>> --hybridization is
much more appropriate,
which is why the original Lyrans
in the very ancient times began
the programs on Earth,
the genetic work on Earth,
because they needed to
create that hybridization
for their future incarnations.
Colonization was not
a comfortable option.
>> I see.
So when we even--
what if it was within
our solar system,
like Mars, if we were to
go to Mars or go to Venus?
Is that a--
>> It would be easier.
However-- and again, we're
speaking metaphorically.
This is basically-- we're going
to make this simple so you
understand, but let's say that--
let's say each of the
planets represents
an energy of a chakra, OK?
Earth being solar plexus chakra.
Let's say, then, that you
moved to another planet that
represents another chakra.
Basically, what you're
going to experience
is a similar structure, but
the aspects of that chakra
will need to come into play--
>> I see.
>> --more or be activated more.
And that's the kind
of the system--
the macrocosmic system
in a given solar system.
>> I see.
And if we were to do
that, we would need,
probably, technology
to aid in that life
force sustaining, you know, not
just air and everything else,
but, energetically, we would--
>> Yes.
>> --either have to do it--
do the work ourselves or have
an external technology.
>> Yes, but, actually, we see
that the most important thing
you would need to colonize a
moon of Jupiter or whatever is
actually mentors,
extraterrestrial mentors.
>> I see.
To help--
>> To help.
>> --with--
>> Yep.
>> --explain more than what
we physically know right now.
>> Exactly.
>> Because we only see such
as a small sliver of what is.
>> Exactly.
>> I See.
>> And that can
help out with that.
>> Yes.
>> Now, you know, I've heard
stories that humanity has
a breakaway civilization of a
secret space program, per se,
that we've been--
individuals from humanity
in the '50s and '60s
worked together to sort of start
colonizing our solar system.
>> Yes.
>> And started
doing this already.
And a lot of this whistleblower
stuff is coming out now.
And we're sort of
being made aware.
And then, hopefully, we can join
our own family back with us.
But they had--
I guess, they did have Draconian
assistance in their evolution
to colonize.
Is that-- am I
correct in saying that?
>> Well, we're going to say
there's truth and distortion.
>> OK.
Now, when truth
starts coming out,
there is a whole
faction on your world
that works very hard
to distort the truth
through sensationalistic things,
or red herrings, as you say.
So there is also a lot of that.
The researchers, themselves,
having good intentions
are given very, what seems to be
for them, credible information,
that isn't really credible.
So the truth gets
buried at another layer.
>> Sure.
>> So there is a lot
of different things.
This is why we don't talk
so much about this stuff.
It's also not our
mission, so to speak.
>> Sure, sure.
>> However, we can say,
just very basically, yes,
secret space programs.
Yes, the powers that
be, if you will,
are quite aware
that Mars was once
a thriving
civilization, that there
are things happening on the
moon, et cetera, et cetera.
>> OK.
Very good.
We don't need to go
into any more details.
>> Yes.
Not our forte.
>> Not yet.
Not until-- it'll all
develop in the way
it's supposed to develop.
>> Yes.
The Japanese energy
healing Reiki.
Lyssa told me the mountain
to go to where I can
find where it was developed.
But was that--
I think the founder even
said it came from the cosmos.
>> Yes.
>> It was downloaded to him
through this sort of cosmic
energy.
Did that come from a specific
star system or some beings?
>> Yes.
Again, we very often use some
of the star names as archetypes.
But we see that the--
well, the legends
of Mount Kurama--
>> Yes.
>> --which is the mountain
we're talking about in Kyoto,
are that.
Beings from Venus--
>> OK.
>> --originally, two
million years ago,
came to that mountain.
Now, the question then is,
did the founder of Reiki
tap into Venus energy?
We would say that Venus, itself,
is a portal through which
other cosmic energy can come.
We see the Reiki energy as
being much more connected
to Arcturist energy.
>> Oh, OK.
>> It's very, very balanced
and very powerful in its
simplicity.
>> Mm-hmm.
And is that a representation,
then, of Arcturus, is
balance and simple?
>> Balance, simple.
You have also termed
it the angelic realm.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> It's a realm of--
>> OK, I see.
>> --integration where mental,
emotional, male, female,
et cetera, is all balanced.
It is also an energy that
is very easy for humans
to tap into when they
allow themselves to do so.
>> I've heard analogies.
They're like the
Jedis in Star Wars.
You know, the Arcturians,
they're sort of always
wearing robes and
sort of in that--
>> While, that's
how they're seen.
Yes.
>> How they're perceived.
How we perceive them
as, sort of masters.
>> Because mostly they
are sixth density,
so they're not physical
in that way any longer.
>> Very masterful.
And even, I've heard throughout
our galaxy and universe,
many other beings
sort of go there to do
pilgrimages and homework and--
>> Yes.
>> You know, and go to--
Sasha, have you been
to Arcturian system
to do some study and work?
Or--
>> Well, in my time
frame, the, you might say,
high Arcturian
civilization is long gone.
>> Oh.
OK.
>> Because they have gone into
they're ascension process.
>> Oh, I see.
OK.
>> So when people are
talking about that,
they are talking about--
again, we're going
off the timelines--
>> Sure.
>> --a past era--
>> Right.
>> --of the civilization.
>> When there was a
physical version to visit.
>> Yes.
>> I see.
I'm not sure if it was
you who mentioned this, but--
the Sirius energy, the way
they-- sort of their evolution
is they tapped into
their emotional body
through their mental
pineal gland direction.
>> Yes.
>> You know, and that was sort
of their evolutionary state.
Took them a while.
But through the
mental body, they
were actually able to access
their emotional bodies.
>> Yes.
They took the back door.
>> They took the back door.
Which is fascinating.
And you know, I see so many
similarities in humanity
where we get very mental.
>> Yes.
>> And I was wondering--
I've been working a lot with the
Amazonian medicine, ayahuasca.
And the chemical compound, which
induces a psychedelic trance
state, is DMT,
dimethyltryptamine,
which is very--
I see it very third eye
going into that state.
And that's sort of resonated
when I heard that download
because it feels that's
a similar path using
this medicine in a mental way to
connect to the emotional body.
>> Yes.
It's similar to the work the
Sirians did, but with a booster
rocket.
>> With a booster--
so they-- the ayahuasca
is the booster rocket?
>> The ayahuasca is
the booster rocket.
>> OK.
>> The Sirians, being that
their lineage is Vegan,
are very hard core.
And they didn't--
for most of the time,
didn't like to use help--
>> Sure.
>> --so to speak.
But humans like
shortcuts sometimes.
And we don't mean that
in any way disrespectful.
>> Right.
>> But it's like a booster
rocket for the same idea.
>> I see.
>> If it's used
properly, of course.
>> Right.
And the energy of
the ayahuasca spirit
that the shamans speak of,
this Grandmother Earth energy,
that's the way I've
always seen her,
is this almost a collective
unconditional love,
Mother Earth energy.
>> Yes.
>> That being, I was wondering
on a galactic scale--
how do the other ET races
interact with that energy?
Do they interact?
And is that part of--
is that part of the Earth's
collective consciousness?
>> It is part of the Earth's
collective consciousness.
And it goes back to some of what
we were talking about in terms
of how every planet, every
sun has its own consciousness.
>> OK.
>> And so from the point of
view of an ET, such as myself,
whenever we come to a planet
to do any type of work
as an offering or as a service,
we have to get permission from
that collective consciousness.
>> I see.
>> First and foremost.
So you, as humans, are
moving toward this as well,
in terms of recognizing
your own planet as a living
consciousness.
And of course, once you
do, everything changes.
>> Oh, I already have.
And tapping into that energy
is-- it's so beautiful.
And I'm working
with the medicine
and working with the shamans
and our indigenous cultures who
have been working with this
energy for thousands of years.
>> Thousands of years.
>> With or without the medicine.
You know, the medicine is
just a permission slip--
>> Exactly.
>> --to talk to this energy.
But it's so beautiful.
And I'm just assuming that
that collective energy
is interacting with the
Pleiadian collective energies
on--
and other Sirian collectives--
>> Yes.
>> --on a greater
galactic scale of--
>> Yes.
We have to.
We have to do it that way.
>> So with that--
would she be part of the
Association of Worlds?
>> Yes.
Yes.
>> I see.
Interesting.
OK, well, thank you so much.
>> Now that we hear the
wheels going with that one.
>> Oh, there's so more.
I know I could go on forever.
But I want to honor
everybody's time.
And we've got lots of
great stuff to share here.
So thank you so
much for everything.
I'll leave it open just for
one last thing, if Sasha
wants to share anything for me.
I've heard that maybe--
>> My brother.
Yes.
>> I heard that--
I heard that earlier.
So--
>> There is another you in
my time stream, my dear.
And he is much more
flamboyant than you.
It's a he.
>> Flamboyant?
>> Flamboyant, actually.
In a-- we don't--
maybe not what you're imagining.
>> OK.
>> He doesn't wear rainbow
streamers or anything.
>> OK.
>> But he's very
excited and gregarious,
even more than you
are as a human.
And whenever he-- he's involved
a lot in some of the contact
work, in general,
introducing planets--
new planets to the
galactic community.
And whenever he is present, he,
let's say, lightens the mood.
Not that it's ever
a somber mood.
>> Sure.
>> But it's always he's always
a welcome invite to a party,
let's say.
>> Excellent, excellent.
>> So just tap into that
and see what you can get.
>> I would--
I always love parties.
>> Excellent.
>> And lightening the mood.
So that's very much so.
I resonate with that.
Does he have a name?
>> Let's see.
Again, of course, it would
have to be translated
into an English concept.
>> OK.
>> No, of course.
We are receiving Japanese.
>> Oh.
>> Or Japanese sound, at least.
>> Sure.
>> We have the
first two syllables.
Just a moment.
HARUKI
>> Oh, very nice.
Nice to know.
>> Recognizing that that
is not really his name,
much as Sasha is not my name.
>> Sure.
OK.
>> But energetically--
>> Yes.
>> --a close vibrational match.
>> OK.
>> Yes.
>> Well, thank you for the
very stimulating conversation.
We have enjoyed it quite much.
And thank you, Ronald,
also, for your energy.
>> Yes.
>> We can feel you over there.
And then, for now,
we wish you much--
first of all, much
excitement on your journey
and good luck with the project.
>> Thank you.
>> Much luck.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[LAUGHING]
>> Holy crap.
>> How was that?
>> Wow.
>> Yeah.
Time flew by.
>> It flew by.
Totally.
[MUSIC PLAYING]