Animals are and have always been
offering their love and vibrational
support to assist humankind.
They can show us how to love
and how to live in harmony,
and balance with Mother Earth.
The whales and the dolphins have
been singing their songs to help to
awaken humanity, and they've been
doing this for a very long time.
Also, our dogs, our cat friends,
horse friends and all other beings,
are offering us unconditional love.
They teach us about unconditional love.
Now, light language can uplift
us during these challenging days.
It bypasses the mind and the ego.
It nourishes our mind, our body,
our emotions, and our soul.
It brings us back to our hearts, our body,
our soul and light language can actually
shift us into feeling calmer and bring
us back into alignment with ourselves.
We need to remember that we're
all beautiful, amazing souls,
and we need to remember to be
in our power and to listen to our hearts.
And this is a profound period
of awakening for humankind.
Ever wonder if there's intelligent
life elsewhere in the universe?
Well, I have.
I've been wondering since I was a kid.
My name is Ruben Langdon. And on March
29th 2007, in the middle of the day.
I saw a number of strange objects
in the sky.
Coincidentally, I was working on the
film Avatar at the time, playing an
alien. And ever since then I've been on
a quest.  A quest to find out if aliens really do
exist, and if so, are they here with us?
If beings of higher
intelligence are here,
what is their purpose?
Why don't they make themselves more known?
Why the secrecy?
I've asked these questions to
many experts, yet each seems
to have a different theory.
So I thought to myself, why
not ask the aliens directly?
So that's what I set out to do.
Well sort of...
Yeah, when I
was one of the experiences I had
one of the first one where, I.
When I was waking up in before I
was waking up at 14 or it was 15.
Really?
And at that point it was crazy
cuz I was in the UFO club.
I'm going like, way back then
there was like a UFO club and I
was like in it not knowing why.
And that was when Project
Blue Book and... >>Yeah.
>>And when my childhood was not, we'll
say idyllic and and I just remember
being very upset and angry about my
parents and that's teenage stuff anyway.
But I was sitting on my bed
just yelling and saying, get
me the hell out here you guys.
I said, I wish you UFO
would come and take me away.
Not knowing at that time..  >>The connection.
>>Within a week I went in my backyard and
above the woods in our backyard, midday
blue sky, a silver disc came, sh, came
shot down, was just above the trees.
That's how close it was.
>>Wow.
>>And it stayed there.
And I'm go like, oh my God.
I'm like, and it did all these
angles, which has a meaning for me.
It did all these crosses and not
crosses in the Christian sense.
But, and and then they had actually I
didn't recall this till later, but they
took me on ship starting to prepare
me to have hybrid children, but,
but when I watched the ship
leave, I've never seen anything
spin away so fast in my life.
I could see it, it was clear
blue sky, and I went, oh my God.
I called them in and what the heck
did I really wanna go and leave?
And then I, maybe I need to change my mind
here right about this, and careful for it.
Rethink this, yeah.
But that was an amazing experience for me.
>>Wow.
>>Just amazing
>>I'm sorry, how
old were you at that time?
>>Four, fifteen.
>>Fifteen?
Okay.
>>Yeah.
>>Amazing.
>>So that one really left its mark,
and since then you've just been...
>>Ever since then I've been
on the UFO track.
Really,
yeah, definitely.
Every book, every... just it's
almost like an obsession, but...
it's because -  from the subconscious
that you're just trying to put,
to put it together.
>>Yeah.
>>Understand that
that's where who we are.
>>That's where I think
where we come
in.
Because, when I first woke up
there was this, I was at work.
I was at work, and this
guy comes up to me, right?
And it's odd...
This guy comes up to me and he has two
pieces of paper in his handwriting.
They're like little, they're little
tiny flyers with just some conspiracy
theories written on him, like FEMA
camps and UFOs, and just think, I
wish I had signed that piece of paper.
>>Yeah.
>>But anyways this guy comes in,
he has two pieces of paper and
he says, Hey, I want some, I got
something for you to check out.
And he hands me this piece of paper
and I look at it and I'm like, oh,
I've heard of this stuff before.
And he just smirks at me like,
and then my coworker is oh, do you
have an extra one of those paper?
So he's yeah, I do.
Hands over the second paper,
which is the exact same thing.
It's almost like he knew already
that she was gonna ask for it.
So he was ready, walks off.
I never see or hear from him again.
He just dis, he just walks off.
And so I let it sit for a while and
I thought, okay, I'll, I got sick and
I was bored and I thought, okay, I'll
check this paper out, check it out,
and I was like, oh my goodness,
there's something to this ya know?
There's something going on here.
And I remember just getting scared cuz
when you start reading up on this, you
have the, it's the whole fear thing.
All the world's going, Nibiru's coming and
the world's gonna end and tie waves know?
Yes.
And earthquakes and volcanoes and
all hell's gonna break loose, right?
And I'm like, oh in 2012,
cause this happened in 2009,
2012's gonna be here.
And I'm just like, oh my God.
But then the first craft comes in Jan,
oh, was it let's see, 4th of July.
Yes, 4th of July.
And I remember, seeing this
little tiny satellite in this sky.
And I'm like going, okay, for
something, zigzag, zigzag and nothing.
Later that night, my wife
and I go outside, oh, I was
smoking cigarettes at the time.
Let's go out.
It was like one in the morning.
All the fireworks were done.
Let's go out and smoke cigarette.
And next thing we know
here's that satellite again.
And next thing I know it's.
50 yards away from us, and
it was this golden disc.
And it'd play with us because
when we wouldn't look at it, it'd
turn on and it would move and
then we'd look it, turn off, and
then we're like, did you see that?
What was that?
And then we'd look away.
It's like turns on goes and then
turns, look, turn off and all of a
sudden it just turns off and boom goes
to space, and I was like, oh shit.
I just saw, I was like, I just saw
something, finally I saw something.
>>Yeah.
>>And at that moment, your
life is completely changed.
>>It's, yeah...
>>And I remember I just got
obsessed at that moment.
I was obsessed like, okay, now
I need to find out what was
that, what on Earth was that?
And I just re, I'd done thousands
of hours of research to my wife.
It's you're just getting away too obsessed
with this, and I'm like look what we saw.
Yeah.
And that's when the experience started.
My memory of experiences
started happening.
So I started saying, I need to see a ship.
I need to see a ship.
I need to see something.
I need confirmation.
This is happening to me.
And then we have that 45 minute encounter.
It was I'll give you just a brief.
My, my wife and I were sitting in
the house her mom, we were living
at her mom's house at the time.
Her mom goes to the grocery store.
It was December 20th 2009.
And it was about seven
o'clock in the evening.
So it was just dark,
and her mom takes off.
I go to make a phone call, the
phones are dead and go out.
Yeah, let's go outside.
Smoke.
Here's this smoking again.
But I've quit since then.
But I look up and here
cuz this blue light just.
Pops up in the sky, it
looks like a bar of light.
And just neon blue, I can't even
really describe it because the color
doesn't exist in the, on this planet.
And then another light turns on, so it's
like this big bar and then a little bar.
And it was a 45 minute in interaction,
this thing just zipping around
doing the most crazy things.
>>Wow.
And your wife's saw it as well?
>>Yeah, exactly.
And like I was saying, I was freaked out.
You like, oh my God, what is this thing?
And it flies over us and this blue
plasma turns off and, you know
what a, like these canister lights,
the canister lights like these?
It had three, like a triangle.
Three.
>>Okay.
>>So 1, 2, 3 of them.
>>It was a black triangle?
>>Purple.
>>Purple, okay.
A dark purple.
And then two two sets
of three in the front.
So two sets of three.
And
three sets of three in the back.
Inside the canister is a pyramid.
It's a black crystal pyramid with a,
the best I can describe it was a black
hole at the very tip of the pyramid.
And then when they turn it on, all
of a sudden this blue plasma starts
circling around the black hole
and then starts leaking out and
then circling around the others.
And it's like floating
on this blue plasma.
And when it flies over, it's like a,
it was like a amethyst crystal ship.
It's seamless and had these
just weird designs on it.
And the things that it
did was just mind numbing.
>>It's amazing.
>>It was an overcast sky.
At the end of the experience, it takes
off and blows a mile wide hole through the,
through the clouds.
>>So it was definitely of
this density in that case,
>>Yeah,
>>because it had to have an effect
on the cloud.
It wasn't just...
>>I tried taking pictures of it.
But every time I go take a picture
the battery life went to dead.
Finally we got a shot and
the flash goes off.
I'll give you that picture.
The flash goes off and the ship's about
a couple, about a mile or so away.
So you can only see the line.
There were two beings across the street.
And when the flash went off, the
being turned into an orb and went
back to the ship, this being turned
into an orb, it went back to the ship.
>>Yeah.
>>And when
you say they were across the street
and doing this motion, what does
that mean there?
>>Okay so here's the being right,
like a humanoid standing there.
Here's those two humanoids standing there.
The flash goes off, this one
turned into an orb and this
one starts turning into an orb.
So I got the picture of the being
materialized, dematerializing
to go back to the ship.
>>Oh wow.
>>And then a being that is, dematerialized
on the process going back to the
craft, and then the craft turned
around and started flashing us.
>>When you say
humanoid, were they the
Mantis humanoid looking?
>>What were they?
>>No different being.
I think they were more like a
just a benevolent humanoid being.
>>There's so many.
>>There's so many cultures, so
many different races and cultures that...
>>I
got ahold of MUFON cuz I was,
damn who do you get ahold of?
So I went to MUFON, I was, Ahhh -
you won't believe what I saw!
And they sent their
star level investigator.
He was a nuclear physicist
from Livermore Labs.
>>Wow.
>>Yeah.
and,
>>That's some interesting people.
>>Yeah.
He went through, he said, oh we
had a class level four encounter
and it's been investigated.
Then Bigelow Aerospace started
calling and I'm like, who do I?
How do you help?
I need help.
>>So wait, Bigelow Aerospace called you?
>>Yeah, Bigelow Aerospace
called me and they were like,
>>And what?
And because they read your MUFON report?
>>Yeah, exactly.
Well MUFON,
I guess the guy that I was with
transferred my information to Bigelow
Aerospace and did, so they called
me trying to get...
>>Why did he transfer,
Did he say?
>>I have no idea.
I have no idea.
But the Bigelow guy was real pushy, he
was like, I need, I want this information.
You know who I am.
Brrr, brrr, brr.
I was like, alright, I'm done.
I'm done.
So I need to find help.
And that's when finally, after a couple
other experiences..
>>More pieces of the puzzle,
sorry, I know a lot about Bigelow Aerospace and what's going on there, but..
>>Yeah.
Yeah, now I do.
>>It's really, yeah, it's
just really nice for...
>>Yeah, I got in touch with other
contactees and other hybrids and
we formed a real tight community.
So everyone that's in, yeah, most
people in Barbara's book, we've been..
>>We've really..
>>We just help each other.
And that's another point to this.
We're...
>>Right.
>>We wanna just help other people
that are experiencing to get over
their fear and just to connect.
And so that way we have someone to
talk to and to let you know - yeah,
you're not alone!
>>Our connections, we are family.
We are family and when, and
I wouldn't do very well if I
didn't have these connections.
>>Sure.
>>It's just different.
>>Yeah.
>>It's not trying to look
special or anything like that.
It's not about any of that because
we're not, but it's just coming
from, I come from, I feel so ET
it's so hard to be here some days.
But we're here and it's really fun
to share what we've, it's what we're
here to do and and I love doing that,
but we, we're so blessed to have each
other and when Barbara and Miguel
asked us to come together to do
this, we've all gotten a lot closer.
And have come to meet these, some
other hybrids connected with the book.
And then Barbara and
Miguel have totally...
respected and honored us for who we are.
>>Yeah, great time.
>>And that has been a
huge gift for all of us.
>>Yeah.
>>They're amazing.
>>I'd love to
know a little bit more on how the
idea for the book came together
and then the idea for the book.
Who contacted you and how
did that work?
>>Miguel Mendonca from England.
Had been contacting Barbara.
So Barbara invited a number of us to be
involved to be interviewed for the book.
We spent many, many, many hours together
on Skype being interviewed and so all of....
>>How did you know, I guess
Barbara put you guys together.
How did you know about Barbara's work?
Or had you had done regression
sessions with her?
>>I had met Barbara, actually.
I had known Barbara off and on here,
meeting her at the
conference, but we weren't close.
>>Okay.
>>And then she and I met at a separate
meeting where Rob and I met too
last April, and Barbara and I just
connected and went off and just had our
own little meeting for a little while.
And and then she invited me.
She said, Jacqueline I'd love
to have you to be a part of this.
And I said, oh, I would love, be so
honored to be so we were all
contacted.
>>Yeah.
>>And it's been an incredible journey
and we've all become very close.
>>Yeah.
>>Very close.
>>This is a door that's been
needed to be open for a while.
And the gift is that it's open
now, and that Barbara could be here,
and open that door and that we
could all be a part of it together.
It, it means more than I can even say.
>>Yeah.
>>Perfect.
Have you come across, a lot of times
in this world we see a lot of the
positive and we mentioned the shift
in the perspective and whatnot, but
is there a negative force or negative
entities out there that have, that
you've encountered and come in
contact with?
>>Yes.
There's the
full spectrum of beings of what
humans label positive and negative.
When I talk to the star beings,
they present it in this way.
They say this just is.
We do not have the perspective of negative
or positive, it's just the spectrum.
So, but for us here, in terms
of what we would label as, I
kind of prefer to use the 'darker energy'.
That's just a part of it.
Yes.
I've had actually many encounters
with those kinds of energies.
Yes.
There are star beings or ETs
who have the darker energy.
And I have had some encounters with them
and it took me a while to understand
and to learn how to work with that.
And once I understood it,
it became easy.  For me
it's all about sending
them love and light.
And when I send them love and light
and I say to them, I choose to stand
in the light and serve divine love and
light, they're not interested in me
at that point.  I'll say, you
need to go find someone else.
If you need to do that, but I am not
going to choose to work with you.
I have worked with a number of people
where I will help clear them as a
certified hypnotherapist, and I do healing
work as well, to help the person come
to a place of coming out of the fear.
To help the person become empowered
within themselves so that they can
learn how to send the love and the
light and stand in their power,
and not be afraid because it's
the fear that attracts them.
So there...
so there are those beings, ET
beings who are of that nature and
many other darker energies as well
that we would not label ET,
who are just of the darker
forces doing what they're to do.
If we shine the love and light,
they're not interested in that.
They're not resonating with that.
So they will go elsewhere.
And I do like to, when I'm working
with other people or I see them in
the area or trying to intrude upon my
space, I do call in Archangel Michael.
And my other star families who are very
high love and light to escort them into,
to connect with the original light.
If that's appropriate, to take
them where they need to go.
And I always say I release all
of you with love and light.
I honor respect,
honor respect your role.
And I release you with love and light.
I don't go in...
>>And you say
if that's appropriate, meaning maybe
in some cases it is, that's the
experience that they need to experience.
Is that..
>>Correct
>>Is that fear and..
>>I leave that up to Archangel Michael.
And the other angels who are working
with escorting them into another space
or dimension, that's not up to me to
decide that's about their soul.
And those angels, but, and once
you learn that it's really pretty
easy then to shield, I call it
shielding yourself with love.
And my Qua Bar, my star being
family, that's what he always says,
they always say, cuz it's a group
consciousness, they always say
to all the star seeds,
your shield is love and light and...
>>So you're not necessarily putting
up a wall or a shield per se,
you're just vibrating at this
love frequency, which creates an
automatic sort of cloaking device.
>>It does put out love and light, and
for me it does create a kind of shield.
And I do put love and light around
me as a shield, if you..
I mean everything.
Yeah.
That's just for me that I like
to love is, love and light is
allowed to come in and out.
But anything else is filtered
because of I'm doing this work every day
of my life, pretty much with people and I,
it just gets filtered out.
>>I guess when you say love and light
shield, I guess the idea of putting
up a wall or a barrier..
>>Right.
>>actually attracts, but then if you're
putting up a wall of love and light
then it's not, the frequency....
Usually when we put up the walls,
it's a hate or a distaste, a
not liking of...
>>It's out of fear.
And then that wall is created of
fear and then it attracts more fear.
>>Correct.
And I don't create, it's not a wall.
Maybe I shouldn't even call it a shield.
I perceive it in that way.
But it's just, I have certain boundaries.
I keep my psychic, I wanna keep
my psychic boundaries,
because of the work I'm doing.
>> I learnt my lessons the hard way with that.
>>And that's how I learned too,
cuz I didn't have anybody
to teach me.
And I learned some of it the hard way.
Definitely hard.
>>Yeah.
>>Yeah, I did too.
Yeah.
I feel like, enough of this!
>>For me, on the negative spectrum of
things, I went to, when I first started
waking up, I went full, I, what I like
to call full blown light warrior mode.
I felt like I had to physically
combat these negative entities.
And I'll tell you in these physical
forms, having a fist fight with
a interdimensional being..
>>Wow.
>>It doesn't turn out good.
>>Yeah.  I can imagine.
>>Ever.
You know and I just I was just always
just, oh, I need to just fight.
I need to fight.
I need to fight because these things are... and I
noticed that the more and more and more
I fought the more and more
and more I had to fight.
And the more and more I just kept
getting beat and kept getting beat.
And I think that's the part where
the sickness came in too.
>>OK, the physical sickness?
>>Yeah, the physical sickness.
Cuz I was just Warrior Mode.
I gotta be the most powerful
light warrior I can.
I need to save the world.
>>Which is... the contradiction in that title.
>>Yeah. It's great.
>>I'm The Light Warrior!
>>Yeah.
>>I love that.
And then when I finally discovered that,
when I finally said, you know what?
I'm not gonna fight you anymore.
I don't want to fight anymore.
I'm tired of fighting.
You know, I gotta.
I gotta leave what's back there in
the past, it's just the past, it's
just, I had learn to let go.
I had to learn to forgive myself and I noticed
and just when I stopped fighting and
I went more into here, into my heart
and I became more accepting of every,
of everything and the negative entities
that came around, I'm just like I
don't even want to deal with you.
They stopped coming around cause I
stopped giving 'em what they wanted.
I stopped feeding into them.
Cause that's what really what it is
we, they we feed into them and in a way
it becomes a symbiotic relationship.
>>Right.
>>Too, where,
they're giving me what I want.
Because I'm, I want to fight
them so they'll be more than
happy to come and fight me.
>>Come and fight.
>>Yeah.
>>So I'm giving them what they want.
They're giving me what I want.
>>Right.
>>And I see that that's in a way, what, how the
negativity on this planet works.  >> Yeah.
>>Is we ended up as a human species,
we developed this symbiotic
relationship with these negative beings.
And in all reality I feel
that we, we brought 'em here
by warring with each other,
>>Yeah.
>>over countless of eons.
And so they're gladly come in
and say, okay, you guys like war.
We'll give you war.
You guys like, torturing each other.
We will come and we'll give you that.
We'll give you what you want.
>>Well this is, I guess, these higher
beings understand this as well.
So that's, they're this higher vibration.
But let's go to, I guess in your
cases with the mantis, but also
with the Zeta reticuli beings.
Cuz this is - more people have
had experience in this realm.
They, even though they may be benevolent
in their intentions across the large
scale spectrum of things, these, the
fear that's created from the abduction
scenarios or temporary detainment scenarios,
doesn't that draw in negative entities?
Because the people who have these
experiences and then they're like you said
in the beginning, I'm a light warrior.
I'm, you've had these experiences and
now you're gonna go and fight them.
And is that creating a negative...
>>Sure.
>>reality here on Earth and aren't they
aware of that?
>>And then it, all of that energy is in
the collective human consciousness.
So that's what we're trying to help
shift now, is to shift that energy in the
collective, that, that it can be different.
And fear, again, wherever there is
fear, it opens one to attracting
>>Right
>>the, these other energies.
>>Yeah.
>>That and so it's, it is unfortunate.
And then and people do often see that
the grays and all ETs are demons and
and I talked to a gentleman yesterday
here, for a while back that he was so
scared and I said, nooo, you know, it's, yeah...
>>It's about the perspective.
>>It really is.
>>So what do these ETs, these higher
ETs that are doing the temporary
detainments, to upgrade our DNA, to
move us into these higher realms?
How do they, I don't wanna use the word
combat, or how do they deal with the,
the scenarios when certain individuals do go
into these states of fear and demonizing
them and all these other things?
Is there, do they just okay,
that's that person's soul contract,
that's what they need to deal with.
Or, but because that's very
contradictory to what their mission is.
>>Yeah.
>>Or is it?
>>It's a whole soul thing.
We're living many lives at once.
>>Right
>>Simultaneously.
So what might be going on in another
aspect of the soul might be affecting...
>>Yeah.
>>the human part that's here on Earth in
the moment. Maybe they're wanting to
learn something that's crossing over..
>>Yeah.
>>from another aspect from
the soul, it's so... >>Yeah.
>>Complex, but...
>>Yeah.
>>It's, but I hear what you're asking.
And the higher we call them, the
higher beings of light in that because
they come from a place of love,
divine love, unconditional love.
They're they just allow the scenario
to play out in whatever way.
Now if someone calls on the higher beings
to come in and help, then they can come in.
>>Yeah.
>>And..
>>and help but it's...
>>Yeah.
The interferencing is, ya know...
>>Yeah, well like in in my case, in my
experience, when I, had this entity,
just grabbed me by my throat, it's
like they, they have the ability,
the mantis beings have the ability to..
>>Sorry, this is not the getting
the toothpick out of you, it's a different,
that's when you grabbed that being?
>>Yeah, that's when I grabbed that being.
But this is the whole, when I, my warrior
time, I got into a, like a skirmish
with an entity and it picked me up and
slammed me down, and you hear this, wow.
It's scary as shit, but, oh, yeah.
>>Yeah.
>>Looking back, the Mantis being
has the ability to go leave 'em alone.
>>Yeah. Like the Jedi, just..
>>Yeah, exactly.
But they're, it's more for
them, they're like you
brought that entity to you so you know
now how are you going to deal with it?
And it's not until you,
you say, okay, please help.
>>Then they come in and
they do their Jedi stuff.
>>Yeah. Then they go, okay.
Yeah.
>>Alright.
>>And it's about us learning
to be in our power here.
So how do we learn, ya know.
>>Yeah.
>>We have different experiences.
>>And I, yeah,
because that's how I learned really
stand up and be in my power was, and I
thank them for those experiences and
sure.
But...
>>Opportunities to learn.
>>Opportunities.
If we all can take that
perspective in the moment.
That would...
>>In the moment..
>>It's near impossible.
>>Yeah.
Because it can be very very scary and
that's what they love to do is
scare you as much as possible.
I've seen objects float across rooms.
>>Yeah.
>>I've seen all kinds of things from...,
and then I was working with people
with that, and then I actually
gave that up at some point.
Cause I thought, I don't
wanna be doing this any more.
>>Yeah.
>>Well speaking of fear and the mantis being,
so my first encounter actually wasn't
the encounter on the lunar eclipse.
I had a meditation on a mountain and I was
given this vision of the back of a Mantis
Being, and he turned and looked at me.
Oh, and then I said, hello.
And there wasn't, I didn't have any fear.
I was like, oh, interesting.
This is..
>>That's great.
>>What is this here?
And then I'm connecting the
dots and thinking that maybe because
of my non-fear in that vision, in
that meditation I didn't get startled
and get knocked outta my meditation.
I was like, oh that - this is interesting,
who are you? Just a
look, stared into the eyes,
and then and then I started meditating
on other stuff, kinda went away.
So I just acknowledged that.
And then, a couple months later on the
eclipse, I got this, the massive download.
And then part of what I've been doing,
my invest, trying to find out more about
Mantis beings, I heard that they're keeping
in the back because of their looks,
because they're so
different looking, and...
>>If someone's fearful of them,
they'll all step back,
but boy, they're in my face all the time.
Yeah.
But they know that I love them and
I love seeing them as they are.
But yes, they'll, they're very respectful.
They know how each person will
handle it and what they can handle.
>>So they already kind of,  they don't want, if
people are gonna have that fear.
They don't, so then they...
>>No, they're gone.
>>And then, but they also know, maybe they
know that because of their looks and they
are quite different than than what we have
in our conscience with the grays or with,
the Palladian blonde blue-eyed type beings.
So they keep in the back a little bit?
>>Yeah.
>>Yes, definitely.
>>Oh yeah,
I've had, if you imagine, where
a seven foot tall Mantis being
was at the foot of my bed.
>>Yeah.
>>If you can imagine a normal
person that you know...
normal if you will?
>>Someone who's not exposed to this..
>>Someone who's not exposed.
>>And next thing you know, you got an eight
foot tall praying mantis in your room.
It's horrifying.
It's the same thing as imagine if you're
scared of spiders and now there's a ten
foot spider in your house, and it's
like dripping venom and like going raaar, but
it's like really telling you, I love you.
>>Yeah, exactly.
>>Yeah.
>>You're gonna freak out.
And they, I was so happy when
they, and they initially showed up
because they came as themselves.
And they always come in my
bedroom, I'm always, when I'm
in bed, they always show up.
And there were eight of them
around my bed with my first actual
encounter in that way with them.
And I went.
>>Yeah.
>>Wow.
You guys are the mantis.
And I was like, so excited.
>>Yeah.
>>And I said, welcome! Ya know it didn't,
I was just like, and they come all
the time because me, I just love it.
>>You just reminded me of something.
You know an important thing to know
for everyone this would be for
everyone, to tell the difference.
>>Okay.
>>Cause I, I come across this a lot,
how to tell the difference between
a negative and a positive entity.
My, cuz I've had encounters
with both, physical 3D manifestations.
I don't have, I don't have
the ability, like some people
to see, I don't see auras.
I don't see the ghost.
I see full.
It has to be a full 3D manifestation
in order for me to see it.
I'm just like a everybody else.
I've had now the mantis beings, I've had
them physically appear before me, and
the feeling that I get from them... imagine
you have a childhood friend, right?
And that childhood friend, you grew
up with that friend, and you
guys did everything together, right?
It's gonna be here in your heart.
>>Yeah.
>>You'll feel it right here.
I know you.
>>Yeah.
>>You're so familiar to me.
Why are you so familiar to me?
My first encounter with a mantis
being with just like that. I'm
staring at it's face and it's
like, why are you so familiar?
How do I know you?
And for the negative beings.
It's here.
>>Yes.
>>In your stomach.
There's a feeling you get
right here in your gut.
Something's not right.
Something is not right here.
When you get that feeling
that something is not right.
That's how you know, just, and you don't
have to be like, you don't have to go,
I'm gonna fight you guys right now.
You don't have to fight 'em.
>>Out comes the switchblades.
>>Yeah, exactly.
So you know, you just leave 'em alone
and you say, hey, a lot of times you, just leave
me alone, I don't wanna deal with you,
they'll leave you alone.
I'm sure you get caught up the
wrong way for a long time a lot.
But for the most part it's - you
get that feeling in your gut.
You just say, just get out of my face.
>>Yeah.
>>To really trust that, and to really
bless them and release them with love.
>>Exactly.
>>Because they don't want that.
That's, they're not resonating,
so they're gonna leave much more
quickly than if someone...
>>Yeah.
>>yells and screams and...
>>Right.
>>Says, get outta here, then that..
>>That's what they feed off of.
>>That starts to create the..
>>There,
another warning that I have
there is a false light.
There are what I call things that hide.
>>Yeah, hide.
>>I hear that a lot.
>>Yeah.
>>Oh, yeah.
I call 'em the dark ones
that hide in the light.
>>That's...
>>Yes.
>>That's kind the name I gave
them because they do have this.
Oh hello.
How are you?
Please come with me.
I got something to show you.
Here's the ascension chamber
you're gonna go into, and this
chamber is where you're gonna down
download all of your information.
You'll become a beautiful being.
But, and then, oh, here's
our cloning chambers.
Here's where we clone beings.
And clone things, and this is so nice.
And oh, and here's here's the controllers
or these, this is where your channel, a
lot of your channel messages come from,
but the whole time you'll feel this,
wait this...
>>Uneasy feeling in the stomach.
>>This doesn't feel right
doesn't feel right.
>>Yeah,
and what I like to do is, I will
always, this is just my way,
I will say do you serve
the divine light and love?
>>Yeah.
>>And right away, if they don't, I
can see the light dropping away
and then they know they've been
discovered and they're gonna take off.
>>Yeah.
>>Usually,
cuz I work with a lot of this, we just,
in terms of all kinds of spirit, cuz I
mean I've worked with this my whole life
in the spirit realm with people who call
me about different spirits and homes
or I had a woman who I worked with in
Australia recently who said three little
kittens showed up at the foot of my bed.
She said, I wasn't sure
cuz it was a dim light.
That for me, that was a
red flag to hear dim light.
And she said, and then they're, and
she said, but now they're not leaving.
And I said, oh, interesting.
So as we worked through some of that,
these were beings that camouflaged
themselves as cute little kitties.
And they were not cute little kitties.
And because they can appear however
the person - ya know she loved kitties.
So and so I said, we need to release
them and move them out, which we did.
And they were not kitties, so they,
there's lots of interesting ways that
that they can camouflage in that.
>>And what was the term that you said?
Do you? The question you asked?
Do you serve the divine light?
>>I ask them if they serve
divine love and light.
>>So I sort of, so I, as you're saying that I felt
that it was more than just the words.
>>It's, I'm putting it out...
>>You're putting that out.
>>Even as I'm saying it right
now, I'm putting it out.
>>So maybe that's for people watching that.
>>Yeah.
>>You can't just say the words.
It's, you really have to
feel into what the..
>>Right, I say it from my heart, from my soul.
And yes.
You can't just say divine light,
divine light, divine light...
>>No, it's like holding onto a cross and
Jesus, Jesus, or whatever.
>>You're freaked and going, divine light.
Divine light.
>>Exactly.
>>It's not gonna work very well.
It's centering and coming...
>>Yeah.
>>to the still point within the self, that
quiet place of heart within and then..
That's the first thing to do.
And then to feel the love
and to really share that.
>>Yeah, you know what?
I've used when I, in my
ignorant time, I was learning,
I thought you know what?
I gotta study all the different religions
and no respect to, disrespect to any
religions, and it had all people of all
religions need to forgive my ignorance
of their religion, but I decided I
wanna check out the whole Christianity
thing, and I did that at first.
I had this, the negative entity, pushing
me down, holding me down, and I did the
whole: 'In the name of Christ, I command you
to leave me, I command you to leave me.'
>>Right, okay.
>>And nothing, it still kept...ya know
I'm struggling and I, 'In the name of
Christ command you to leave me.'
And it wasn't until I was able to
break free and I had one of those
touch lights, alls I had to do was
turn the light on and it was gone.
>>Yeah.
>>It was all I had to
do, was turn the light on.
>>Wow.
>>And if you think about this analogy
here, if you go into a dark room right?
Alls you have to do is
turn the light on, right?
And all the darkness goes.
>>Yeah.
>>And you still have your shadows.  >> Right.
But all the darkness goes away
and the brighter the light, the
least amount of shadows you have.
>>And I tell people to physically
turn light on.   >>Right.
>>Yeah,
physically light a white
candle, sometimes to just add, ya know,
to do incense or something
that could really help shift the
energy of a household or something.
>>Wow.
So it sounds like even though you've had
all these, both of you guys have had these
extra terrestrial, so to say, otherworldly
experiences, you still are very in tune
to angels and moving energy in the room.
>>Absolutely.
>>And you say you don't see auras,
but you still have this sort of
feeling of different energies.
>>Oh yeah.
Oh yeah.
>Oh, there's so many different
wonderful beings, species in
creation that it's just amazing.
I've had lots of encounters with
nature spirits, and being in my home
and around my home and talking to me.
And...
>>Would the experiences with ETs have
opened, you think that it's opened you
up to these other energies of things, or
is just, that's just naturally?
>>It's always been that way for me for some
reason, with the animal communication.
And that it's just part of it and it's
just unfolded through my whole life.
>>It's not one or the other.
It's a package.
>>It's, for me, it's been
a total package deal.
>>Awesome.
>>I said, what was my soul
thinking coming in here?
Had a lot more in mind, than not
remembering what it might be like here.
>>Right, we probably didn't realize it
was gonna be soooo tough.
It's so tough.
Tough it is.
>>Correct.
Absolutely.
>>Yeah.
>>So different.
It's oh yeah,
piece of cake,
not remembering that fractal thing.
I got that.
>>What it's like to be in density.
>>Yeah.
>>And yeah.
>>Yeah,
imagine a master of the universe,
saying, looking down at this,
oh, I got this.
>>Piece of cake.
And then I'm going, Oh, whoaaaa.
>>And then we go through
it, and then we die.
And then we're like, oh that was kinda fun.
>>Yeah.
>>Maybe let's go back and do it again.
>>Do again.
>>Let's do it again.
I got this this time.
I got it.
>>Exactly.
That's right.
>>Oh my goodness.
But one thing the ETs have taught me
or talked to me about too is even well
from the human perspective that we can
go beyond what many people refer to as
the karmic wheel or that going round and round.
We don't have to keep
going round and round.
We can go
beyond that.
And make a choice to not do the looping.
Honestly.
>>Yeah.
>>That there are other ways that
we can choose to do all of that.
So I just wanted to...
>>And speaking of that, it seems the
message I've been getting with all
these interviews is we're at this
place and time in our evolution as
the humanities has been doing this
cycle for 25,000 years or more.
>>Or more, yeah, definitely.
>>But at least in this go around. That
we're, we are ending this karmic cycle
and going into something different here.
>>Yes.
>>Yeah.
>>Is that the messages you
guys have been getting?
>>The ascension event, that comes
up the whole ascension event,
right that I'm sure you've heard of?
And what is the ascension event?
And it's funny that you say 25,000
years ago, cuz what is at the, how far
is the distance between the sun and
the center of the milky way galaxy
is approximately 25 - 26,000 years.
>>Oh, interesting.
>>Okay.
>>So on a physical level, from
my understanding imagine this
to our astronomers are just now
discovering, you're seeing the light
from this event that happened.
So about 25 to 26,000 years ago, a gas
cloud came in and fell into the center of
our black hole at the the super massive
black hole, the center of the galaxy.
And we really don't have any kind
of as a species, our scientists
can't really comprehend what the super
massive black hole is at the center.
When we need to fall, when the gas
cloud falls into the center it's
instantly converting all that
mass and matter into energy, right?
And it pulses, it brings, pushes
out this energetic pulse, right?
We see in other galaxies and our own
galaxy before, remnants of previous
times where black hole woken up and
there's, there'd be a energetic beam
that shoots up 50,000 light years.
One going up, one going down.
And so if you can imagine,
that's a lot of energy.
So what happens is this energetic
wave comes out from the center
of the galaxy, and it's traveling
near the speed of light.
The light itself takes 25 - 26,000 years
for astronomers, they're saying, okay there's
gas clouds going in, what happens next?
Right behind the light,
here comes the energy of it.
Just this wave.
Coming outwards.
And it changes everything.
It changes everything.
Now that's, from what I understand,
that's part of one of the reasons
why the ET started coming back.
Cuz it's okay the negativity's
getting outta hand here on
Earth, and here comes this wave.
What happens when this, it's a frequency,
what happens when this frequency gets
to Earth and Earth is going woooooo, and here
comes this wuuuuu, you know what's gonna happen?
>>Oh, okay.
>>Clash.
>>Chaos.
>>Yeah, chaos.
Okay.
I see.
Interesting.
>>So if you look at things..
>>A storm?
>>A storm,
exactly.
So when this wave gets here, they want
to help try to raise the vibration to
get the planet, the frequency specific.
So this galactic wave
doesn't hurt Earth, hurt us.
It just evolved...
>>The hot and cold pressures.
>>Exactly.
>>Don't collide as hard.
So you don't get a hurricane,
you get just a few raindrops.
>>They took me that ship that that I
witnessed, they took me up once and..
The triangle ship?
>>Yeah.
>>Okay.
With these beings that you
don't even know who they were.
>>Yeah but the mantis be the mantis,
there was a mantis and zeta aboard that
craft, they use each other's ships.
>>Okay.
>>The experience was, ya know,
these beings, I wake up in the middle
of the night, and walk down the
hallway and there's like a French door.
It goes in the back and there's a tall
white zeta, if you will, standing there.
And he says, hey let me in.
I said, oh, I ain't gonna let you in, man.
There's no way.
So it says, okay, we're gonna do
this every night until you let me in.
And so I pass out, wake
up next night, same thing.
Let me in.
Alright, I'll let you in.
I crack the door open, it sticks it's hand
through, and I slam the door on his hand.
It's fighting, and pulls away.
It's rubbing its hand.
It sits down.
I sit down, we stare at each other, and
he is it's okay, man, but we're gonna
sit here and do this until you let me in.
And finally the third night, I let him
in and, all right, here, let's do this.
And he's like, all right, follow me.
I go up with him, and there's that.
Triangle craft floating above
me and it pulls me up into it.
And next thing I know, he's standing
in front of the view screen.
It's like view screen.
And he's - come here.
Look at this.
And I, okay.
I walk and it's all telepathy.
Okay?
So I walk up and
we're over the valley, where I live, where I
lived, the Salinas Valley and there's
a, there's like Northern Lights, right?
But red and orange, just like
translucent energy, but it wasn't
in the sky and it was on the ground.
And I remember going, oh yeah, I'm
just seeing the world end because I
was listening to the, I think his name,
oh, one of the remote viewers that
talk about this kill shot of the sun.
Oh, Ed Dames?
>>Yeah.
>>Oh don't listen to Ed Dames.
>>I thought for sure that's what I saw.
I thought, I was like, oh my God,
you guys are showing me the kill
shot that destroys everything.
Don't be silly.
That's not what this is.
That's not what this, what they showed me.
It's this energetic wave that
comes from the central black hole.
And it's more of a hug from the creator.
>>Yeah.
>>The best way I can put it.
Hopefully it snaps the minds of
humanity up to be like, there's more
to this universe than just these walls,
>>And just humans.
>>and the couch, there's
more to it.
>>Yeah.
>>And, but it goes, it even
goes further than that too.
How would I describe this?
Imagine yourself as you are now, right?
And you look forward, you
look backwards, right?
If, imagine all these different
strings, they come from your center,
there's all these different
strings that kind of go off in
infinite amount of directions, right?
That is what that is, is represents
at this point, there's an infinite amount
of possibilities for me to do, right?
An infinite amount of possibilities.
Behind me is the same.
There's an infinite amount of
possibilities that got me here, right?
So an infinite amount of possibilities
that got me here and an infinite amount of
possibilities for where I'm gonna go.
Okay.
We experience these
possibilities simultaneously.
The thing that my little spark is, is
kinda like a little zipper that
pulls all these experiences together.
The singularity
if you will, pulls all these experiences
together and then now my spark gets
to choose which way I'm gonna go.
>>Yeah.
>>Of course
it's hard for me to jump from, cuz this
spark is experiencing this spectrum.
I can't just jump to this spectrum,
I have to navigate through the bars.
>>Yeah.
>>Okay, so
but we split, we're constantly splitting.
And we're experiencing every possibility.
Now what happens when this happens over
countless numbers of thousands of years.
Now if we go back to,
everything's a fractal of itself.
What happens in our universe
as far as we know, when something
gets too big for its britches,
let's take a star for an example.
When a star gets too big, it
collapses in on itself, right?
Becomes a supernova black
hole, a white dwarf, whatever.
But it's becoming a new,it's becoming
a new divine expression of creation.
It wants to experience, oh, I'm too big.
Let's experience something new.
So we have all these lines that go
out and we've got, we've exhausted it.
On this planet, we've exhausted
all the possibilities.
So now it's gotten too big.
So it's like now our possibilities are
collapsing in on themselves.
It's just one big... >> The timelines. >>compression.
Yeah, the timelines and everything.
It's a compression.
So we're experiencing all these
possible realities simultaneously.
And now they're...
>>Within the limitations
of the third density.
>>Exactly.
>>Okay.
>>And now they're collapsing in on
themselves and we become a new
expression of divine creation.
>>Fourth density consciousness.
>>And how do you want to
experience that event is up to
how you want to experience it.
>>Gotcha.
>>If it's gonna be a world ending
event, then that's how you're
gonna experience your collapse.
You hear about the collapse of the
economy, the collapse of society.
>>Yeah.
>>Collapse, collapse, collapse.
So it's a collapse of
possible possibility...
>>Of that those old
paradigm ways of doing things.
Because we've exhausted the, we cannot
continue to do things in that way.
>>And somehow the
trigger is this energetic wave from
the black hole that's coming in now.
That's what triggers the collapse.
>>It aligns right with all the
other teachings and sayings,
the harmonic convergence of '87.
>>And yeah, there are so many
potential people will ask me
what's absolutely going to happen?
There are so many possibilities.
I'm just saying this a little
different way, but kinda the same, of timelines,
there are all those choices that,
or potentials, that can happen
depending on what humanity chooses.
Also collectively.
>>Yeah.
>>And but each soul gets
to choose their journey,
journey as well.
For me, a very key message of what we term
ascension is basically about humanity
remembering
that they are one with everything.
We are all one.
That we are cosmic citizens.
And that expansion in consciousness
and that on Earth that, that we need
to come together in cooperation.
And to live from our hearts.
And in doing that, then there is
no need for the greed, the war,
and struggle.
If we all come to that
remembrance that we are divine.
That, that we are all divine.
So in the end it's, for me that
is a big part of our message as
hybrids or my, what we to share.
And but the message I think is
being a hybrid is really to help
people understand we are all cosmic.
They are family.
Really they are us and we are them.
And they are evolving
just as we are evolving.
They've told me this over and over.
You think you're the
only ones going through...
>>Yeah.
>>the process,
they go, we're going through
this process as well.
It's all of creation.
Moving through this incredible process
that is just an inspiring, and in the
end it does come out to a new creation.
And I like to
talk about the new human.
That's why I call it the new
human awakening and coming into
being a new creation in that way.
And so I think, and that's what
we're, that's what we are here for,
bottom line.
>>This new
consciousness comes with a
new whole set of DNA upgrades.
>>Absolutely.
The DNA shift, and and all of that is,
is happening in terms of the energy
just cosmically, it's just happening.
>>Yeah.
>>It, the creations where all the
creations expression and creation is
shifting and evolving all the time.
And so we're in an opportunity, this
is a period of time on Earth that we
have the opportunity to really embrace
and remember who we really are.
>>Right.
>>We're not these bodies, we're
not Joe Accountant or
whoever.
That is not our main I identity
or the car, the, all of that.
That's the whole illusion
that we're evolving out of.
>>I'll give you this real quick.
Our scientists actually have, and they,
most people don't even think about
this, but our scientists on Earth,
they've actually came up with a oneness
theory, and that's the Big Bang theory.
>>Yeah.
>>Think about this.
They say that all matter
originated from a single point.
If you put your finger out
for me, Jacqueline, right?
So imagine this.
It took, as far as scientists know, 14.5
billion years for that atom and that atom
to come together again.
So if you imagine not only is it a
physical, not only is it a physical part
that we all came from the central point
in the universe to reconnect again.
Imagine that singularity is also
consciousness and our consciousness split.
And now it took 14.5 billion years
for me to meet you in these forms.
The same as this atom here was in a star.
>>And it's going back the other direction,
but it's happening at the same time.
So it's expanding and contracting
at the same time.
>>Yeah.
>>Yes.
It's pretty, yeah.
>>Separating and coming together for all of
eternity, just trying to figure out what
we are, because it's a being that just
came into consciousness saying, what am I?
>>And yeah.
>>It's beautiful.
Thank you so much.
This has been a very enlightening
interview and thank you.
Thank you for sharing.
And I thank the mantis beings
for providing an opportunity
to talk about them a little
bit.
>>Definitely get this out.
>>We love it.
>>Yeah.