I have been exploring
and traveling
through what you might think
of as timelines, what you might
think of as for a very
long time in terms
of how you perceive years in
past, present, and future.
And in doing this
type of exploration,
it allows me to experience
extraterrestrial civilizations
from a variety of choices
in terms of who they choose
to be as individuals, as
a society,
This, then, for
me is a great joy
to explore, experience, and
learn from other civilizations,
other extraterrestrial
beings, other worlds,
other ways of life, other forms
of experiencing the infinite,
that we all are, unconditional
love, that we all are.
I, in doing this, have developed
the type of translation ability
that affords me the
ability then to speak
with a variety of
extraterrestrial civilizations
in a language they
can understand.
These are some, then, of the
activities and functions for me
that are fulfilling,
that are a part of who
I enjoy experiencing and sharing
with others in other worlds
and in my own
Yahyel civilization.
Ever wonder if there's intelligent
life elsewhere in the universe?
Well, I have....I've been wondering since I was a kid.
My name is Reuben Langdon.
And on March 29th 2007, in the middle of the day,
I saw a number of strange objects in the sky.
Coincidentally, I was working on
the film Avatar at the time, playing an alien.
And ever since then I've been on a quest...
A quest to find out if aliens really do exist and if so...
...are they here with us?
If beings of higher intelligence are here...
...what is their purpose?
Why don't they make themselves more known?
Why the secrecy?
I've asked these questions to many experts,
yet each seems to have a different theory.
So I thought to myself,
why not ask the aliens directly?
So that's what I set out to do!
Well, sort of...
>> Wonderful to be here with
you in these blending moments
to God, to have this opportunity
to explore more of the infinite
that we all are, more of the
unconditional love that is all
of our actual nature.
And with this in heart
and mind, in what way
would you most enjoy
exploring together?
>> Oh.
Hi, Ishuwa.
I'd like to ask a few questions.
>> Very well.
>> First of all, I'd like to
know a little bit more about
yourself and your civilization.
>> Very well.
I am Ishuwa--
>> Yes.
>> --of the Yahyel civilization.
The idea, then,
in brief brevity--
your and our civilization
were at one time
the same one civilization.
There were some in
our world who chose
to step out into
space to explore
new worlds, new creations,
new evolutions, hybridizations
of life forms.
And some of those who embarked
on that co-creation from
our civilization--
they, over eons and eons
of your time in a sense,
through the blending,
through the hybridization
through the evolving
with other civilizations
some quite different than
ours but human, yes...
...have evolved and become
your earth human civilization
so you do, as the channel was
mentioning earlier,
you do each of you on Earth
in the DNA of your human biology
all of you without exception
born here on Earth
have DNA that is then
very much that of
our civilization. The one in
which you in a sense were
part of before the time of
stepping out into space
to explore, to create new
hybrid worlds.
So in that sense we are family.
We are human as you are.
There are variations in our physical appearance
from those of you on your world.
We could walk amongst you and
the variations wouldn't make you
think necessarily we were
from another world,
perhaps just from a different
part of your world you aren't
familiar with in that way.
We are very different in our
vibration, our consciousness,
our sense of who we are.
Our knowingness of
existence is quite different
than that you have in
your world at this timing.
We all know in that
sense who we are.
We all support one
another in all moments
without hesitation,
without question.
We are then supported by
ourself and by all others
in our civilization at all
times without hesitation.
This is a wonderful--
a wonderment, a wondrous
experience for us
to be a part of.
This simply is the way
we have chosen to co-create
our experience together.
So it is no less or greater than
that in your world's choices
to choose as you
have been doing,
to be somewhat separate
from the awareness
of your actual nature.
So the idea then--
I have been exploring
and traveling
through what you might think
of as timelines, what you might
think of as for a very
long time in terms
of how you perceive years in
past, present, and future.
But it isn't all that
long in my experiencing,
for I am able, as many of us
are, to move about in time--
past, present, and
future at rates
that don't then take as long
as you might think they would.
And in doing this
type of exploration,
it allows me to experience
extraterrestrial civilizations
from a variety of choices
in terms of who they choose
to be as individuals, as
a society, how they choose
to interact with
other civilizations
in their own worlds
and on other planets,
in other solar systems.
This, then, for
me is a great joy
to explore, and experience, and
learn from other civilizations,
other extraterrestrial
beings, other worlds,
other ways of life, other forms
of experiencing the infinite,
that we all are, unconditional
love, that we all are.
This is of great excitement and
fulfillment for me to do this.
I, in doing this, have developed
the type of translation ability
that affords me the
ability then to speak
with a variety of
extraterrestrial civilizations
in a language they
can understand.
It is as though
I am a translator
in a sense for several
extraterrestrial worlds,
civilizations,
beings, life forms.
These are some, then, of the
activities and functions for me
that are fulfilling,
that are a part of who
I enjoy experiencing and sharing
with others in other worlds
and in my own
Yahyel civilization.
It is always a great
joy to have opportunity
to interact in that,
then in your civilization
to share and interact with
those of your human experience
in your current
timeline, which is always
changing in every moment.
There's a great joy for me to
be able to interact with you.
So that is a little about me
and the Yahyel civilization.
Did you have more around
that-- you wanted to ask about?
Or was there another direction
you would like to explore?
>> A few more questions
in regard to this.
For when-- for interacting
with other civilizations,
do you also--
do they also have the same
type of channeling mechanisms
that we are using in
this case and other--
specifically my series
that I'm doing here
is utilizing the channeling
mechanism or techniques.
>> Some other
civilizations do this,
yes.
It is part, in a sense, of
human biological ability.
There are different
ways that the channeling
can be done than
what you are most
familiar with experiencing.
But those will be
more evident in time
as those types of channeling
capacities unveil themselves
in your world's
experiencing of them.
There are then
other civilizations
that simply choose not to
interact in that capacity.
>> What would be--
if it's OK to
share, what would be
some of the other capacities?
>> Some do not speak at all.
Some are entirely, let's
say, telepathic in a sense.
Some do not do that at all.
Some are very vocal.
They are very behavioral
in their communication.
It is then to learn what their
behavior is communicating
in a sense.
That then is a very different
type of communication.
It isn't necessarily
as specific as words
in telepathic
communication can be.
In those types of transactions, interactions,
communications with those
behavioral communicators--
it can-- at first, interactions
seem that the information
is very vague.
Not much one can learn from
that type of interaction.
However, giving it time,
behavioral communication
can be a little bit
like those in your world
who do sign language.
And so it can get to be very
useful, very meaningful, very
fulfilling in levels of
great depth, and detail,
and interlayerment in a sense.
And so that is another type
of communication where channeling
isn't really taking place--
behavioral communication.
>> Almost like how we interact
with some animal species--
>> Yes.
>> --on our planet.
>> And there are then-- many of
your animals do more of this.
>> Specific, like
dolphins and apes?
And some people have
telepathic communication
with these animals, but--
>> They can with
themselves as well.
>> Yeah.
I see.
Fascinating.
Is there any sort of technology,
how we understand in our world
with electronics,
AI, and gadgets?
Is there any kind of
gadget communication
with other civilizations
through your civilization?
Or is it more biological?
>> We do have some artificial
constructs that in that sense
convey communication.
Yes.
>> I see.
We recently had in our
collective consciousness--
the US government had made--
brought to the awareness--
programs of studying UFOs and
not fully announcing the UFO ET
presence, but sort of
coming close to sort of seed
the collective.
I wanted to ask how you--
from your perspective,
how you guys
see this energy or
this news affecting...
>> It can facilitate
more of those
in your world's willingness
to accept this idea
of extraterrestrial reality.
>> Has it sped timelines up?
Or is it early?
>> It can.
Yes, jump a little bit
ahead, so to speak--
>> I see.
I see.
>> --in the way
that is supported,
so it can still be appropriate.
>> Right.
Many, many people on our
planet say it's not enough.
They need to disclose more.
>> It has to come from within
the individuals more, really.
And then they can
feel more comfortable,
in a sense, within
what they are sharing.
They don't fully understand
it themselves at this point,
even though the understanding
is contained within all
of your DNA in a sense.
Not many of you have
accessed to it yet,
acknowledged its existence yet.
>> If it were to
happen too fast,
it would almost be
counterproductive.
>> Yes, it is happening on a
very organic rate in a sense,
just as the seed grows into a
tree that produces branches, leaves,
flowers, and fruit, but then
ripens in its appropriate,
in a sense, organic
timing in a sense.
And there are many
factors involved
in facilitating alignment
with your civilizations,
aligning in alignment
with an organic unfoldment
as though you're awakening
to this ET reality
is coming through as though
it had come out of a seed
and is growing,
surfacing, breaking
the surface of the soil,
seeing the sunlight--
the light of day in a sense.
And in a sense,
that is about as far
as you've gotten in this analogy,
with your growth at this point.
Beginning to break the
surface, the seed of a plant,
the tender growth process
is occurring at that level
in this analogy in a sense.
>> Well usually
when we plant seeds,
before it sprouts out of the
ground is the longest time.
But once it starts to
sprout, it comes very fast,
so hopefully that's the case.
>> And in a sense, as
more of you embrace this,
you are like the sun
giving light to this,
that it may grow even faster,
but all the while in its own
appropriate rate.
It will not grow
faster than it can.
There are times in
your plant world,
there are those who
might try and accelerate
the rate of growth of
a particular plant,
experimenting with it
or not knowing, simply
wanting to see if they can
kick it into gear faster.
And there are then those in
your world who do at times
and will continue to try and
accelerate the rate to even try
and genetically alter it in
a sense to be something other
than that which
they might perceive
it would be if it were allowed
to grow into its own tree
and create its own
fruit in a sense.
So there are some who would have
an idea to try and genetically
alter the outcome.
Again, there are
many forces, factors,
beings of high intelligence
within the one that
has the all-- that are
very focused here with all
that are in our interacting
in this exchange of unfoldment,
of these co-created realities to
facilitate an alignment of how
it unfolds in a sense.
And so that what is the
final and in a sense result--
the fruit is very ripe for all
involved human beings on Earth,
human beings in
our civilization,
others who facilitate this.
For there are many that
are part of the one
that we and you
all are one with.
>> So many factors that we
maybe can't quite understand.
So we should just--
>> You can open--
invite to learn
more about them--
won't need to know all of them.
Some will be very
helpful to learn about.
Yeah, some very
exciting to know about.
Some that you can, in a sense,
stand beside and grow and learn
from and with and
share what you know,
that they may learn from
you as well in a sense.
>> Well, these interactions
are quite informative.
So this is one way, I suppose.
>> Certainly.
>> You described earlier.
You described your
civilization's
physical appearance
and maybe being
quite similar to us humans.
The human physical appearance
is so wide in its spectrum
from different nationalities--
Asian, African, Spanish.
We have such a wide variety.
Is there such a variety
in your civilization?
>> There is a variety
potentially as wide,
but generally not as wide.
But the potential is within
the genetic framework.
>> Oh, I see.
>> We can mirror, given
the characteristics
of our physiology to those in
your civilization at this time.
>> Would there be a
density level that we
could classify Ishuwa in his--
>> Fourth, fifth,
and sixth, primarily,
in interacting with your
civilization at this timing.
>> OK, so for-- my understanding
from that would be very close
to an almost non-physical being,
but still having a physicality,
but close in the evolution.
>> Different than vibration
of your physiology
yes. Physical for me, all the
same in my vibratory world.
>> And in that sense, you can
easily adapt to our likeness.
Or other -- to adapt your physicality.
Is that sort of when you
say you are mirroring?
>> There are those who
are similar in physical
characteristics in our world
to those in your world,
mirroring in that sense.
So those from Asia--
we have some in our
world similar to that.
They would then mirror one
another in that respect.
If they were in the
presence of one another,
they would mirror one
another in that way.
>> I see.
>> There are those in
your South America,
in your continent of Africa,
in your North America,
in your European continents.
We have those in our
world who would mirror those
of your Earth humans in
those regions as well--
>> I see.
>> --that the
mirroring is the idea.
>> I see.
I see.
>> Similar.
>> We've
heard a lot about the Yahyel
civilization having--
or being the offspring of humans
and the Zeta Reticuli beings.
Is there a relationship
with what humans
know as Grays or Zeta beings?
>> To my civilization?
>> Yes, to the
Yahyel civilization.
>> There are some of
our DNA within that,
that you would think of as Zeta.
Not necessarily all of them
contain some of our DNA.
They have varieties as well--
hybrid.
They have moved out and
have some variation as well.
>> So many people have talked
about interactions with
their hybrid children.
And they talk in the sense
of their understanding
that their children
are Zeta-human hybrids.
>> They can be.
>> Are there
Yahyel-human hybrids?
>> Yes.
>> Oh, OK.
>> The Yahyel and
the Earth humans--
one civilization
that is, in a sense,
being co-created from our and
your collective consciousness
through choice, our and your
collective conscious level,
super-conscious levels,
choosing to co-create--
Yauaney civilization.
>> Yauaney.
>> The Yauaney.
Some Earth humans have hybrids
in a sense that are Yauaney.
>> So would that be what
collectively we're starting
to understand-- the
hybrid children?
Would that be a
name of this race?
The Yauaney would be our--
>> Some of them are Yauaney
>> Yauaney.
Some are.
Not all are.
There are then Earth
humans who have connections
to extraterrestrials
from other civilizations,
interacting with
them in various ways.
And then they can have
created some hybrid children
with those extraterrestrial
civilizations.
So we are not the only one
interacting with Earth humans
at this time.
>> Not just Zetas,
not just Yahyel.
But we have Pleiadians.
We have Dracos.
We have Arcturians.
We have a whole big cosmic
family and lots of offspring
from that at some point.
>> Family.
>> Exactly.
>> Galactic family.
Yes, a variety of hybrid
children are a part of this.
>> Do these children
play together--
different races,
different offsprings
from different cosmic--
>> This can and does occur.
>> OK.
Does it--
>> Not to say that they are
all aware of one another
necessarily.
>> Oh, OK.
It said that the
Phoenix Lights--
the big ship that sort of
flew over Phoenix, Arizona--
>> A variety.
Yes, there were more than one.
Yes.
>> Oh, OK.
And I think it was in 1997 was --
>> Very powerful visual contact.
>> Yes.
Yes.
In a boomerang shape, isn't it?
>> Yes.
And a visual contact occurred.
>> And is this
Yahyel civilization?
>> Primarily, this was
of our co-creation with
your civilization, although
we were not alone in terms
of extraterrestrial
civilizations.
But it was primarily our
civilization bringing a larger
input into your awareness
on a conscious level
of our existence at
a time and in a way
that on a super-conscious level,
your civilization knew about
in advance, agreed to,
co-created, understood,
understands, can see
what is occurring--
past, present, future
timelines and understands
the powerful, beneficial
results and growth in positive,
nurturing ways for all
involved in that choice
to have that come out,
come through, evolve,
develop in that way.
>> Yeah.
Well, it still is
a large imprint
on the collective
consciousness and continues
to expand, so thank you.
>> Yes.
And there were others before,
perhaps not as highlighted.
There were others since.
And there will be a variety
of other ones coming.
The light forms will vary.
At times, they will not
seem to come from a craft.
They will seem to be
very organic in form,
and shape, and coloration
as though they are phenomena
of space and time itself.
>> Yes.
Would you be able to name some
of these other civilizations
that you work with closely?
>> They are those you are most
familiar with at this time
in terms of the ones that
are to focus and be aware of.
There are others.
Yes, but not to come
through at this time,
simply because you will then,
through your own mechanisms,
begin focusing and
expanding your focus
when truly focusing your focus
will bring greater connection
in a more heartfelt,
intelligent way,
allowing for clarity through
simplification, focus.
Pleiadians-- yes.
There are certainly a variety
of Pleiadian civilizations
that have a very close contact,
conversing, communication,
co-creation, interrelation
with our civilization.
>> Do you also share DNA from
the Pleiadian civilization
as we do?
>> There are-- yes.
In a sense, there
is no end to this.
>> Yeah, it just goes forever.
>> Learning which then will
be most applicable for you
in unfolding a future and a
present that you most enjoy
fulfillingly, will then
provide the greatest excitement
for you.
Understand, then, to know
that there are in a sense
no end to the numbers to
suggest that it is not finite,
perhaps allows you to focus more
on a finite number of them.
To know that there
are an infinite number.
And in this physical
embodiment, your awareness
will not truly embody all of
the infinite number of them
nor need it do so.
Allow, then, to focus,
to know the ones that are
of greatest heartfelt support
will find you as you open
up and focus on those.
But reaching out to uncover
new ones can be a joy to do,
I understand.
>> Yes.
>> Do not let go of that
explorative joys, if it is a joy
for you to do that.
>> Yes, it is definitely a joy.
It's so expansive into--
>> It will guide you beyond
that which you are aware or have
heard of in terms of trying to
create a family tree of sorts
or a point of origination, for
the point changes as you learn
of the next one, and then changes
as you learn of the next one.
>> Yeah, that seems to be the
case, and that's exciting.
>> Yes, understand.
>> That's fun.
That's a lot of fun.
How would you describe,
from your perspective,
the angelic realms that we
consider on our Earth plane?
>> They are non-physical
beings that support Earth humans
in your life here.
They can be thought
of as angelic beings.
There are extraterrestrials who
are in the physical form who
support Earth Humans.
And Earth humans might not
be aware of this coming
from physical extraterrestrials
who might then
define their experience
and communications
as coming from angels
or spirit guides.
So an extraterrestrial could be
for someone on Earth, thought
of as an angel or
a spirit guide,
even though they are physical,
all the while then being
some angels and spirit guides
for an Earth human's experience
are non-physical
consciousnesses.
So it comes down to, then,
which a person is connecting to,
to decide or determine,
is it a non-physical
or a physical being that they
are defining or experiencing
as an angel, or a spirit
guide, or communication
with extraterrestrial?
>> And in your realm where
you exist, do you work with--
I'm assuming you work
as we do with a lot
of these non-physical energies.
>> Yes, there are a variety of
non-physical consciousnesses
that support the matrix in a
sense, the physical experience,
the experience of physicality.
There are a variety of
consciousnesses interacting
that allow for
the way we and you
are experiencing
physicality, that which
holds what you experience as
time and space in a sense,
in a physical spectrum.
There are consciousnesses
that are involved
in this that have evolved to
be more focused at doing that,
that are in a sense,
born to do that,
in a sense, gifted
at doing that.
It is their joy in a sense to
be that support to live life,
almost as if they are
the substance that
holds the physical experience
of your life together.
>> Yes.
>> Conscious being.
So even, for example,
a peach or an apple--
physical item you
experience contains
some of these conscious beings.
>> And this goes back to what
Shaun and I were talking about
earlier.
When we consume these
consciousnesses,
we're putting in what--
what you put out is
what you get back.
>> Yes.
Now, what you put
in, what you put out
is what you get
back or live within.
>> So having awareness of
what types of consciousness we
consume can help us in
our external reality?
>> Yes, it is conscious
energies and entities, beings,
lifeforms that you are consuming
in the food that you are
consuming or the chemistry
that you are consuming that is
interblended with some of
the foods or many of the foods
that are constructed at this
time that many people on Earth
are eating, construction
of synthetic and chemical
consciousnesses with other types
of organic consciousnesses.
>> And I'm assuming
the constructor--
the cook, the preparer
of these foods
also puts in their own
consciousnesses in the mix.
And then it becomes--
>> Certainly.
Thank you.
>> --a consciousness soup--
>> Yes.
>> --and can become quite
tasty if you have a good one.
>> Very much so.
>> I see.
So what we're enjoying
is not just the taste,
but we're also enjoying all the
other different consciousnesses
that are-- go into that making
of this wonderful creation we
call like an apple pie or--
>> That can play a part in it.
Yes.
>> Wonderful.
Many of these
civilizations have talked
about a council of worlds,
a sort of federation,
a galactic federation.
There's many titles for this.
Are you part of...
>> We interact with those of
extraterrestrial origin that,
in that way, choose to
come together and interact
spontaneously to
gather enjoyably,
supportively to gather.
When one is no longer
in a moment of joy,
they will become focused on
another venture or activity
that is more exciting.
And they will move along.
They may come back
at another time.
In this way, it is
always an interaction
of very positive
communication and support.
We can give it names.
But it is free from
friction and conflict
that is imbued or envisoned
in your televisions
and that which is
in the pan of vision
of the theater and
theatrical movie releases.
>> I see.
We sort of formulate our
version of that idea and then--
>> Yes.
>> --put it into a context
that we can understand--
>> Yes.
>> --in our specific
timeline evolution.
>> So our interaction is
friction free in that way.
We are not fighting.
We are not trying to commandeer
some other civilization's
desires and wishes
to supplant our own.
There are no secret
bodies within one
or the other of these
civilizations trying
to take control of the
whole body, so to speak.
>> I see.
>> That is an illusory
reflection of beliefs that are
illusory beliefs.
And we do not in
that way contain
those in our experience.
>> Very human construct.
>> Earth human, Yes.
>> Earth human.
>> Those that you have in
your film and television--
Earth human constructs
with beliefs
that are illusory, illusory
being out of alignment
with your actual nature.
We understand our actual nature.
And therefore, the beliefs
that which we put within
and experience are in alignment
with the actual nature
of existence, of
unconditional love,
of the one that is the all,
the all that is the one.
And because we know this
and we put that out,
we get back experiences
in alignment with that.
It's that simple.
We know who we are.
We put out beliefs that are
in alignment with who we are.
The one that is the
all that we are.
And we get back experiences
in alignment with that.
The infinite effortlessly
creates together and co-creates
interactions that are of
this level of frictionless,
non-friction interaction--
fun, fulfillment, friendship.
>> I understand.
Yeah.
There are people on our planet--
Shaun and myself who--
we were just talking
earlier that we sort of live
these rules.
We sort of live these ideas
and are physically manifesting
this sort of
non-friction way of life.
But the human spectrum
seems to be so great
that Shaun and I can be having
this experience of non-friction,
yet on another
side of the planet,
there are others who still
embrace this idea of friction.
I guess I'm saying is we have
such a wide variety on Earth.
I'm curious to know the variety
on the Yahyel civilization.
It sounds like it doesn't
go to that extreme.
>> It is an infinite
variety within the vibration
of alignment with actual nature.
>> Earth alignment.
>> The Earth frictions are the
result of putting out beliefs
that are illusory, out of
alignment with one's actual
nature.
And thus, putting that out,
they get back friction.
That is a choice
within the infinite
that can exist for an
infinite period in a sense.
The infinite contains
all that can be.
And that can include
those who, currently
through their upbringing
and state of awareness,
choose to create friction.
That can continue to
exist within the infinite
for an infinite amount of time.
The idea is you could
choose to only experience
the free from
friction, that which
is alignment with actual
nature, that which
is filled with an
infinite number of ways
to experience being in
alignment with the joy.
The friction-free experiences
are infinite in number,
unlimited.
So each person has a choice
and has the ability to choose.
Do they want to play around
in the illusory beliefs that
create the frictions or
move off into the realm
of unhindered joy and
excitement in ways
that are free from
friction, that
are fully fulfilling
and fascinating, one
moment to the next--
new, new, refreshing.
That they're in that realm--
are an infinite number
of unlimited realities
that can unfold now, and now,
and now, it is a choice
that you can make.
>> So as we move individually--
as we move into these
non-friction realms,
these infinite possibilities
of joy and non-friction,
will we begin to see less
and less other people having
friction and I guess--
>> Yes.
>> --in our realities as well?
>> OK, so we attract those
people who are also in that
same vibratory rate.
Yes.
And the frictioners--
if that's a title,
we can call them frictioners--
>> The frictioners.
>> --will become sort
of less and less,
until eventually there's just no
frictioners left on the planet.
>> They will not be a
part of your experience.
They will be too
vibrational different.
>> I see.
>> You can and will in time,
for it does exist-- a world,
a Earth which all Earth humans
are living and choosing to know
who they are--
the free from friction
experience where you all truly
have an abundance
of what you truly
enjoy having, and are
supporting and being supported
by one another, supporting each
other, and supporting yourself.
This is a reality that exists.
And you will in
time be aware of it,
because you will be focused
and tuned in with it.
>> Much of your messages
have been in that realm,
in that space of saying, what
you put out, which that--
the four laws that you exist
is the one, is the all.
What you put out is
what you get back.
And everything changes
except for those first four
or first three.
>> Different ways to say.
Yes, you exist here and now.
The one is the all.
The all is the one.
What you put out is
what you get back.
Or what you put within
is what you live within.
And everything is
always changing,
except those first ideas
that I just mentioned--
>> Yes.
>> --you have mentioned.
Yes.
Those are not changing.
And so you can always utilize
the understanding of those
to create an ever-changing
experience of the infinite,
that you are perceiving yourself
to be a part of it perhaps?
Being a part of
unconditional love or existence
here and now and putting
out the one that you want
to be experiencing that of.
Then you get back that one
of the all that is the one.
In the way that you are most
strongly choosing to put that
out, you will get back.
You tune in.
You become in alignment
with that existence,
that experience, that
vibratory reality.
Your ability to do this,
then, never changes.
But how you do it will
always change in a sense.
>> And that's sort
of the secret sauce,
the magic formula for what some
would say law of attraction.
We have many titles
and many different--
>> Yes, certainly.
>> --ways of creating our
reality in this realm.
But that's a very
simplified, direct, but yet,
expansive way to put it.
So thank you for
those wise words.
Talking about
the consciousness
of the peach and
consciousness of the apple,
and what we perceive
as technology
and artificial
intelligence-- we're
entering into a
time on our planet
where we're learning
these concepts.
We're learning the intelligence
behind physical manifestations.
And we're almost to this point--
we actually are to this point
where we have computers
now that we're talking to.
Can you-- from your
perspective, how does this--
how do you interact with these
forms of consciousnesses?
>> Well, in a variety of ways.
As you and your world
are learning to do,
we in our ultimate
state will let
go of all those types
of constructions.
Yes-- and enjoy being, in a
sense, unclothed in a sense,
not wearing--
>> Oh, I see.
>> --any idea of technology and
our experience in interacting
with one another.
>> Oh.
As we have created phones,
and devices, and these things,
the Yahyel civilization
doesn't have these types of--
>> We have some of these.
Yes, spacecraft and other forms
of transportational ideas.
Yes, there are,
in our experience,
opportunities to have,
let's say, a spacecraft
with a variety of
extraterrestrial civilizations
interacting to gather.
This spacecraft provides
a forum for a variety
of extraterrestrial
civilizations to be, to gather,
to interact, to gather in that way,
physically in a sense.
Ultimately, we let go of those
in our deepest, most fulfilling
interaction, in
a sense, for life
free from all such
external creations
of artificial
intelligence in a sense.
We will let go of those and
engage in interaction together,
free of those and yet, we
will take them on and interact
with them in the timing that
supports their function, for us
to have a particular
experience that they
afford us to have that we
would not have without them.
So we do enjoy
having some of those.
Yes.
>> So almost--
I've always had the
idea that the internet is
an external mechanism, external
creation for letting us
humans connect to the idea
that we're all interconnected.
>> Bringing you together as
a single body, a single mind.
>> Right, which we're using
in a technological form.
But ultimately, we're
learning that we already
have this connection
without the internet.
>> Yes.
And now, you're learning the
mind shares a heart together
as well.
You're learning to
live as one heart.
>> But we're using the internet
to teach us something that we
already have, kind of.
>> It is.
>> Because I'm going to put
this video out to the internet
for people to view and
understand that, oh,
we actually have--
>> For many, like an
intermediary step in a sense.
>> Yes.
Yeah.
>> It is like training wheels
on a bicycle in a sense.
>> Yes.
Yes, exactly.
And so as I was
saying earlier, these
interactions with
artificial intelligence
that we're now creating--
is it sort of training
wheels for interacting
with extra-dimensional
intelligences?
>> It can be, for there are some
that are interacting on that
level.
There is consciousness in
the information that is being
conveyed with the computers--
There is conscious
civilizations of a sense,
of a type that are allowing
to make it possible
for the computer
information to be shared--
the information itself.
It isn't just information.
It isn't just packets.
It isn't just ones and zeros.
It isn't just electrical pulses.
It is consciousness.
>> Right, as all intelligence.
>> Intelligence.
>> Yes, just like
our peaches and our--
>> Yes.
>> --apples.
Many people are afraid.
Many people are afraid
of the internet.
Many people are afraid of
these artificial consciousness.
They fear it.
They demonize it.
What would you say
to those people?
>> That is an aspect of the
one that is the all that I am
in a sense, that you are.
So in a sense, I am in the
question speaking of myself,
to myself understanding that
then being accepting of myself
in that framework with
those set of beliefs
that are limiting my
awareness of my actual nature,
then I can be accepting of me
behaving or choosing to have
that experience in that way.
Oh, there is an aspect
of me that perceives
that the computer is dangerous.
All the while, anything
that is, is existence
and thus, then, is equal to
all and everything else that
exists.
Because existence
is equal unto itself
and always that it
exists, actually.
So for someone to take
existence and create the idea
that a computer that
exists is dangerous,
that is a concept that exists.
Their perception that it
is dangerous is existing.
All of these things
exist and thus,
on that level of
their existing, they
are all equal to existence
to the one that exists.
That is the all
that exists, the all
that is the one, that I
am, that you are existence.
And so the idea
that someone thinks
the computer is dangerous--
I can understand.
They are utilizing
the existence that
is equaling unto itself to
create the illusion that it
is not, that it
might be dangerous.
They are creating an illusion.
Because they have
a belief system
that does not enlighten
them to be aware
that the computer is existence.
And thus, they are existence.
And thus, they are
actually equal.
And thus, they can't be
dangerous, more or less.
They are equal.
>> So it's, again, going back
to what you put out is what you
get back.
>> And I understand it is them
and that limited framework
of belief system as
simply creating a play,
a theatrical play, an illusory
belief, an illusory play.
That can be very
meaningful for them.
And because it exists,
it is equal to any play
that I in my experience
create, even the ones that
are in alignment with the
actual nature of existence.
Because they both
exist, they are equal.
>> They're all
possibilities, all options.
>> Everything is
equal unto itself.
Because existence
is that which is
the base of all that is, whether
it is a cloud, or a tree,
or a person, or
laughter, or a thought,
or an action, or a
statement, or a person.
It all exists.
And then it is this-- all
equal in its existence
level of being, the
one that is the all,
the all that is the one.
>> So it's just my--
it's up to me whether
I would choose
to adopt that belief that
that other person has.
>> You could choose.
Or you could acknowledge,
oh, he's just playing that--
>> That game.
>> --form of illusion--
illusory limitation for his own
choosing, for his own reasons.
You can get up on stage
and interact with him
in that limited construct
in whatever way you want.
Try and let him know of a more
expanded way to look at things.
Or you can get very frightened
as well, and team up with him,
and combat computers.
>> Yes.
>> Your choice.
>> Exactly.
>> But in order to be
effective combating computers,
you have to begin veiling
yourself of the awareness
of your actual nature.
Because if you know
everything is equal,
you can't very well believe
that something is dangerous
or better or less than.
So you have to get
on the stage and play
the part of the actor that
believes, yes, it's dangerous.
And to believe that, you have to
put out all other beliefs that
would tell you differently.
So the awareness of
your actual nature
would prevent you from playing
the illusion that the computer
could be dangerous.
>> But as soon as I sort of know
in the framework that you just
laid out-- as soon as I know
that that's how things work,
I sort of diffuse the danger.
>> Yes, because you realize it
is another expression of the all,
the one existence that you are--
>> And it's just a--
>> --that it is.
>> --possibility that I can
choose to explore and like you
said, play that role
if I want to go there.
>> If you want to fit into
that game in that theatrical
presentation.
>> Right.
Right.
>> It is entirely the choice of
the individual who's choosing
that reality.
>> I see.
Yes.
>> Many in your world do not
know of the other choices.
They think there are only
these limited choices
available to them.
They are not aware.
They do not know.
They have not been
shown that there
is a whole buffet in a sense,
a building full of choices,
of beliefs that
they can choose from
and an unlimited number of
choices that are in alignment
with their actual nature.
>> Yes.
>> And when someone begins
to know that there are more
choices--
well, as an analogy, if you were
to go to a restaurant that only
has one item available at the
buffet and across the street,
there's a building or restaurant
that has 30 choices available.
Well, if you know there's
30, perhaps you're
gonna stop going to the
one that only has one choice.
Well, there's 30 over here.
Maybe I want to try
something different.
>> Exactly.
>> Or there's a hundred
choices over here.
This one has a thousand choices.
Oh, there's somebody telling,
no, there's only one choice.
Don't go there.
That food is bad for you.
You eat that, you'll be sick.
>> Exactly.
So it's just up to us to choose.
>> And to know
that it is infinite.
There's unlimited
choices can be in alignment
with friction and
illusion, out of alignment
with your actual nature.
Or they can be choices
that are in alignment
with your actual nature.
And there are an infinite
number of those choices
available as well.
You can choose the
ones you want to.
>> And knowing that
we have the buffet--
>> Knowing that you
have the buffet,
knowing that you have the choice
will afford in almost every
instant the individual's desire
to take and move into the path
of the infinite number of
uplifting choices that are
in alignment with
one's actual nature.
Because it is effortless
more and more,
because it is in alignment
with one's actual nature.
It is not friction full.
It is free of friction.
And it glides.
And it slides easily
and effortless
in creating more experiences
that are in alignment
with one's actual nature.
There is no need to hide to
create beliefs that prevent one
from knowing this or
that in order to believe
some illusory belief.
Don't have to put
a lot of weight
on oneself with all
these illusory beliefs.
That can depress, and create
sadness, and depression,
and illness, and disease.
By choosing the choices
that are in alignment
with one's actual
nature of which there
are an infinite
number, the person
experiences a greater
sense of easefullness
in their experience.
And they are happy.
And they are not
being pressed upon.
They are free to flow, to be
very spontaneous, flexible,
and in that state
to connect to more
of the infinite of their
heart's intelligence
that can come in the appropriate
time and moment that will serve
them in each moment in the
most uplifting, fulfilling,
meaningful way.
>> Which goes to ask, if you
are sort of in a stuck idea
or belief system that
seems to have friction,
then you simply ask the
question, how does it serve me?
>> To recognize if you're
having an issue or an obstacle,
then you must have a belief
that's out of alignment with
your actual effortless,
flowing nature.
And you can ask,
then, if you are
choosing this illusory belief,
this discordant belief.
Somehow you are
defining it as being
the most pleasurable
and least painful
choice, based on your current
set of beliefs and definitions
about what is available to you.
When you get to the bottom
of that, or the top of it,
or the side of it, or
get in the middle of it
in any number of ways
available to you and realize,
I had this discordant
belief about it.
And that then I realized
that isn't accurate.
And no longer does that serve
me as the most pleasurable
and least painful
choice to make.
Person stops making
that discordant choice
and will replace it within
a choice in belief that's
more in alignment with
their actual nature
and then move more in alignment
with their actual nature
of being, putting out
more beliefs in alignment
with their actual nature and
getting back more experiences
in alignment with that.
What you put out is what
you get back in a sense.
What you put within is
experience you live within.
Always you choose
to put out what
you perceive is closest
to pleasure and farthest
from pain.
What you perceive
as pleasure and pain
is going to be unique
to each of you.
So the idea then is to choose
that you're always putting out
that which is most in alignment
with your actual heart nature
and farthest from
that which would
be out of alignment
with your actual heart
nature, your actual true,
unconditionally loving nature.
That you exist here and now
is the one that is the all.
And what you put out
is what you get back.
And those ideas never change,
but everything else always
does, thus allowing you to
have an experience of change
from one moment to the next.
>> Yes, that
resonates very much.
Thank you.
We're pretty much
wrapping up here.
Is there anything
else you'd like
to share before we say goodbye?
>> Thank you for the venue,
for the opportunity to share
and to interact with each
and every one of you,
the one that has the all that
is me, the one that is the all,
that is all, that is
the one that is the all,
that is unconditional love,
that is supporting and being
supported by itself in
each and every moment,
unconditionally sharing and
receiving, giving, receiving,
sharing and receiving, giving
and receiving unconditionally
moment to moment to moment
to moment to moment.
Always with you in this way of
unconditional love, dear one.
Thank you in all ways always.
>> There he is.
How was that?
>> Still here.
>> Are you conscious
when this happens?
I forgot to ask that earlier.
Do you feel someplace?
>> Yeah, I have some awareness.
>> OK, so you're sort of here.
You're in the backseat, sort of?
>> I have a sense of
what's being said.
But right now, I don't have
any sense of what was said.
>> Oh, OK.
Yeah, so it's of what's
being said, but--
OK, the details
are kind of vague.
>> Now, if you start bringing
up something that was said,
it will come back
to me, perhaps.
>> Oh, OK.
I see.
>> So for me, it's like when
I wake up in the morning and I
remember I had a dream.
If I sit down and start
taking notes in that dream,
then more details
can come back to me.
But if I go in the kitchen
and cook breakfast,
I could skip the whole thing.
So right now, when
I come out of it,
I'm like basically
going to breakfast.
>> Let's go to breakfast.
Well, we got it all
recorded for you, so you
could remember this dream.
>> OK, I can take part of
this meal at another time.
>> Exactly.
>> Very well.
>> A special recording--
>> Awesome.
>> --today.
>> Thank you.
I appreciate this.
>> Thank you so much.