Mother Earth is currently rebalancing herself.
Many imbalances have taken
place through the years.
This really gives us the
opportunity to go
within, to listen to our heart and soul,
and to become still in the midst
of the chaos and the fear.
It's a time to be loving and
compassionate with ourselves
and with others globally.
We need to remember that we're all one.
This is an opportunity for humankind
to come together
and to support each other.
So let's focus on what we have in common.
We are all human ...and set aside
the mind and the ego differences.
And the Earth has been letting us
know that we need to respect her
in a much deeper way than we have.
Let us listen to our hearts and
our souls and learn to live in
harmony and balance with each other,
with ourselves and with Mother Earth
It's a challenge to not get lost
in the fear, I know that's happening.
And the star beings as well
are assisting us during this time.
Ever wonder if there's intelligent
life elsewhere in the universe?
Well, I have....I've been wondering since I was a kid.
My name is Reuben Langdon.
And on March 29th 2007, in the middle of the day,
I saw a number of strange objects in the sky.
Coincidentally, I was working on
the film Avatar at the time, playing an alien.
And ever since then I've been on a quest...
A quest to find out if aliens really do exist and if so...
...are they here with us?
If beings of higher intelligent are here...
...what is their purpose?
Why don't they make themselves more known?
Why the secrecy?
I've asked these questions to many experts,
yet each seems to have a different theory.
So I thought to myself,
why not ask the aliens directly?
So that's what I set out to do!
Well, sort of...
>> Robert and Jacqueline,
thank you for being here.
You say that you're hybrid
human extraterrestrial,
and you have actually
DNA that's hybridized,
and you've also had just an
amazing set of encounters
and experiences ongoing
with different beings,
so I'd love to get into that.
And it seems that we're all
hybrids to some extent.
Did any of the
beings that you've
interacted with sort of tell
you what the basic human soup
genetics-- did they mention
which ones are involved?
>> I don't know all of the
races that were involved.
I would think-- a
lot of people say
there's 12 original races
that came down and started
messing with our DNA.
It sounds right to me.
I do know that these beings
have been modifying human DNA
since humans have been human.
They've been doing
this for thousands
upon thousands of
years, you know?
But as far as what
species, I'm not
too exactly sure which ones.
Do you know which?
>> Well, I do believe
the Anunnaki are key,
pretty key in terms of having
a hand with altering, or--
I'm not quite sure
how to say that.
>> Genetically manipulating--
>> With creating
some of the genetics.
And I was told that there is
a council of beings who kind
of were-- they created
this experiment,
and that they all had a hand
in putting in different--
all of their DNA
in different ways
in terms of seeing
how that might go.
>> So we all could be literally
walking hybrids of different
species, different things.
>> Totally.
Totally.
>> And I think the reason we've
been asked to step forward
as hybrids is we have-- this
is the way I think about it.
We have a much higher
frequency of star beingness
than most other people.
And we are weird, or
different, or fringe,
or however you want to
say that with our skills.
I've had wild things
happen through my life.
>> During many of my interviews,
I've talked to people who are
sort of telepathic
or have abilities.
And a lot of them say
around the age six,
I was visited by a
thing, or I saw a saucer,
and it seems to be an ongoing
theme that they probably
already had it in them, but this
experience sort of woke them
up.
>> Activated.
>> Activated it.
Do you guys recall
around that age having--
>> I got my implants
when I was five.
>> Five, OK.
This goes to the ignorance
thing of a five-year-old.
I remember when I was--
what is five?
Like first grade?
Kindergarten?
Around there?
>> Kindergarten.
>> Yeah.
>> Kindergarten?
I remember going to
the school library,
and the librarian
would be reading books
and they would talk-- it
was a book about a kid that
had cancer, right?
And the kid was talking
about how he was feeling
these lumps in his mouth.
And it wasn't like
just, I would say
a week after I heard that
book, I was feeling two lumps
under my tongue.
And I remember going to my
mom, mom, mom, there's lumps--
there's lumps under my tongue.
There's lumps under my tongue.
I got cancer.
She's like, oh, no, son, there's
lumps under everybody's tongue.
So I just kind of like--
I always played with them.
They stressed out, like,
I know it's cancer.
But--
>> I'm feeling around
my mouth right now.
I'm like, oh, I think
I feel some lumps too.
>> Yeah, right?
But you know, I actually--
I can grab them
and pull on them.
Even my dentist doesn't quite
really know what they are.
>> Oh, wow.
>> One's about the
size of a little--
like, shaped like a teardrop.
It's a grain of rice, but like
a size of a grain of rice.
And then the other one's
like a little tiny ball.
>> Interesting.
>> And they flip.
You can flip them
around and everything.
>> You can flip the--
no, that would be freaky.
OK.
>> But yeah, so it
started at five.
Five is when I got
those implants put in.
>> Interesting.
So that's the implant--
those are implants.
>> Yeah.
>> Interesting.
And at that age, were they--
were you sort of aware
and told that you
were getting implants?
Or you were just--
>> Oh I'm totally unaware.
>> Or that came later.
>> Totally unaware, yeah.
It came later.
>> All right.
And these are from
the Mantis beings?
>> I believe so, yeah.
>> OK, well, speaking
of Mantis beings,
I've had sort of a personal
experience recently with them.
And it's interesting
because I haven't--
during all these interviews I
do with different ET collectives
and individuals,
you know, you hear
about the Zeta Reticuli, the
Pleiades, the Arcturus and even
Reptilians.
But the Mantis hadn't
really been in my radar.
And then I had this experience
with this Mantis energy.
That's all I can say, you know.
I identified it as the
Mantis because I had seen--
in this world, you read and
it pops up every now and then.
But it hasn't been really
explored and discussed.
So I'd really like to sort
of get your viewpoints
on what are the Mantis beings.
What do they-- why
are they interacting
with humans in this way?
And sort of just your
personal take on that energy.
>> I've noticed that too when I
was starting to do my research
on the subject, trying to figure
out what was going on with me.
I noticed that there is
not a lot of information
out there about the
Mantis beings at all.
You know, there is that
the Mantis beings created
the Gray race, you know.
But--
>> I didn't hear that.
But that resonates now with
the download that I got.
So thank you for sharing.
>> So what I understand from
the Mantis beings is that,
there's many praying mantis insects running
around, different species,
different looks, different--
and it's the same out there.
But from what I understand
is that they were here
at the very beginning.
You know, they were, like,
one of the first aspects
of creation in the universe,
of physical creation.
If you think everything is
kind of like a fractal, right,
of the whole, you
know, here on Earth,
if you think of Earth as far
as humanity knows how evolution
went, you first have
your bacterial life
and then more complex forms.
And then finally, you get
into the insects, and then
the amphibians and
the reptiles, right?
Because the
conditions are harsh.
So you need that
exoskeleton first.
So I believe-- and that's where
you're more negative Mantis
being comes from.
It's just-- the universe
is just created.
And it's chaos.
It's--
>> Survival of the fittest.
>> --radioactive.
It's survival of the
fittest, you know,
so I believe that's where your
negative Mantis comes from.
Then they evolve
to the next stage,
where now, they're not
so negative, you know?
And then evolve to the next
stage, to the next stage,
and to the next stage.
But since there
they've been evolving
for countless billions
of years, they
exist on every single
level simultaneously
because as we know it, time
is more circular than it
is linear, as we experience it.
So they exist just on
every level simultaneously.
The ones that we
interact with, they've
evolved beyond
their exoskeleton.
So they don't have the
harder shell anymore.
And they're extremely
benevolent and extremely loving.
The reason why they're here
interacting with Earth,
these are creator beings.
If you imagine,
they're so evolved
that just one of
their consciousness
has the ability to be
aware of everyone's
conscious-- every living
things' conscious on the planet.
It can literally encompass
an entire galaxy,
whereas we can only
experience and comprehend
these walls around us.
Because I can only see and
perceive what's around me.
They have the ability to
perceive galaxies, you know.
So they're just here.
I think they're just here mostly
to observe but just to help.
And alls they want to do
is help humanity evolve.
And they also want to
help create new divine
expressions of creation.
So that's pretty much
why they're here.
>> Interesting.
Jacquelin, you want to
piggyback off of that?
>> Yeah, I've had a lot of
interaction with the Mantis
beings.
And when they come and
talk to me-- and also,
I do star origin
readings for people.
So a lot of the times--
well, a number of times,
those people will be Mantis.
So I get to have the
interaction with different types
of Mantis beings.
And then I'm clairvoyant so
they show me where they're from.
And actually, I go there from
that frequency, I'll call it.
And what they have
shared with me is--
I agree in that they
are very, very highly--
one of the most--
I believe, one of the most
highly evolved cultures,
and that they did certainly
have a hand in creating,
and creation, in creating
the universe as we know it.
And some other races do as well.
But the Mantis,
they are very highly
evolved beings,
incredible healers.
And they're very playful.
They love to laugh and have fun.
So they show up at my
house all the time.
And I-- they like to dance.
It sounds silly, but they
like to do movements.
And one morning I was
actually laying in bed.
And eight of them
showed up in my bedroom.
This was very calming for me.
Yeah.
And I go, good morning.
And they said, we would love for
you to get up and move with us,
or some people might say dance.
And that sounds kind of silly.
But they have--
>> A little more than exercise.
>> Any being that has
evolved understands play,
the concept of play
and joy and laughter.
And I said, oh, I don't
want to, but I will.
>> [LAUGHS] Talk about
getting dragged out of bed
in the morning.
>> I was.
I was dragged out.
>> Could they at
least make you coffee?
>> I was complaining.
And so I got out of bed, OK.
And I started moving.
And my whole neck snapped.
My whole spinal column aligned,
and my whole neck snapped.
And they had aligned my whole
spinal column and neck just
like that.
>> Wow.
>> And so I thanked
them for that.
>> So like a cosmic
chiropractic appointment.
>> Absolutely.
>> And so they interact.
And they come to
me, and I draw a lot
of the symbols they give
me to share with others.
And actually, yes-- so I have
interactions with them often.
And even though they're very
high creators, and where
they come from, where I have
visited, they just of course
all telepathically communicate,
because they're energy.
And they have showed a little
about their culture with me.
And there's a temple that I've
been to at least six times.
That's just-- it's like a
crystalline temple that's
a spiral.
And they've taken me
through, showing this to me.
And I've been
through the spiral.
And earlier on, what
the Mantis beings
did was invite other
cultures, other races
to come that they felt were
ready to come and engage
with being a part of a--
it's not really a ritual
but with experiencing
this crystalline
temple where they
would go through the spiral.
And it would actually
help their DNA to evolve.
>> So the actual physical
structure of the temple was
like a spiral form.
>> Yes.
It's-- and it's not
density like here.
It's more of an etheric,
crystalline frequency.
It's just incredibly beautiful.
So I have a very high respect.
But yet, they're very
playful and can be very silly
and give you information
that's just amazing.
On this New Year's Eve--
I was sharing with
Rob that eight of them
showed up at my house.
There was a white Mantis being,
so there's different species.
Some show up to me as being
a neon purple, blue green.
There's brown.
There's all these
different species.
So they all showed up.
And they were around
me most of the day.
And I understood
they were preparing
me to write down this DNA
code from them, which I did.
And after I wrote
it down, I shook--
my body shook for half
an hour because it
was such high frequency.
And I thanked them
because I was so
moved that I could have the
opportunity to allow that,
to just sit and come through.
And actually, it
was on the screen
when I had given my talk.
>> Oh, OK.
>> And actually-- yeah.
So-- but they're very loving,
kind, compassionate fun, fun,
fun beings.
>>Would you have any idea of
what dimension or density
that the majority of
these beings reside in?
>> Well, you're asking
about the Mantis.
>> Yes, the Mantis being.
>>From my perspective--
and again, there's
different species that are
in different frequencies.
>> Yeah.
>> Those who I interact with,
I would classify them more with
the angelic realm definitely.
And when they appear
to people sometimes,
they will appear with the
wings to not scare people.
And they're not truly wings.
It's their energy around them.
But that's how highly
evolved they are.
>> So it's almost beyond
physical form in a collective.
>> Absolutely.
Yes.
>> The best way to describe
it, it's like a drop of water
in an ocean of consciousness
is what it is really.
And there is a singular
consciousness amongst them.
But they do have a--
it's not a hive mind.
It's a collective.
>> A collective.
>> It's like an ocean
of consciousness.
>> Yeah, we've explored-- in
past episodes we've explored
Peleiadian collectives,
different densities
and dimensions of
the collectives.
And it sort of seems that
from seventh and beyond,
individuals sort of lose their--
they don't lose it.
They still have their individual
experiences and ideas.
But then they start
operating from
a collective consciousness.
>> Well, and there's
no ego involved.
Humanity, we have the ego,
and we need the ego here.
But they don't.
It's a whole
'nother experience--
>> Yeah, it is a weight--
>> --without the
ego, they understand,
they know the oneness.
We do too.
You know, everyone really does.
It's remembering.
But it's just
there all the time.
It's a oneness, the love,
the harmony, the peace.
>> Yeah.
It's a curious-- you know,
it's infinite curiosity
is what it is.
Because--
>> Curiosity on
their behalf or--
>> They-- they're just curious.
And it gets into how
the universe was created
and why we're all curious.
>> We're all curious.
>> It's interesting.
The download I got-- and
you mentioned angels.
So I sort of made
the correlation.
So this-- the visitation I
had was on the lunar eclipse.
>> What perfect timing.
>> Yeah, when was it, the
end of September last year?
>> Yes.
Oh.
>> And it went on
for a couple hours.
And I was shaking and
got a full on experience.
And I've never had--
I've been doing this kind
of work and interviews
and everything and ET
realms for a long time,
but I've never had a
personal experience.
>> That's wonderful.
>> And I was sort of getting
this download of the creation
not of the universe but
of the human experience.
And then I related--
so the Zetas came up,
the Grays, and also,
a lot of Reptilian
stuff came up.
And I sort of saw--
they were presenting to me
telepathically images of--
and what I was I guess
translating in my own--
with these images,
having to translate,
and feelings, and all sorts
of stuff was happening.
But I saw how Reptilians
saw them as Angels.
Does that resonate?
>> Yeah, if you think
about it, you know,
you hear a lot of abduction
experiences where the Mantis
beings always
playing an observer role.
They work with every--
all the beings, all of them.
They don't like to-- they don't
interfere with the other races
so much, you know?
They're just they're
mostly to observe,
to understand every
aspect of creation.
And so a lot of
the time, they're
just there as observers.
>> Yeah, that's--
I got that there was a distress
call from the Reptilians
in a way that they
wanted to evolve,
I guess, out of their
Reptilian archetypal structure.
And in order to do so, they
called upon the Mantis,
just like we would pray
to an Angel in that sense.
And then the Mantis
beings came in.
And I guess that's how
the human experience was
formed, to help the evolution
of this Reptilian consciousness.
>>They also have--
I do know they also have--
they have symbiotic
relationships
with a lot of beings too
because for an example,
there's is a race of beings.
They would look like a Gray.
They look just like a
Gray, except for the ones
that I've seen there,
they have a small head.
They're really short,
like, three feet tall,
wear a black
jumpsuit type thing.
They have these
lines on their faces
that are just like wrinkles.
And they were
created so that way,
the Mantis beings can
interact with lower dimensions
sometimes.
A lot of times,
when the Mantis work
with me, these little Gray
guys, who act as a barrier of--
because I've had an
experience where I was eating.
My wife made some jalapeno--
bacon wrapped jalapeno poppers.
She put the toothpick into it.
And I was just
gobbling them down.
And I accidentally
swallowed a toothpick.
>> Oh, no.
>> And so--
I was like, OK, well,
it doesn't hurt me now.
I had a little upset
stomach, but I'm
going to have to deal
with this tomorrow.
It's like 12 o'clock at night.
I mean, I'm really bad
about going to the doctor
when I'm supposed to.
But next thing I know, I feel--
my body starts stretching out.
And I'll see these
little beings walk in
and the Mantis
being behind them.
The Mantis being says, you know,
this is going to feel weird.
And the little guy puts
his hand in my stomach,
and it goes into my stomach.
If you've ever a hand
go into your stomach,
it's the weirdest feeling ever.
So I snapped out of it,
out of my paralysis.
And I grabbed the
being by the head.
And I had my thumb in
it's mouth, you know?
And it's chewing on my thumb.
I could feel it's little
gums, and it's saliva,
and it's soft skin.
And the Mantis being just
waves it's hand over me.
And the next thing I
know, I'm having a dream
where I'm chasing butterflies.
>> Oh.
>> So the Mantis being, they've
evolved to the point where
their minds can
manipulate matter.
So let's take this pillow--
>> Levitate.
>> Let's take this pillow
for an example, right?
They have the ability
to make the electrons
and atoms in this pillow move
to match their frequency.
And so they can just
move through it.
So it's all-- they're just
masters of the universe.
So they don't even
really need technology.
>> Right.
>> And the work that they do
with the Reptilians is--
like, they need this,
and helping them evolve
and just to observe everything.
>> So did you get
the toothpick out?
>> Yes.
It was out.
It did get out.
That was fine.
But what a weird feeling, having
a hand digging in your stomach.
Oh, weird.
>> Well, for years, people have
been trying to get Robert and I
together--
>> OK.
>> --you know, over
the phone and that.
And we both had so much
going on at the same time,
we just did not connect.
A couple years ago, I
came to this conference.
And Robert was here as well.
He was staying in
a separate place.
And I was actually getting
ready to leave the conference.
So all these people
were around us, saying,
you two gotta get together now.
Now's the time.
Now's the time,
which was awesome.
And we came together.
And we were looking
at each other.
And we couldn't even speak.
Our mouths just fell open.
And we were just like,
holy cow and knew
we are on ships together, have
been, are on ships together,
and that we have this really
close Mantis connection.
And we just really clicked.
We spontaneously, when
we were together--
and there were a few
other hybrids around--
we spontaneously did
the Mantis bow together.
And--
>> The Mantis bow?
>> We had never--
there was no way either of
us could have known that.
You know what I'm saying?
We had never-- we just
spontaneously did it.
And then we went into speaking
the way we do as Mantis.
And then we just
had so much fun.
Everybody was having fun there,
watching and enjoying it.
And so he and I, Robert and I
have been very connected since.
We talk a lot over the
phone and have discussions
that most people
would not understand,
that's Mantis.
So we get to share these
wonderful happenings
and frequencies.
And that is very special for us.
>> The best way I put it-- it's
like a similar feeling that
people can relate to, it's the
same thing as two Americans
living in Russia, for example.
And we don't speak
Russian very well.
And now, of these two
Americans, we meet.
And oh, not only are
we two Americans,
but we're from the same
state or from the same town.
So we have this really, really
unique connection that Russians
wouldn't be able to understand.
This is the exact same
feeling, you know.
>> So you had this greeting.
Was sort of an unconscious bow--
>> It just happened
spontaneously.
>> --greeting that
just happened.
And when you say
language, is it actually
another separate
language language?
It's not English?
>> No.
>> Wow.
And is it-- and you
understand the words?
Or is it more intuitive?
>> It's more of a frequency.
If you think about
it, they don't really
talk in a language.
It's more of a frequency.
So it's like a psychic
vibrational connection that you
just-- it's hard to understand--
>> So you're not actually
moving your lips then.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, you are.
>> Oh, it's out loud, yeah.
Everybody thought
we-- it was fun.
>> It's a physical
manifestation of communication.
>> Of the energy.
Because you can't bring
it through in English.
It's a frequency.
And the voice shifts in
all kinds of ways to--
it just comes through.
It's so pure.
And--
>> It's not a learned thing.
It's just--
- It's a natural thing.
>> It's a natural
soul kind of language.
>> Interesting.
>> I've had a being say once--
another hybrid, they're just
full on realized, you know?
And they're able to bring
their full ET self in.
>> Right.
>> They say, everybody uses
the harsh words, you know.
It's hard on our ears.
It hurts our ears.
Why can't they speak
like you speak?
Why can't they
talk like you talk?
When you do the language, it's
like it's just a frequency.
It's a--
>> Harsh words meaning
English being harsh words?
>> Because the vibration of our
language is a third dimensional
language, so if you imagine,
it would be like someone who
listens to Mozart now
having death metal played
in their ear.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Yeah, I can see that.
>> That's the
difference, you know.
>> That's very-- the
energy here is very harsh.
>> Yeah.
>> OK, yeah, OK.
So speaking of the mission
then, let's get into that.
What is the mission?
Why this contact?
Why the hybridization?
Why-- what's going on?
>> It's really a
multi-dimensional thing, right?
So there's many, many layers
and different aspects to why.
One of the reasons
why, for me anyways,
they had to do a little bit
of the tweaking so that way,
my consciousness could
incarnate into this body, right?
Now, that doesn't make me--
in all reality,
it doesn't make me
much different from me and
you because when it happens,
I have the same thing.
I forget.
I don't have any memory of this.
So what happens if, like,
you want to understand
what it is to be--
let's see-- an ant,
for an example, right?
Well, you would come and live
the life of an ant, right?
You can't just like--
you can sit there and
study them all you want.
But actually get to understand
it is to incarnate as one.
>> Sure.
>> And it could have
the exact same--
not as superpower ant.
Sure, some things
do bleed through,
like some psychic
things and whatnot.
But as far as me, it's--
I didn't have the
psychicness or any of that.
Well, I'm sure it was there.
I just didn't realize it.
But--
[LAUGHTER]
But you know, to live
a human experience,
to go through the
childhood, you know,
and the harshness
of this reality.
So that way, I can
better understand
what it is to be a human
being, just so I can understand
humanity so when they do
come to introduce themselves
to humanity, they
can now figure out
how can I do this without
completely destroying
this civilization.
So now, if you go back
to the ant analogy here,
imagine now you, as a person,
looking at an ant colony,
right?
And let's say someone came by
and kicked the ant hill, right?
And now, we're coming
down, looking at it.
I mean, as a person, how do I
make these ants not go crazy?
You can't just take your
finger, and you put your finger
in the ant hill--
>> They'll bite it.
>> They're going to
go crazy, you know?
So you just have to
sit back and observe.
And the only way we can--
the only way they can help the
ants now is to go in as an ant
and tell the ants, hey, guys,
don't worry about the big dude
up there.
Don't worry about it.
There's no need to panic.
>> Just rebuild--
>> They're only here to help.
>> Or the big dude up there
just wasn't paying attention
and kicked over the hill.
>> Exactly.
>> Right.
So we just gotta
rebuild the hill.
>> Exactly.
And so a lot of us
come down to help
so it's not so frightening.
And I know it's
frightening because I've
been through the fear.
And that was part of my
mission, if you will,
to go through being
ignorant, being--
I mean, I was go, George
Bush, you know, at the time,
and bomb Saddam.
And I was, like, ignorant,
just a typical American.
You know, America, woo!
You know?
>> Nice.
>> And then all of a
sudden, it's like I said,
a ET comes around.
And I just-- it scared
the daylights out of me.
And they didn't want--
they didn't like--
>> So you really did.
Most of us sort of have this--
slow, for me, I discovered
spirituality and martial arts,
and you know, kind of
been digesting this stuff.
So you went from George
Bush to Mantis being.
>> Oh, my god, yeah,
a Mantis being.
>> Wow.
And it-- I mean, I believe that
most of the human population is
completely unaware of and
ignorant to the reality of--
>> Reality.
>> Of reality, exactly.
>> What we know reality is.
>> What reality is.
>> Yes.
>> So I ended up becoming
a fractal of what I believe
what's to come.
And that's contact
with the beings.
And so what's going
to happen at first,
when most of the population
just has the truth smack him
in the face--
you know, the same
thing happened to me.
The truth smacked
me in the face.
So now that I have
that experience,
I'm able to tell people,
it's OK, it's OK.
You know, I've worked the steps.
I've gone through the
trials and tribulations.
>> In a short amount
of time it sounds like.
>> An extremely
short amount of time.
>> Huh.
Congratulations.
>> Thank you.
>> You're here.
You're alive.
>> I'm alive.
And you know, it's
been a nightmare.
I mean, if you want to
get into how it started.
But you know, if you want
to do your mission first.
>> Well, I've been an animal
communicator for 36 years
professionally.
And I've always been
telepathic and psychic.
Earlier on, I had
dreams that came true,
and knew when someone
was going to cross over,
which was not fun
to know sometimes.
>> In the-- with the animals?
Or with people.
>> With humans because I
worked with both people
and the animals psychically.
And so it's been a rough road.
And my abilities
developed earlier on
because I had a near-death
experience at six years old.
So I went into all those realms
and knew it and came back
with that.
But in terms of that, it
unfolded for me in that--
I've been through some very
tough stuff in my life,
as most of us have, and had
another near-death experience
in my 20s.
And that really set me on
my path with all of this.
And so it really kicked
me in super high gear
into using telepathy.
I was-- other things were
going on psychically as well.
So I chose to use those energies
to communicate with animals
and to be of service, to give
the animals a voice so people
could understand the animals.
And then I was working
psychically with people
as well, doing psychic
readings for people.
And then when I fully realized
I had the ET frequencies and all
of that, then I started
opening and really unfolding.
Things started unfolding
for me to get into that.
And so I see my mission
as giving the message
that we are all one
and helping people
to get in touch
with who they are.
Because the star
readings I do helps
their star families show up.
And I just get them
connected and give messages
and give them tone mantras
to do that really connect.
So I love doing that.
It's great fun.
And also, I'm a certified
hypnotherapist and work
with experiencers to help
them process their experiences
because I've been
through it all,
I mean, really with positive
experience with beings,
not so positive
experiences with beings.
And I certainly understand the
human experience pretty much
from A to Z, I can say.
>> It's a pretty wide spectrum.
>> It's been an
interesting life.
And I'm glad I'm at where I
am at and so grateful to be
here and have many miracles.
I mean, I have had two NDEs.
And another time, I almost
died about 11 years ago.
So it's been quite a walk.
>> Is that from an actual
physical event and then--
>> Yeah, just some--
yeah.
>> OK.
>> So I've had a lot of
miracles in order to stay here
and continue sharing.
I love sharing with people
and talking about all of this
and about star
beings and sharing
about the different
kinds of cultures
of star beings and their
languages and symbols.
And so I'm doing
a lot of that now,
light language and
symbols with people.
And that's-- I can't think of
anything to do that would be
more fun.
>> Wow.
Well, getting back to your guys'
interactions.
Do you have actual memories
of being on the ships that you
might be able to share and
what those experiences--
and what entailed--
what's going on,
or what happened.
>> Oh my.
>> If you want to.
>> I do, but I'm trying to think
of which one would be--
I'll give you two, two experiences
that I would say are my most
profound experiences ever.
And I drew pictures of it.
To recreate my experience,
I'll let you check them out.
>> Oh, please.
>> The one-- one of my most
memorable was when I have
an experience, I call it--
I come into
consciousness or become
aware of that I'm
having the experience,
'cause you go to bed,
and next thing you know,
you're having an experience.
So all of a sudden--
>> Like a lucid dream.
>> Exactly.
But it's not-- it's not a dream.
I can tell the difference
between a dream
and an experience
because there's touch.
There's texture.
There's smell.
There's taste, you know.
It's just like-- you know,
in dreams, you don't get--
we don't get this, you know?
So I'm able to
tell the difference
between an actual
experience and a dream.
And in this particular
one, I came into awareness.
And I remember--
how do I start this?
Because it's so
multidimensional.
I remember being able to
see 360 degrees around me.
I was smaller.
I was probably about the
size of a tennis ball.
And I was inside--
I remember seeing--
here's my perspective.
I'm seeing hands like this and
a being's face staring at me.
And then I look around.
I can see around the being.
And my body is in a chair
like this, slumped over.
The top of my head was removed.
And you could see my
brain with all the veins,
and all the layers of--
the film layers.
And there's three beings
there rubbing their hands
through my brain.
And so what I realized
was what I was, they
pulled my consciousness
out of my body,
and was holding my consciousness
in my hand, which we all
are just this little
spark of divine creation.
>> This is the 21 grams.
>> Yeah.
That's exactly it.
And there's no-- when you're
in that state of consciousness,
when you're pulled out from
your body, there's no fear.
There's just curiosity.
I remember thinking, wait.
Where am I?
Wait.
Is that me?
Yeah, that's me.
And then the being
goes-- the being
realized that I became aware.
And it goes, oh,
oh, oh, hey there.
Hey, why is a
giraffe's neck so long?
And I said, I don't know.
Why is a giraffe's neck so long?
And it says, because
of its vertebrae.
[IMITATES LAUGH]
And I remember just
cracking up, right?
And I mean, I
remember thinking, I
can't believe that
this being just
made an attempt at this joke.
That's a terrible joke,
but it's hilarious.
And my body--
I'm looking around, and
my body goes... [SLOW LAUGH]
>> Wow.
That's got to be so crazy.
>> Human joke.
>> Tell me about it, right?
[LAUGHTER]
You know, it just
melted my brain.
And this is before--
this is when my experiences
were starting, so at that time,
I wasn't quite really--
I was just, like, coming
in, like-- so when
I woke up the next--
all of a sudden, black.
And I woke up, feel
like I hit by a train.
There's no marks on my head.
>> Right.
And did you ever get what
they were doing to your brain?
>> A little later, yeah.
But at that time, I had no idea.
It freaked me out.
And I was like, waking up back
in my body, back in my self,
going what the was that?
That's like saying,
what the was that?
You know, it scared
the crap out of me
because I was getting
sick at that time.
At the beginning of my
experience, I was 210 pounds.
Went to 120 pounds.
And the doctor said I was dying.
And they didn't know why.
So at that time, I
was thinking, oh god,
what are they doing to me?
They're killing me.
And this is bad.
That wasn't the case.
So you know, I wake
up the next day.
And I'm just freaking out.
I had to go to work at 6 o'clock
in the morning at a hardware
store that I worked at.
And I can't call in
sick and say, hey
I was abducted by
aliens last night.
Can I not come in to work today?
Yeah, so that was
my most profound--
>> Yeah, that's--
>> --experiences.
I found out later they were
just repairing the damage that
was done to my brain through
being diagnosed with ADD
and having the
anti-depressants my whole life.
And they were just repairing
the damage that was--
>> Wow, they're repairing
the pharmaceutical damage.
>> Correct.
Yeah.
>> Interesting.
>> And I had a similar
experience where they went
into my brain as well to
recalibrate, they told me,
that they had to reset, and
recalibrate some things
after something I had gone
through physically, with hitting
my head.
And so it's a really--
and I was awake.
I mean, I was very aware of it.
It's such a weird feeling
because I could see my brain.
And I knew what they
were doing, so I was OK.
But they had their
hands in my brain
and just shifting
some things around.
And they said, it's all OK.
And I really trusted that.
And they actually
levitated me above my bed
several times when I was
still getting into all this.
Because they came one
night to recalibrate me.
And I was like not as OK.
I mean, we've all
been through our fear.
Even though we're hybrids and
that, we're like anybody else.
We've been through our stuff.
And so they showed
up in my room.
And I was in bed.
And I started running
for the door, thinking--
I couldn't open the door.
I couldn't.
And they levitated me, like,
five feet up over my bed.
And I'm just, like,
being levitated.
And they said, do you think
you can calm down now?
And I just was on
the bed, paralyzed.
And then I was gone.
So the next night,
they came again.
And I got up to run again.
And they said, are we going
to go through this again?
And I went, no.
And I turned around and
went back into the bed.
And then I was just gone again.
But we've had to work
through our fear of it.
Oh, my gosh, I was
being levitated.
Are you kidding me?
>> Yeah, that's terrifying.
>> I was terrified.
And they said, this is what
we're going to say to you.
If a parent's child has
had something go wrong
and they need to be taken to the
hospital to be administered to,
and the child's kicking
and screaming, saying,
I don't want to go, but
what is the parent going
to do in the end?
We're going to take the
child to the hospital.
And they said, that's basically
what we need to do with you
and to get some things--
your frequencies
recalibrated in your brain.
And so they reset me.
And that made me feel better.
And I knew they were loving,
compassionate, and kind.
It's that human response,
even if you don't want to.
But after that, I have no
trouble with experiences now.
I'm just like, hey--
>> Love the experience.
>> Good to see you.
>> And experiencing--
>> Let's go.
>> I crave them, yeah.
>> I'm ready to visit the ship.
Let's go.
But we all go through
our fear experiences
too before we fully
know who we are.
>> The thing is, as a human,
we experience the traumas of--
>> Oh, just--
>> Oh, my god, just this crazy--
Everyone I know is--
I think all of
humanity has PTSD.
>> Yeah, I mean, seriously.
I did.
>> And now we're getting PTSD
from the drugs we're taking
for the PTSD.
>> Exactly.
>> Yes.
>> Yeah, but it took me a
while to process all of that.
I mean, the next
day I was like--
you know.
But it's all a matter
of perspective.
I really want to say this,
is that some people might
be freaked out the rest of
their life from that, saying
they're evil.
They levitated me.
They paralyzed me.
They took me.
Who knows what they did to me?
That could be one
perspective of the victim.
And I don't choose
to be a victim.
I'm a part of this.
My soul volunteered to do this.
And so once I got a handle and
could get beyond the fear--
and I know I experienced
that so I can understand
when I work with experiencers
that deep fear of going
like, holy crap, what is
going on, and being taken.
So it truly is, with everything,
a matter of perspective.
>> It truly is.
>> That I'm an experiencer.
I'm not an abductee.
>> Right.
>> Which there's
a night and day,
a difference of even saying it.
>> Sure.
>> I had to-- that's one of
the major things that I had go
through was that I had the
perspective of these guys were
evil and taking over.
Oh, my god.
I went up for my first
craft, I thought, this is it.
This is doomsday.
The ships are here to
take us and everything.
And my first craft
that I ever saw--
I got a picture of that
craft I'm talking about.
>> OK.
>> It was, like, a 45-minute
encounter with a ship.
And I remember
thinking, oh my gosh.
I'm a good person.
I'm a benevolent being.
I'm friendly.
Don't hurt me.
Even my wife-- imagine
a black triangle,
almost half the size
of a football field,
with, like, black
holes up inside
of it oozing out blue plasma.
If it's a--
>> And so your wife has been--
>> She's been experiencing--
>> --experiencing
things along with you.
I guess if you're hanging
out with a Mantis,
you're gonna get something.
>> Yeah, definitely.
>> The interesting thing is
that with me and my wife,
they didn't start waking us both
up until we both got together.
So it's almost like they waited
until we had that support.
Because without her, I wouldn't
be here talking to you.
I wouldn't have survived
my tribulation period,
as I like to call it.
There's no way in heck
I would've survived it.
So they kind of waited for
me to have the support.
>> And then in turn, is she
having her own individual
experiences as well?
>> Oh, yes, she is.
Yes.
And it's amazing.
But I'm lucky that
I get to share it
with somebody, so lucky.
>> Great. I just wanna
change this battery right quick.
>> Sure.
>> and we will go
ahead and close up.
>> I can go a little longer if you want to?
>> OK, yeah.
>> I get so emotional about all this.
>> I know, I know.