It's exciting to go back to
our original, infinite consciousness.
We've been existing on Earth
with limiting beliefs.
We've created a planet of separation
and lifestyles that are
a source of stress for everyone.
But from here on out, we'll truly
begin to open and embrace infinity.
Everyone will be able to access
the information that is within.
The realities we manifest
will reflect that excitement.
When we know everything comes from within,
friction and conflicts will vanish.
We don't have to take things from others.
We've remained asleep by focusing
very strongly on the external reality.
So the outside reality seems
very tangible to us.
It looks like it's really happening.
However, awakening means
you start redirecting all that attention
on the outside back to yourself.
As you do this
your infinite consciousness
becomes much more tangible.
And reality starts to become "soft".
We'll have nothing to cling on to,
but that's part of the process.
Our old grab bars will
start to fall apart.
We'll learn that the ways
we'd known don't function anymore.
That's when we stop and pause
for the first time
to allow new information to flow through.
That's where
you can start from zero again.
Then you'll allow new perspectives.
That's where we're headed.
We're here with Ms. Ayako.
Or is it Sekino?
Sekino Ayako.
Right, Sekino Ayako
because in Japanese it's flipped.
In English we say Ayako Sekino.
I'm planning to cover
a number of topics with you today.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it.
Ok, first off, I wanted to ask this.
On the internet
you can find a few videos of
you and the entity known as Bashar,
channeled by Darryl Anka.
I found out about you from those videos.
What's the connection?
Can you give us a brief explanation?
Darryl came to Japan
to offer channeling sessions.
I think it was around 1985.
At that time I didn't believe in aliens.
I had no interest in them whatsoever.
When I heard that
somebody was going to channel an alien
I looked at it as a form of entertainment
and went to the event.
It was a three-hour session where
Darryl channeled Bashar.
I had no idea what he was talking about.
Because, you know,
it was 30 years ago.
Earth was still very much asleep
and ensconced in limitations.
Bashar's perspective was
so revolutionary.
It came from such a higher realm.
It was so freeing.
His message was to follow our excitement.
But the gap was too wide at that time.
It just didn't sink in.
But after that session,
about a week later
when I was asleep, I had a dream.
Now, looking back
I know it wasn't a dream.
I was on Essassani.
-The planet?
-Yes.
I believe I was on a mother ship.
I was inside a spacecraft.
And then I had the feeling that
I wanted to go home.
I thought
"I'd better keep my eyes closed."
Then I sensed a presence behind me.
I thought, "no matter what
don't turn around."
-Were you scared?
-Yes.
I knew something very strange
was happening.
Then there was a glass in front of me.
It curved and extended all around
inside the spacecraft.
I saw something flying outside.
Were you aware that
you were inside a spacecraft?
No, the concept of a spacecraft
was foreign to me.
-Just a strange place to you?
-Yes.
I'd somehow landed
in a very different space,
and I just knew that I wanted to go home.
I went closer to the window,
wondering what's going on out there?
It was then that I saw
triangular shaped UFOs
flying in at an extreme angle.
There were so many.
-Out in Space?
-Yes, outside in Space.
I was inside the spacecraft
looking out of the window.
I could see triangular UFOs
showing their underside, flying,
spiraling around in space.
I'd never seen an UFO in my life,
and in front of my eyes were
actual UFOs.
I was like "Wow! I saw UFOs!"
"I have to tell all my friends!"
There was still this presence behind me
and I didn't want to turn around.
The window was all around inside
and I saw a door over to the left.
A door to the outside.
Making sure I didn't look behind me,
I walked toward the door.
There was a small flight of stairs,
leading outside.
So I went out.
And then...
It was like a park.
There was a lot of vegetation,
like a grassy field.
There was water too.
In terms of what we know here on Earth,
something like a fountain.
The whole landscape radiated
such incredible energy.
It was so nice that my body felt
it would melt into it.
There was an indescribable
feeling of peace and harmony.
Not the sort we know on earth.
True harmony and peace.
All the anxiety in my body
dissolved at once.
That's when I turned around
because I was feeling so relaxed.
I saw a set of huge almond shaped eyes.
It was Bashar.
What struck me the most were
his almond shaped eyes
and his really large head.
You mean his head was really this big?
All I could focus on were those eyes.
They were so captivating.
I was so surprised that
I reacted like a child.
Just like a scared child
I jumped out of my skin!
It was with that shock I found myself,
back on Earth in my bed.
I opened my eyes and saw the ceiling.
But I knew, in my heart,
what I'd just experienced wasn't a dream.
"It hadn't been a dream."
"There are things out there"
"that we are never taught on Earth,
in school or by other adults."
This knowing was deep within me,
and resonating into my core.
My body wouldn't move.
My energy hadn't fully
returned to my body.
But I knew...
"I'll get my energy back in ten minutes
and be able to move again."
"This is not a dream."
"My state of consciousness will expand."
"There are all sorts of things
that I'd never been taught on Earth."
And I was allowing these things to happen.
That's how I felt.
Then after ten minutes,
I was able to move, and I got up.
Once I was fully awake,
I thought of these triangular crafts
swirling upward and down again.
They would made a loop, showing me
the pattern on their underside.
There were thick lines drawn in.
That left a strong impression on me.
Considering the level of the
Earth's consciousness at that time,
to tell somebody I'd met an alien
was absolutely inconceivable.
I believed that
people would think I was crazy.
It's not my belief anymore.
I called my now-husband, Naoyuki.
At that time he was Darryl's Interpreter
during Bashar's channeling sessions.
I told him that I had seen UFOs.
He was amused and brought me a picture
which showed the exact markings
I had seen in my experience.
The picture he brought me was
drawn by Bashar through Darryl.
It was exactly the same markings
that I had seen on Essassani in my dream.
It's hard to explain
to anybody but myself.
That experience really made me
wonder about dreams.
Because the times were what they were,
I didn't talk to anyone about it.
-You never had that sort of experience?
-Not at all!
You were leading the "normal"
Japanese life.
Yes, totally! I was really...
A regular person.
Even when I saw aliens on TV
I had absolutely no interest.
Entertainment, right?
I didn't even care to know
whether aliens existed or not.
But my consciousness was
expanding through myself.
I was gaining new information
with expanded consciousness
which came back online.
It was a radical change.
-So that was the trigger for a lot of...
-Yes, it really was!
I knew that everything in my life
would change.
Things like common sense were
important to me up to that point.
I thought the collective
opinion to be always correct.
That it was safest to align myself with
what the majority regarded
as being the truth.
Your common sense had changed?
-It broke.
-Oh, that can be problematic.
But for me, there was a certainty.
"I want to know," I thought.
I couldn't dismiss my experience
as just a dream.
I wanted to know the truth of it.
So about a month after the event,
I was gazing at infinite space.
I thought, "This is outer space"
because there seemed to be stars.
But then, I understood
that was just all my consciousness
that I had yet to tap into.
And I got a little scared because
I'd been taught to live a certain way
using but a fragment of my consciousness.
But I realized that my consciousness
was as vast as the Universe.
It was the first time
I ever connected with it.
It was so vast, so limitless.
Because I had never experienced
to feel limitless, it was scary.
But then...
The knowledge that "everything is here"
immediately filled me
with a sense of infinite peace.
What kind of peace?
As I saw the true expanse of
my consciousness as vast as the Universe
I knew everything to be there.
That my true consciousness holds
as much information
as the Universe itself.
All the information is there.
Far beyond you learn just here on Earth.
And knowing everything to be there
was a source of profound peace.
It was a peacefulness
I'd never experienced.
Even though the sense of having
no limitation felt overwhelming...
So there is no need to search
for answers outside ourselves?
-Because it's all inside?
-That's right.
-Because it's so big?
-Yes.
It's as big as the Universe.
That's the consciousness of my true self.
I came to understand that.
Once I realized that,
I wanted to exist here on Earth,
using that consciousness.
Not the Earthly consciousness
I'd been using with its limitations,
belief systems and common sense.
I wished to use the totality of
my consciousness
as expansive, free, peaceful
as the Universe.
Knowing everything is here fills you
with such profound peace.
That serenity and our true consciousness,
that's what I wanted to experience
here on Earth.
So from there, I...
-You returned to the feeling before birth?
-True, very true.
I started to ask myself.
"To what extent
have I been using limitations,"
"perspectives, and common sense
that I've been taught to believe true?"
As I became aware of those layers,
I began to let them go progressively
as I wanted to return to my true self.
That was the beginning.
From there, a lot of things
began to crumble within myself.
When I thought "I can only go this far"
I let go of that limitation.
And I began to expand into the vastness
of my universal consciousness.
This went on 24/7, even during my sleep.
There was this one particular incident.
Do you know about the Akashic Records?
Yes.
That information was somehow
accessed and began flowing through me.
And it was constantly
coming from my mouth.
-Speaking it?
-Yes.
I was talking even during my sleep.
It was so noisy that I'd wake myself up.
And I'd realize it was only me
so I'd go back to sleep.
Many things within me were
coming back online.
Was it your own Akashic?
No, it was the Universe's
Akashic Record, I think.
Did you receive the information
as images or feelings?
Or did they come out in a combination?
Was one expression stronger?
Mostly images?
Or mostly words?
I'd see images and
that would be translated into words.
Like in a movie, all this
information would come at once.
So as I watched the images
I would translate them.
-Like an interpreter?
-Exactly.
A part of me that is aware of
what was taking place was
allowing the download for
the part of me that is unaware.
So the information was accessed
through the part of me who knew.
It was a restoration of sorts.
There was the "limited me"
who had been fast asleep on Earth.
She'd forgotten that
all the information was right there.
It was like remembering it
through this process.
Did you understand the images
you were seeing?
No, there was no need for me
to comprehend it.
This was only happening to restore
the knowing part of my consciousness.
I was much too "asleep" then to
comprehend what was being presented to me.
I knew it was okay not to be able to
understand right then.
But I also knew that my "truth" was being
downloaded more and more.
That the aspects of me that were
preventing the truth from coming through
were starting to fall away.
I was aware of that.
But I knew I didn't need to
understand the information at that time.
I knew that in time I'd come to
understand what is relevant, and also
it was like creating a better pathway.
Clearing the pipe.
Come to think of it, this was right before
Bashar began contacting me.
I feel this was a step in preparation
to become the clearest pipe for him
as much as possible.
So that the part of me who was
asleep wouldn't get in the way,
and allow the high-frequency information
to be downloaded.
So in July 1987,
when Bashar contacted me,
it was incredibly smooth.
I see.
Did you say, it went on 24/7?
After the dream?
Yes, part of my consciousness
that was asleep was cracked open.
And the downloading began to facilitate
the higher information to flow into me.
This process went on for days on end,
for about a month.
Sometimes, I would just be sitting
and I'd suddenly lose consciousness.
For about five or ten minutes.
And then I'd wake up just as quickly.
This was so I didn't get in the way.
Since this incoming information was so
different from what I knew
it was better for me to be unconscious
so that I wouldn't question it.
Makes it more accessible, I see.
Without warning, I would slip into it
and come back to myself just as quickly.
That went on for about a month.
-I bet everyone was worried.
-I told no one about it.
-How about when you passed out?
-Only happened when I was alone.
So you didn't pass out in front of anyone?
No, there was none of that.
-If that was the case...
-Yes, they'd ask what's wrong.
Whoever was doing it, he or she
had consideration for me.
Did you ever think,
"Oh no, I need to go to the hospital!"
Never. I was fine.
-You knew.
-I had extreme faith and trust.
I have a friend who had absolutely
no interest in UFOs.
But she had a sudden download and
contacted me, freaking out.
She said, "I'm scared!
Should I go to the hospital?"
People come to me like that.
Soon we'll have the opposite reaction.
Everyone's consciousness will
start to expand.
Our gaze will widen into space,
giving ourselves permission to awaken.
I agree.
There are more and more people
who are aware
that there's more than this tiny box
and opening up their minds.
It's exciting to go back to
our original, infinite consciousness.
We've been existing on Earth
with limiting beliefs.
We've created a planet of separation
and lifestyles that are
a source of stress for everyone.
But from here on out, we'll truly
begin to open and embrace infinity.
Everyone will be able to access
the information that is within.
The realities we manifest
will reflect that excitement.
When we know everything comes from within,
friction and conflicts will vanish.
We don't have to take things from others.
Do you know about David Icke?
He's become famous within circles
of people who follow stuff like this.
He speaks of lizard, no,
I mean, reptilian.
Reptilian way of doing things.
The way of apprehending life.
Let's call it "Yakuza Mind."
A pyramidal organization.
People at the top of the triangle.
-Like on the American dollar bill.
-Ah yes, the pyramid.
A few individuals maintaining
their position at the top.
People fighting to get to the top.
That idea or consciousness.
It's a structure where everyone
becomes a slave
for the sake of the very top people.
Like the political system
that we've been using.
The system that has been
running our planet.
The top controls, the bottom follows.
The top people are considered winners
and the bottom can only follow them.
And those who refuse to fit in
that system are labeled as the enemy.
This pyramidal structure will
begin to shift into a different form.
I see it as a symphony where
each individual contributes
with their own talents.
There is the idea of equality
that everybody stands equal
with no top or bottom placing.
Everyone is equal and equally important,
in the various positions
each with its own importance.
In schools and society
the pyramidal structure
has been systemized.
You just followed that flow by default.
That's how our society has been built.
Now it's crumbling apart fast.
That's extremely positive!
It's fun for me.
But it may be scary for others.
We'll have nothing to cling on to,
but that's part of the process.
Our old grab bars will
start to fall apart.
We'll learn that the ways
we'd known don't function anymore.
That's when we stop and pause
for the first time
to allow new information to flow through.
That's where
you can start from zero again.
Then you'll allow new perspectives.
That's where we're headed.
I agree.
And that's fun and exciting.
To me, anyway.
For the majority, I think the excitement
will come when that realization hits.
Yes.
But like you already are, Reuben,
and just as I experienced,
there are individuals who have realized
the vastness of their true consciousness.
They've realized that it contains
everything that the Universe contains.
Those people are grounded
and don't waver.
For example, somebody might say
"You believe in aliens?
How very weird!"
But they don't waver.
There is no doubt in their hearts.
Thanks to the emergence of
such individuals,
others can learn that it's now safe
to be open to new perspectives.
But in the process of their awakening,
one may begin to doubt themselves.
When they are subjected to
harsh criticism
they waver, thinking
"Maybe what I'm doing is weird."
That makes others decide
it's safer to remain where they are.
There will come a time when there are
so many people on this Earth
who are truly open and
remain strong in their truth.
That's when grounding happens.
They exist with a consciousness that's
free of preconceptions and limitations.
When those people begin to
reveal themselves on this planet
they'll show others that everything can be
exciting, easy and simple.
Inventors and the like, there will be
more and more of them.
Until now inventors were
regarded as special.
Now anyone can become one.
These people will remain strongly
grounded in their truth.
They don't waver when they are told that
the mainstream perspective is correct.
They know that anyone can become free.
That anyone can return to
their infinite consciousness.
When they share that knowing
with complete conviction,
they'll incite others to
shift into that space as well.
When you're in doubt,
others will react as
"This sounds dangerous."
But there will be unwavered people
who will show others a way.
We'll see more of these people soon.
They'll become living examples
for others to awaken,
while remaining powerfully grounded
in this physical reality.
And more and more people will
also feel compelled to do so.
Also children who are being born now
are beings from the Universe
as we all are.
But they come with the knowing that
they don't need to use limitations.
They refuse regulations at school and
don't let themselves put into a mold.
They'll show true ease and natural talent.
For example, they might start drawing
without taking any lessons.
Or start playing piano like Beethoven
without training.
-There will be more children like that.
-I see many of them already.
They'll start showing the adults
what is now possible.
As I've said, these new children,
Well, they aren't actually children.
They're little people
who know they don't need
the limitations of the Earth.
They'll work hand in hand with adults
to open the parts of their consciousness
which had remained closed until now.
And re-integrate that sense of
limitless possibility.
As they're grounded in that knowledge,
they can offer an example to those
who are in doubt and afraid of
the uncertainties of the future.
They'll get a sense of relief
and the possibility of
shifting to a new way of life.
They'll feel much more stable.
So you're supporting those
who do not waver
so that they can set
examples for everybody.
They're showing others that
it's indeed safe to awaken.
I offer classes called
"Lessons from the Universe"
to those who have agreed in
consciousness to truly awaken.
As they reconnect to themselves,
I back them up and
support them in that process.
Because those individuals will in turn
contribute to creating
a sense of security for others
to open up and expand.
This is a truly important thing.
What do you teach in the class?
Can you give me an example?
In our daily lives, we each create
our own reality, right?
For example, you manifest a situation
wherein you feel "disappointed."
But that "disappointment" is
an Earth frequency which we can let go.
The frequency of our true nature
is excitement.
When you were asleep here on Earth,
just like I used to be,
when something positive happened,
you felt happy.
When it wasn't the case,
you felt disappointed.
Our emotions were focused on
the external reality.
As we awaken, we establish
a different relationship with emotions.
You project your own reality
and experience the feeling of
disappointment or powerlessness.
Those are only frequencies
and there is a way to simply remove them.
When you look at your reality
that your everyday self projects,
you can find out which frequency
of the Earth you're using.
Then you remove them.
Would that be image training
and meditation?
There is a method for turning
those frequencies into form
assigning them hardness and weight,
and then removing them.
We've remained asleep by focusing
very strongly on the external reality.
So the outside reality seems
very tangible to us.
It looks like it's really happening.
However, awakening means
you start redirecting all that attention
on the outside back to yourself.
As you do this
your infinite consciousness
becomes much more tangible.
And reality starts to become "soft".
I agree.
That is how we can start using
our day-to-day reality
to become aware of
the frequencies of the Earth.
So that you can let go of them.
There is usually a two-week period
between each class.
It's like a University course.
-A cosmic University.
-Nice.
Instead of teaching you limitations,
it teaches you how to remove them.
For my part, I've never
attended a class like that.
But I've studied a lot on my own
and received a lot of my own "downloads."
That's how I started to see
reality differently
from a broader perspective.
The best practice for you is the one
that you feel most attracted to.
And it's different
depending on the circumstances.
For example,
feeling drawn to a place.
If you feel like traveling to America,
there's meaning in that.
If you feel like staying home
that's meaningful to you too.
That's why choosing what brings joy
to your body and heart is important.
That's how you come across
information you need.
There's this fairy tale.
Are you familiar with the
story of Hansel and Gretel?
These two children leave pieces of bread
behind in the forest, creating a trail,
so that they don't forget
their way back home.
This is the analogy I like referring to.
My future self is leaving
breadcrumbs for me, lining them up.
Guiding you to the path
leading to yourself.
-Animals eat them sometimes.
-Oh my!
But if I'm attentive, I find it again.
The next breadcrumb
that my future self has left me.
And that can be information.
Or our interview today.
Everything that comes up
shows me the path.
Yes, listening to your own signs
is so important.
Following your excitement is
always meaningful and
leads you to new encounters.
The more you listen,
the stronger the signs become.
If somebody offers you advice
suggesting not to act on something,
instead of being swayed by it
you reflect on how YOU feel.
If it feels right to you
and brings you excitement
then clearly that's your truth.
Like you said, it guides you.
Excitement is the sign.
If you choose it,
you'll be on the path to your true self.
When you listen to your true excitement
and really trust yourself in that process,
you start choosing things that feel
right to you, and bring joy to your body.
In doing so, your signs become stronger.
Then you start to understand
the different types of excitement.
You'll be able to tell
if it's not right for you.
The true excitement contains joy,
so you won't hurt others or yourself.
We're experiencing a planet of separation.
When we see things
through the filter of separation
conflicts and friction result out of it.
Then we'll have the sense of
superiority and inferiority.
The ruler and the oppressed.
The pyramidal structure.
The Yakuza Mindset.
That's what leads up to wars.
But when everyone decides to return to
that vast, familiar,
incredibly peaceful self...
When everyone remembers their true self
that is of excitement,
they begin to take the time
to listen to themselves.
They're not influenced
by the outside reality
but listen to their own feelings.
You can start with small things.
Things like "What do I feel like eating?"
Instead of saying "anything is fine"
you can now
really check in with yourself.
As you make it a habit
the signs you receive become stronger.
Then you won't follow the excitement
that is not of your true nature.
I see.
Returning to my first topic,
you and Darryl did some events together.
What was the process
leading up to that point?
It started in July of 1987, when
Bashar first contacted me.
For me this was the first time
using telepathy.
Bashar wanted me to channel him.
He said,
"The people of Earth are awakening."
"We went through a similar experience.
We wish to support you."
Bashar delivered this
information to you directly?
Yes, it was from him directly.
But I was still
very much asleep at the time.
I mean, channeling
an extraterrestrial in public?
It was just unconceivable
in our deeply asleep society at the time.
But then Bashar said...
Well, at first, I was
frightened by the whole ordeal,
the idea of channeling him publicly.
So I traveled to the US,
where I spoke with Bashar
through another channel.
He said
"Are you afraid you are going to fail?"
I said, "That's exactly my fear."
Then he said "You have not failed
in the past, nor will you ever fail."
I didn't understand the meaning of it.
But I thought "There is no use
trying to run away from this."
I was starting to
become aware of my true self,
and I really didn't want to shut this out.
And it was then
I was ready to lose everything.
Even if I lost it all, it was okay.
Even though you risk losing friends,
it still felt right?
Yes, I knew people would take
their distance.
But my conviction remained strong.
I wanted to live my true self.
The part that had come to life.
The part who hadn't learnt limitations,
my essence.
If that was indeed the "real me",
then I really wanted to
experience that freedom here on Earth.
This was the "truth" I kept returning to,
no matter how much fear came.
That's how I overcame that period.
From that point on
I officially started to channel,
appearing in public events in Japan.
Did that take time?
To get familiar with channeling,
did you have to take
lessons with Bashar?
-Was it easy?
-No, I wouldn't call it easy.
But when I decided to channel,
knowing I could lose everything,
I started speaking with Bashar
telepathically.
"Yes" would come from up here,
a "No" from below.
We created rules,
things to make it easy for me.
Also, as I mentioned earlier,
there was that "preparation phase"
where I was downloading information 24/7.
The pipe cleaning.
It really was like cleaning, I think.
When I was channeling Bashar,
I would put all that
Earthly knowledge aside.
I would put aside all the laws and rules
I had learnt on Earth,
so as to become a transparent, clear pipe.
I decided to be
just a clear channel to let it flow.
That's how I proceeded.
At the time...
We all have a Higher Self, right?
We just hadn't contacted it until now.
I would connect to my Higher Self
then tune into Bashar.
When you try and reach out to
information from "higher realms",
whether you're trying to listen to it
or watch for it on TV,
this is facilitated by your Higher Self.
It's not just passive listening.
You're using your higher consciousness.
This is a great exercise.
So then, I started channeling.
No matter how far Bashar was,
on Essassani or on a spaceship,
we were in telepathic contact,
so I would receive images instantaneously.
He would send layers of information
at once like plates stacked on top
and I would simply "read" them
in Japanese.
Since my physical mind didn't interfere,
I was able to transmit
the information clearly.
So at that time,
when you put yourself aside,
did you step off to the side
consciously?
Or were you in a completely
different space entirely?
-Like in a full trance?
-Yes, everyone has a different process.
For me, since I was speaking with Bashar
telepathically from the beginning,
I would remain fully present
so I could hear all the information.
I see, you clearly understood
what you were saying then.
I was fully aware and listening,
just like the audience,
so I could apply the information
to my life.
That's convenient.
It'd be a waste to lose it.
You had an advantage compared to
other channels who go into full trance.
But nowadays there are fewer and fewer of
trance channels.
Compared to previous years,
or so I've heard.
This is only one perspective, but
without going into full trance
they couldn't receive higher information.
But now the collective consciousness
is rising and expanding.
So we can access higher information
without getting in the way.
That's what's been said.
The signal generated by people's thoughts,
which used to get in the way,
are now softening.
Yes, it's changed. It's really changed.
So, to go back to those
channeling years...
Two years.
-In the 1980's?
-Yes, it was in...
I started channeling publicly in 1988.
I met Bashar in 1987.
I spent two years channeling
starting in 1988, so I stopped in
1990...?
I channeled in 1988 and 1989.
Then in 1990, I'd already quit, I think.
That was Bashar's wish too because
Sassanis share this information to
support human's evolution.
They support us to
not just being passive listeners
but integrate the information to awaken.
Not just being a channel,
but I reconnected with my true self.
I was accessing more and more of
that information to further awaken.
He expressed deep joy at this.
The more I reconnected with myself,
the more my consciousness expanded.
It made it easier for me to access
different states of consciousness.
I then started using this stream of
information to structure it into a class.
Collaborating with Darryl was from 2008.
Oh, that's pretty recent.
You, Darryl and Bashar.
2008, 2010 and 2011.
When you're with Darryl,
sharing the stage
what's the feeling?
When we are collaborating?
Let me see.
It's always like this,
but I'm always quite plain.
-Empty?
-Yes,
Clear. Transparent.
When I take the next step,
I don't hold onto anything.
For example, when we collaborate,
even more so than doing it alone,
it's something of a challenge.
There's some concerns like,
"it's been so long since
Bashar and I have collaborated."
We've done channeling and
communicated telepathically.
But having Darryl channeling Bashar
and me there,
I wondered if it'd go well.
But for the most part,
insecurity and fear are
signs for me to move forward.
These are opportunities for me to expand.
These are doors to open.
If there is fear and insecurities,
I use that to propel me forward.
So I exchanged fear for excitement
and did the collaboration.
With that in mind
when we collaborated, it was like
the most exciting thing I could achieve.
It was very exciting.
So now, what do I say?
Bashar and I would talk back and forth.
It was a grand transmission.
It went across the stage.
It was so much fun.
I knew Bashar was having fun too.
I could tell.
So there was a first for Darryl
when he was channeling,
He stood right up while channeling,
that hadn't happened before.
Bashar was so into it,
it was a sign of excitement.
Oh, we see we just don't fit in again.
Around 1990 to 1991...
-Do you know Andrew?
-No.
He also channeled with Bashar.
Around 1992, 1991-ish.
Maybe for three or four years.
At that time, through Andrew,
Bashar spoke of you.
-Oh, really?
-From 1990, around that time.
He said,
there will be three entities on Earth
who will continue to channel Bashar.
Ayako, Darryl and...
Well, a number of people were
channeling Bashar.
But the names given, that'd be Ayako,
Darryl, and a dolphin.
-Yes! I'd heard that.
-You had?
During an public event in America
Bashar had said,
he was channeling through
only three people.
Darryl, Ayako, and an Australian dolphin
who's name was...?
Dreamer. A dolphin called Dreamer.
What's Dreamer up to?
That's something I don't know.
I didn't have a chance to meet him.
What a shame.
He should come to Enoshima and visit.
Dolphins generally have
a higher consciousness.
They have a lot of information.
-Next week I'm going to Hawaii.
-Are you going to swim with them?
I'll be swimming with dolphins.
There's an amazing vibration.
I too have swam with 50 wild dolphins.
A long time ago.
Even though I didn't know how to swim,
I was with them for three hours.
I got separated from the dock
at about 500 meters away.
I ended up in a deep ocean
because we found dolphins
and at first followed them on a boat.
When I realized
I was a ways off from the beach.
Hawaii's ocean was so clear,
I could see into the deep waters.
Freezing up in fear, I started to sink.
Blub, blub, blub,
all the air came out of me.
I thought,
"Is this how I'm going to die?"
Then a dolphin's voice
cut through the ocean.
"Oh, dolphins!"
Excited, I saw a vision.
I was wearing my diving mask.
And there was a snorkel attached.
In this vision, I saw
myself floating, looking down
through those goggles.
The dolphins were showing me that vision.
I was sinking but realized,
"That's what I need to do!"
I floated like the image.
That saved me.
These dolphins came to get me
and together we swam.
From both sides, two dolphins
held me between them.
Then we teleported.
With these two dolphins
there was a child-like excitement.
When I said "We're friends!"
I found myself surrounded by
about 50 dolphins all around me.
We didn't swam into a school of dolphins.
The two suddenly changed into 50.
They played with me like that.
It was such an amazing experience
so you should try it too.
Dolphins will come to you
when you're enjoying yourself.
I'll have fun.
By laughing you draw them near.
According to Bashar, in four years
a great many people on Earth
will come to understand
that the dream dimension is the reality.
When I heard that, I thought
getting there in just four years means
the acceleration must be amazing.
Right now I'm in that dream dimension.
It IS my reality.
I wake up in the morning
still in that dimension.
Therefore I'm always in the state of
being able to do whatever I want.
I want to tell people about it.
This is the real way of life.
As you connect to your true self
and return to that higher consciousness,
you'll remember that you can do anything.
With that awareness
you're moving through parallel worlds.
You can shift your reality freely.
-It's like a game.
-It sure is.
When you understand the function
and how to control it,
it's just a game.
You can shift to the planet
that reflects your state of consciousness
and experience it.
With open eyes, living in a dream.
That's the era we are headed towards.
Everyone has forgotten
that they're playing a game.
We're playing a game of being asleep.
We've gotten so involved into that game.
But we're on the verge of realizing
it's all a game so we can control it.
You can choose your favorable frequency.
Gradually, as we connect to ourselves,
we can zoom out and see the big picture.
Like the breadcrumbs
we talked about earlier.
If you look at a maze from above
you can see the exit.
So you can guide yourself.
It's the same idea.
When you see things from
higher perspective
you can guide yourself
who is in this physical reality.
Like, "Don't go that way. Go left."
Your Higher Self can call out to you.
The other day in a class,
the Galactic Council joined us.
Bashar works with them.
-The Council is a...
-The Association of Worlds?
It's a collective consciousness.
How should I put it?
They're close to us.
We can become one body
and do many things together.
We can give guidance to the people
who are asleep on Earth.
The more I connect to myself,
the more I can see what I can do too.
So it's fun to work with them.
This conversation made me
remember that class.
Gradually this non-physical collective
will participate more and more.
There's a reason why many UFOs are
seen but not landing on Earth.
Deep sleep creates separation.
We're quick to fight
because we use fear.
If UFOs land and we start fighting,
they'll have no choice but to fight back.
They don't want to scare us,
that's why they contact from afar.
But gradually we're raising
our frequencies.
Now finally, we can see the possibility of
joining the Council in ten years.
And the young ones
will have been prepared for it.
So the ETs are
waiting for us to prepare.
Yes, there's nothing
they can do but wait.
We're trying our best,
but really, we have to wait too.
For the people on Earth
to gain elevated awareness.
But things have really sped up.
If things keep accelerating, by next year
the subject of UFO will be open.
In general, when I talk to people about it
it's not strange to them.
Yes, that's already happening.
But once it's disclosed,
the change accelerates.
People suspect that aliens exist.
They can accept that idea.
Once they know that aliens do exist,
they reject the idea because
all they've learned is separation.
Then everything you know collapses.
At the end, you'll shed
yourself of separation
to return to "One."
It'll be a shock to know
that aliens exist.
But it's a good shock because
you need to let go of stereotyped ideas.
Once this happens,
things will change very fast.
It'll accelerate.
Speaking of shock,
when you first saw Bashar
the shock was brief, wasn't it?
How many days or months would it take
to recover from the shock?
In my case?
When I went to the spacecraft
and came back
I had this resolute knowing
within myself that I wasn't dreaming.
So there wasn't much of a shock.
I think it's the same with everyone.
It's for you to think "This is the truth."
It's different from accepting
other people's idea of truth.
Once you know your own truth,
you'll stop doubting yourself.
Then you'll start preparing
to accept the truth.
Of course,
you're the protagonist of your story.
You're the one to open the gate
to let the information enter.
Right now on this planet called Earth
there will be more people who are ready
to accept the idea that aliens exist.
They'll become the majority.
From here on out, the changes will
create some shock,
the shock of the truth.
But it'll be different from the shock
that I experienced before.
Somehow, I think
the future will be extremely pleasant.
Children and awake people are
emitting that signal.
So there's equilibrium.
Without these people
there will be just shock.
Thanks to those
who are stable and don't waver,
the shock will just be temporary.
Others will quickly learn from them
that there's no need to be shocked.
But without those awakened people,
things will be difficult.
We are like an antenna,
receiving signals.
And we emit signals as well.
So, do you think
when the time for "disclosure" comes
people won't be so shocked?
For those in deep sleep,
it will certainly come as a shock.
The extent is different.
If you don't want to see the truth,
you'll be hit the hardest.
But if you're starting to awaken
there will come a time
where you need to choose.
You may be swaying between
being awake and staying asleep.
For those who are swaying like that,
this is a good shock.
Now they have to choose.
-So they choose.
-Yes, that's what happens.
-And there are those who stay...
-Deeply asleep.
For example, people who are into
the stock market and such.
The top brass, you mean.
Like, people who make chemicals.
What you do for work is
separate from this deep sleep.
This is also a chance for those
who are in deep sleep.
But disclosure may be
a really big shock to them.
It might take a little time,
but the awakened people
will show them the way.
A wave of them will come and show others
the possibility of a bright future.
So the sleepers will be afraid, but
they'll gradually think all's well.
It's like when you're on an airplane
and there's turbulence.
When it's really terrible,
everyone's scared and
looks at the flight attendants.
When they see the flight attendants
staying calm, they feel safe.
Just like that,
when something out of control happens,
people will look at the ones who know
that this is the greatest thing ever.
The signal those people send out
is an invitation.
Not only that, our Galactic family are
all supporting us.
There's stability.
We already have those
awakened people and children.
Earth is ready.
That's why disclosure happens.
This is what I think.
The sound of truth is
different from the sound of knowledge.
You can say things just from knowledge
"The future will be good!"
"Don't worry! You can be free!"
But if you don't believe in it,
it's not convincing.
When you have the knowing,
"Our future is bright"
has the sound of truth.
That creates stability.
Returning to the conversation
about excitement,
in nature there's
nothing but excitement.
There's no overthinking.
A tree is as it is.
-In the natural world, like forests?
-Yes, and animals and such.
Everyone seems to be excited all the time.
They create and take on various forms
without thinking about it.
If it hits a barrier or a block
it redirects itself.
In regard to trees and grass?
Yes, similar to that.
But this blooms through ideas.
It thinks "I'm a lily", therefore
brings out the lilies from seeds.
Plants are not completely innocent
nor without thought.
Plants learn ideas.
There are lots of ideas in the soil.
Same around the Earth.
Just like cell phone signals,
there are lots of ideas around us.
Plants pick up those ideas.
One might pick up an idea of a tomato,
producing three fruits from one seed.
That's how it works.
Plants don't just bloom
without any ideas.
This is an Earth-based plant.
It learns ideas in the soil
and takes that shape.
When people of Earth return to the center
the signals will change.
Up until now,
we've created limitations and rules
from the idea of fear.
People have resonated in that idea
and created this planet.
But once people start to
return to the center,
that will create
an incredibly harmonic sound.
When you know that you're perfect
and you can be anything,
you'll return to unconditional love.
When bringing about this awareness,
our civilization will change.
Also, the Earth's frequency will change.
The harsh ideas will become softer.
When the idea of
"I can be anything" appears
plants will pick up that idea and
start taking different forms, I think.
-That's our future.
-I agree. Thank you.
Well, our interview became
longer than expected.
It was fun.
-Thank you for all the good information.
-Glad to hear that.
When you contacted me,
it was perfect timing and
I was very happy.
Same. Thanks for letting me do this.
What you're doing is wonderful, Reuben.
Thank you.